You'll need a car jack, a lug wrench, wheel chocks, a spare tire
tire pressure gauge road flares or
reflective triangles.
turn off the engine and engage the
emergency brake.
put your hazard lights on and place road
flares or reflective triangles on the
ground
to make yourself visible to oncoming
traffic. use your tire gauge to check
if your spare tire has enough
air pressure. if it doesn't try to get
another tire or call roadside assistance.
place a wheel chock or something heavy
under the center of each tire
before you jack the car up off the
ground. remove the hubcap
if necessary. then use the lug wrench to
loosen the lug nuts.
most vehicles have a marker in the
bottom panel indicating where
your car jack belongs. once it is placed in the proper
spot
use your jack to lift your vehicle until the
flat tire clears the ground. remove the
loosened lug nuts.
once the lug nuts are off pull the flat
tire off the wheelbase.
store all the lug nuts in a secure pile
so you don't lose the before mounting the new
tire.
line up the wheel holes with the bolts on
the wheelbase.
slide the tire as far back on the wheel
base as it can go
and place your lug nuts back on. Tighten
each nut until there's resistance.
use the car jack to lower your vehicle
until the tire is back on the ground.
then remove the jack. use your lug wrench
to rotate each nut clockwise
until they're completely tight. now put
away your tools.