The first thing you want to do is
to make sure the car is in park and make
sure that the emergency brake is applied
we don't want the car rolling away when
we get it off the jack. Second thing we
want to do
is to pop the trunk. There it is
where the rear of
the 2013 Corolla to lifted.
What's in the truck : your spare tire
, jack and all the tools to use it are
located under the trunk cover.
Lift the flap to gain access to the
tools. First thing you want to do
is to pull these tools right off the top
and set them aside.
Second thing you want to do
is to use your hand to unscrew the jack
in a counter clockwise motion to loosen
it up
and pull the jack out. The third thing is
to counter clockwise
unscrew the spare tire.
And lift the spare tire out.
Now we are going to pretend that this tire
is our flat tire on the side of the road.
You with better the jack
there the spare tire and we've got the tools
that we need.
this tool is your tire tool.
This is what we will use to loosen the
lug nuts and tighten the lug nuts.
This tool
we're going to use to jack the car
up and down as we needed.
The next step is to loosen the nuts
at least one full turn because when you jack
the car up
before you loosen the nuts the tire might
turned a little bit make it a bit
harder.
The next thing we want to do is to jack
the car up.
For safety reasons you need to make sure
that you jack it up from the correct
place.
We want to put the jack as right here on
the two notches on the frame.
There is two notches for the rear and there is two
notches for the front on this part
of the frame.
there's a slit in the jack and that's
just gonna go
right up
on that piece of the frame.
Now you wanna take the jack handle
with the loop at the end, slided it in the
hole on the jack
and turn clockwise until the tire just
lift the ground.
Now the tire is off the ground, we're gonna
finish removing the
wheel nuts. In in this process you want
to take the bottom nuts
off first so the tire doesn't fall
this way as you're taking the nuts out.
When we have all the lug nuts off, just slide
the tire right now.
Okay you want to install this spare tire
with this part of the hub sticking out
as seen.
Push the hub down there.
You gonna put the lug nuts on, taper the
end on the inside.
Top first.
Putting them hand tight
then you gonna lower your jack.
Lower your jack counterclockwise
Then you are gonna to tighten your lug
nuts with the tire tool.
Now that we're done with that stuff, that
everything is tight. You want to
basically check to make sure the tires
got enough air pressure in it
and it's ready to drive. Now we need to
put the tools back in the way that we
found them.
The first thing we want to do is put the
tire back in the compartment.
Now the tire and the jack will fit
back in here
but your tools of course won't. We have got
to put them on top.
Now we're gonna put the jack in
its place.
Like I mentioned before
the other tools will not fit in there
with with full size tire so
we're going to put the tools
right here in the trunk. Now that we put our
tools back, we're
gonna to close the trunk. We've completed
changing tire on the 2013
Toyota Corolla.