The first thing you need to do is make sure you change the tire in the
safest location available to you.
Changing a tire on the road shoulder
can be dangerous. Take two minutes to
assess the potential dangers around you
before you start.
Once you have parked the car make sure the
handbrake is on
and put the car into park for an automatic
and into first gear for manual.
Next, get out the spare tire,
Jack and wheel brace from the boot.
Place the jack on a secure flat surface.
Position it so it is directly
under one of the jacking points of the
car.
Your car manual will show you where they are.
But simply
they're usually behind the front wheels
or just in front of the back wheels.
Now just before you jack the wheel up
off the ground you want to loosen off
the nuts otehrwise depending on the type of car,
the wheel can just
free spin when you tryin to turn the nuts. so
you take the wheel brace
and you put it on to the nut and
have the wheel brace
roughly horizontal to the ground and
only with your arms straight
pushing downwards, this will be
enough for you to loosen off the nuts.
As a tip to remember which way you turn
to loosen the nuts, left is loose and
right is tight.
Use the jack to lift the car. You'll find
you won't have to lift it too high.
Remember never put any part of your body
under the vehicle that is being jacked
up.
Now remove the wheel nuts completely
using the wheel brace.
You can now fit the spare wheel
tighten the wheel nuts and then lower
the jack.
Once you're finished up, don't forget to take
your damaged tire to a shop to be repaired.