Switch on your hazard lights. Make sure the
handbrakes is on and the car is either
in gear or for an automatic
in park. If you have a safety triangle
place it "wheel" before your vehicle to
alert oncoming motorists.
Remove the jack,
jack handle, wheel brace and spare tyre
from the car
and place them on the ground. This is to avoid
any unnecessary movement of the car
once its hoisted. Finally before lifting
the car
loosen the wheel nuts slightly but don't
remove them
entirely. Different jacks have different
instructions and every car
has a specified jacking point. Be certain
to familiarize yourself
with days before hoisting the vehicle.
Instructions
must be followed exactly and nearby.
Place yourself
under a vehicle that is hoisted by a
jack. Jack the car up slightly to secure
the jack
under the car but not to raise the wheel
off the ground. Then
once you're sure of that, continue jacking
the car up
until the tire is approximately five to
ten centimeters
off the ground. Remove all the wheel nuts
from the studs
and store them in a handy place. Remove
the flat tire.
Rolled it out of the way and lie it down on
its side
so it doesn't roll away. Roll the
replacement tyre
up to the vehicle. the tyre now needs to
be lined up with the wheel studs
these can be a little tricky but with
a bit of effort
it should slip on without too much
hassle. When placing the replacement
wheel on
try to keep it as upright as possible.
This will help the studs aligned with the
holes in the wheel rim.
Once the wheels is located,
replace the wheel nut
onto the top stud as this will help to
keep the other studs located
on the rim. All wheel nuts can now be
secured
finger tight. Using the wheel brace,
slightly firm up the wheel nuts.
They don't need to be completely
tightened at this stage but the wheel
does need to be positioned correctly.
Lower the jack
and vehicle. The wheel nuts should then be
fully tightened
using the wheel brac. There's no need to
stand or jump on the wheel brace  :
the correct torque can be achieved using arm
strength.
Replace the wheel cover if necessary.
Collect the flat tire,
wheel brace, jack and safety triangle and
store them securely.
you can get back on the ride but don't
leave it  too long before you get your damaged
tire repaired or replaced.