You can change the wheel yourself.
Everything you need is in the bot:
spare wheel, jack and wheel brace. There's
also a socket to fit a locking bolts on
other wheels.
Start by slacking in each bolt by half
a turn.
Locate the jack at the mounting point
as shown in the owners manual and lift the
car so the wheel
is clear of the ground. Remove the bolts and
then the wheel.
Most of the spares nowadays are space
savers.
They must only be used to get to the
nearest car repair a
and a maximum speed limit applies. Place
the spare wheel in position
and hand tighten the bolts. Moderately
tight each bolt using the wheel brace.
Lower the car and then remove the jack.
Now fully tighten the bolts in a cross
sequence as shown. And there you have it back
on the road!