First make sure your emergency brake is
engaged.
This will prevent the vehicle from
rolling.
Next locate your spare and jack.
This can usually be found in the trunk.
Lay all your tools so they're easy to
reach.
Locate the pinch weld where the body and
the frame meet.
Slight the jack underneath and raise it
until it touches the weld.
Loosen the lug nuts just a bit then jack
up the car.
Make sure the tire has completely lifted off
the ground.
Then remove the lug nuts
and the flat tire.
Put on the spare and replace the
lugnuts.
Lower the car until the tire makes
contact with the ground.
Tighten the nuts in a star pattern. This ensures
that the tire goes on straight.
Drop the car down the rest of the way
and you're good to go.