Generally speaking your spare tyre
and the toolkit are placed in
the boot of the vehicle. It
does vary from car to car so check
your owner's manual and that'll identify
exactly where in your particular car those items are kept.
What you'll need is a wheel brace to enable you to undo the wheel nuts
you'll also need a jack to raise the vehicle to allow you to get the flat tyre off.
You start by removing the hub cap or the wheel nut covers
whatever's fitted to your vehicle, then using
the wheel brace you want to loosen
each of the wheel nuts half to approximately one turn before jacking up the vehicle.
Next, we're going to raise the vehicle to allow us to remove the flat tyre
the jacking point and the type of jack used does vary from car to car so again its worth
checking your owners manual.
Once the jack's in place you then commence jacking the vehicle to release the weight of
the vehicle from the flat tyre. Now that we've got the wheel off the
ground.
We can remove each of the wheel nuts until
all 5 or 6 or 4, depending on whatever your car's fitted with are off
and now we can remove the flat tyre. A good idea is to place the flat
wheel under the vehicle just for a safety feature in case the jack were to give way
you've then got something to support the vehicle
so lift the spare wheel up onto the
hub and make sure it's sitting nice and flat
and square to the vehicle.
Then start each of the wheel nuts by hand
then remove the flat tyre from under the
vehicle and
lower the jack. Lower the vehicle down
until the weight of the vehicle is on the
spare tyre that's just been fitted
We'll then use the wheel brace to
tighten each of the wheel nuts
in sequence. If you can't get to a tyre
repairer
in the short term it's worth checking those wheel nuts again
after a couple hundred kilometres of driving, just to make sure they are still tight
I guess the main thing is to know your vehicle, so you should be checking that your
spare tyre
is fitted to the vehicle and inflated and
also that all of your tools
are in a serviceable condition. With some
vehicles it can vary, you've got
emergency spares or space savers as they are commonly called and they're only for
literally emergency purposes to get you to a place of repair as quickly as possible
when in doubt ring RACQ and we're happy
to come and assist.