If you have roadside flares or a reflective
triangle, use them to warn other drivers that
you're working on your vehicle. Consider keeping
a canned tire sealant in your emergency kit.
If your tire has only been slightly compromised,
the sealant may patch it long enough to get
you to the service station. Step 2. Find heavy
objects ( like bricks or rocks ) to block
the wheels. Place them in front of and behind
the tire that's diagonally across from the
one that went flat. If you have plenty of
rocks, block both wheels on the opposite axle.
If you have a digital camera (or a cell phone
with a built-in camera) snap a picture before
you start disassembling everything. That way,
you'll have a ready reference guide of how
things should look when they go back together.
Step 3. Lay out your spare tire, jack, and
lug wrench. Many tires feature a locking lug
nut to guard against theft. To remove, use
the special key tool the car's manual will
specify where it's located. Step 4. Most lug
nuts follow the righty-tighty/lefty-loosey
rule. Attach the lug wrench to a nut, and
turn the wrench counterclockwise. Repeat with
each lug nut until all the nuts are loosened.
Step 5. Refer to the owner's manual for the
best spot to place the jack typically along
the frame, very close to the flat tire. Jack
the car up until the wheel is off the ground.
Never get under the car when it's on a jack.
Since it's fairly unstable in this position,
keep other people away until the car is safely
on the ground. Step 6. Remove the lug nuts
one at a time, and keep them together in a
spot where they won't roll away or disappear.
Then remove the flat. Step 7. Mount the spare
tire onto the wheel lugs. You may need to
jack the car up some more to slip on the spare
tire. Check the tire pressure on your spare
regularly. That way, it won't be flat when
you need it. Step 8. Replace one lug nut at
a time. Begin tightening each by hand, then
continue with the lug wrench. Lower your car
to the ground, and finish tightening the lugs
in opposite pairs, to ensure uniform pressure.
Once you're done, replace the hubcap. Step
9. Remove the objects blocking the wheels,
and place the tools and the flat tire in your
trunk. Step 10. Your wheel is ready, but you
won't be able to drive as quickly on a spare.