In most vehicles if you need to locate your
tire they'll usually be located in the trunk unless you're
driving a truck or an SUV, they'll usually
be located up under the car next to the fuel tank.
So in this car here, we have the Jack
on this side, we have our tools then
we have our actual tirelocated here.
So I'm gonna pull all this stuff out
and show you guys how to do this. Alright so we got our spare tire here, we've got our jack stand and we also got our tool to remove the
lug nuts. On this particular
car we also have a lug nut key to deter
people from stealing the rims off your car.
First thing we're gonna do here is look up under the
car and we're gonna look
for the folded piece of metal and that's gonna
be our actual jack point
and that's where you actually want to have the jack centered.
Now we're just going to raise the jack up a little bit.
Alright so once we get the jack in position, we don't actually wanna
jack up the car yet.
We're going to break the torque on the lug nuts
You gotta remember, right to tight and left to loose.
Now that all of our lug nuts are nice and loose now
they're not finger loose but they're loose
enough that we can deal with it, doesn't have to deal with
the torque. Start to jack the car up now.
Alright now once the tire's actually
left the ground
we can use the key to take off the lug nuts rest of the way.
Now we got our lug nuts off, we just want to
remove the tire.
At this point we put our flat tire in the back of the car
and we put on our donut.
Now with most
most donuts that come with new cars nowadays
they're good for
about 40 miles before we actually need to get the tire changed.
it's important to get it changed as soon as possible.
So now what we wanna do is put our lug nuts back on.
Don't worry about tightening them down all the way yet.
Put them on snug so they don't go anywhere.
So now we got them all snug on there we can now lower the
car back down
Once we got car back down on we can now
tighten up all these lug nuts.
Now how you want to tighten these, you wanna do it in a star pattern.
Start at the top here then you skip one.