First have it in park and on level ground. Also set your
emergency brake.
Once the brake is set, each car has a spare
tire somewhere hidden. And the jack this
one's underneath the liner in the trunk.
You can use your tire iron
to take off the hubcaps. Be careful they
can break. From the other side of your
iron, is the socket
and loosen all the bolts. Don't remove them,
just loosen 'em. Then slip the hook
right into the jack and if you look at your
jack
there's some markings underneath it on
Toyota's to show you where
to put your jack. There's two little markings
for each wheel.
Then lift the tire off the ground about
one inch
and take off all the bolts.
And place the new tire on
and put the blts on by hand. Once
each bolt is a little bit snug use your
iron
and then tighten diagonally from pole
to pole
to get all five. And tighten all of them with
the same amount of force
Once you've done all five, start over from the first
again.
Give it a little bit more of a tweak. Then
lower the jack till the tire is on the
ground
and tighten the bolts the rest of the way
again. Going on
in the star pattern diagonally give it a lot of
force and lastly when you put the hub cap
back on