First, remove the spare wheel,
jack and wheel brace from Bryce from
the vehicle.
If the vehicle is equipped with
the wheel chock use it
to chalk the diagonally opposite wheel.
Loosen the will nut before jacking.
If you're having a hard time trying to
get them undone
use your body wheigth.
Find the jacking point. The jacking point is
different on
all marks and models, so refer to your owners
manual. Make sure the jack is lifting
nice and square.
If not, lower and reposition. Do not risk it.
Jack the car up slightly and place the
spare wheel
under the car just in case the car falls
of the jack.
And remember to jack the car a little
bit higher
allowing for the fully inflated tire.
When trying to remove the wheel you may
find it fused on with rust.
Some force might be needed. Remove the
flat tire
and place it under the car just in case
the vehicle falls.
When changing the tire
never sit with your legs under the car
or put your hands at the bottom of the
wheel.
Before you fit the spare wheel, make sure
the hub
and wheel studs are clean, free of dirt
and bright.
Fit the spare wheel. Make sure the wheel
is located correctly
on the hub. This is extremely important.
Some wheel nut
can go on two ways. Always remember to
put the tapper part of the wheel nut
towards the wheel itself.
then put all wheel nuts on and tight
them by hand
before nipping them up with the brace.
Once the wheel nut are nipped up with
the brace,
you can start lowering the jack. Then you
can tighten them properly
when the car is down on the ground.
Tight opposite wheel nut
after each other. Don't go around in a
circle. Use a stop at.
Now remember if your car was equipped
with the spare tire
the full-size flat tire may not fit
correctly in the re. So there you go!