First stop the car on a hard flat surface.
You're gonna set your emergency brake,
put the shifter into park for an automatic
or reverse for manual transmission.
You're gonna stop your engine and turn on your emergency
flashers. We're gonna begin by identifying some
tools and components that you're gonna be using to perform this task.
Location ofyour spare tire and jack may vary from model to model. Please
refer to your owner's manual to find out where the location is on your model.
You're gonna access your luggage compartment and remove
any loose items or articles that may be in your way.
Remove your Jack cover to access your jack.
Once you have unhooked the jack
then slide the jack out of the vehicle.
Next remove the large plastic screw in the center of the luggage compartment.
And then remove your spare tire cover.
Next you are going to remove your hold down bolt.
Now you are able to remove your spare tire.
The tools that you are going to want to be using
are your lug nut wrench and your tire jack handle.
They are located on the bottom side of your spare tire cover.
You are going to want to remove these to be able to use them with the jack.
We are going to begin by removing your wheel hub cap using the
flat ended end on the lug wrench.
You are then going to loose each of the lug nuts about one time.
You are now ready to position the jack under the car.
You are going to put the notch of the jack on the pinch rail moulding
which is located under your car up here. There will be indentations
on your pich rail mouldings where to locate the notch of the jack..
This is the view of the pich rail mouldings.
Notice the arrow
and the indentations on your pinch rail mouldings. This is where you
place
the notch of the Jack when you are raising it.
Now you are gonna take your jack
and by hand start screwing the jack up
until it comes in contact with your pich rail moulding.
Now you can insert the jack handle
and begine raising the vehicle by twisting
the jack handle in a clockwise motion.
You are gonna raise it until the tires up off the ground.
Now you can remove the remainders of your lug nuts and your flat tire.
Using a rag or paper towels, clean the surface, remove any dirt or debris,
then you can install your
spare tire.
Install all your lug nuts and tighten them by hand.
And now lower the vehicle back on to the ground.
Using your lug nut wrench, tighten each lug nut two to three times
moving in a star pattern while you're doing it.
Use your body weight with your lug nut wrench to ensure proper torque.
We can now finish lowering the vehicle and reinstalling your jack and tools
and your flat tire back into your luggage compartment.
Once you lay your large trash bag out in your luggage compartment,
you can reinstall your tools and your flat tire back into your luggage compartment.