He locates the spare wheel and the jack.
Remove the hubcap to expose the wheel nuts.
While the car has not been raised do
drive a slightly loosens the wheel nuts.
Positions the jack in the appropriate
location.
At this stage the car is being raised to
a safe heigth
to allow the wheel to be removed.
The wheel nuts are then completely removed and
placed in a secure spot,
stopping them from rolling away.
The wheel is then removed and replaced
with the spare wheel.
It might take a little bit of fiddling
around
to align the spare wheel. Use the wheel
nuts
to fasten the wheel.
While the car is still raised, tighten
the wheel nuts
firmly.
Once the jack has been removed, you must
insure
you retension the wheel nuts again. Use
the criss-cross
method to fasten the wheel nuts.
You have safely executed changing a
tyre.
If you personally feel you are not
capable
of changing the tyre safely remove
yourself from
danger and call for assistance.