We are going to check the owners manual
so you can learn
where and how to use you spare tire.
Oh! Tires are heavy!
These are you tools to help you jack up
your car
and to take the old flat tire off.
And,
It is up to way right here : the jack.
So, using the wheel wrench, you are going to
loosen the nut half a turn.
Remember
lefty loosely right inside it.
Here you can see the jacking point is
this part right here on the frame.
Now as you remember we first loosen the
wheel nut a half turn
all the way around before we jack the car.
So now what we're gonna do is
fully remove the wheel nut and take off
the wheel cover.
And, voila : the wheel cover!
As you can see,
there is a significant difference between the
spare
and your actual tire.
So you want to get to a tire shop ASAP.
The first question you may have is :
Which side faces out?
and the easiest way to check is that
the air valve, this thing right here.
always faces the outside.
Then, you take the wheel wrench. Of course it is very
important to get these on
as tight as you can so you make it
safely to a tire shop.
So now we are going to slowly lower the car back down.
You're gonna get dirty! I have to tell you :
this is not a clean job. Alright if you remember
the trunk is where we found the spare
and now we're gonna put the flat tire in
here with all of our equipment and head
down the road to the tire shop
to have an expert check things out. After
packing the bad tire into the trunk
I carefully drove over.