To access the spare we need to open the back latch compartment
where you'll find your spare tire and all
tools that you'll need to change your flat
tire.
remove these covers from the vehicle the
so you'll be able to remove the tire.
once these covers are removed we should
be able to remove the spare tire
easily.
in this vehicle the jack is located in
the same compartment with the spare tire.
remove the locking mechanism
on the side which is in this case the
rubber band which hooks into this piece
of plastic here.
pull that to the side and slightly
unscrew
the tensioner and you can remove the jack
after that.
the jack tools and spare tire lug nut
tool
is located to the right of the spare
tire in this vehicle.
on this particular vehicle
the lifting location is located just to
the front
of the rear tire.
on the bottom of the rocker panel is an
arrow which will show you
the location of the jack when lifting the
vehicle the jack should be put on
the pinch weld
so it does not slide out. check to make
sure that the jack is located on the
pinch weld
after the vehicle starts to raise.
once you've accomplished that
proceed by lifting the vehicle slowly.
make sure that you have
firm ground to place the jack on before
you started the jacking procedure.
while the tire is still touching
ground
remove the hubcap
and loosen the lug nuts slightly.
when the lugnuts are loosened slightly you
can continue to raise the vehicle.
at this point we can remove the lug nuts
by hand.
it
Carefully remove the tire from the
vehicle.
your spare tire is now ready to install.
proper pressure for spare tires is
located on the sidewall. every
maintenance visit that you
accomplish you need to make sure that
the tire pressure
is filled properly.
install the spare on to the lug studs
and start by just latching
the lugnuts on to the threads.
Spin the nuts till the rim of the tire
so that they are snug by hand
and then grab your lug nut tool and snug
slightly.
at this point we can lower the vehicle
down so that the tire is just touching
the ground.
take your lug nut tool
and retighten the nuts
using about 50 percent your body's
weight.