Pull over where it's safe to do so, apply the hand brake
and put the vehicle into first gear. Grab
your vehicle jacking equipment from
under the mats in the boot and jack up the car
slightly from under the jacking points.
If you have any wheel chocks place them
under the opposite wheel
from the wheel affected.
If you have a locking wheel nut, be sure
to have this in hand.
place the locking wheel nut on the locking wheel nut
bolt.
Should you be using the wrench, be sure to
select the right direction.
Consult your vehicle manual to correct
all settings
if you're using the torque wrench. Remove each bolt
and keep safe nearby.
Jack up the car slightly higher to free
the wheel. Remove the wheel.
Get the spare tire from out of the boot.
Place the spare tire in position
and hand tighten each wheel bolt. Select the
opposite direction you were using earlier
if using the wrench. You may need to lower
your jacking device
ever so slightly to stop the wheel spinning.
Using the diagram displayed on this
video on screen
tighten each bolt in ascending order. Both
five bolt and four bolt wheels are
displayed.
This keeps the torque tightening equal for
all
of the bolts. Once you're done, remove your jacking
device
removed from under your vehicle along with
the wheel chock. Place both back in your boot.