Another thing you want to consider before jacking up
the vehicle is putting the parking brake
on.
Normally spare tires are located in the
trunk or
in the case of this car they're located in the hatch.
They are usually located under some kind of
access.
This is normally where you would find
your spare tire. These are the tools
the you will need to work the jack and
to get the wheel off. And this
tire is flat.
Now here's
something else to know and that is that
many times when you get your vehicle
serviced
check the air pressure not only in all
your tires but also in your spare tire.
Unfortunately this rarely gets done
so may have to request this
and in some cases you may have to pay a
little more to have it done.
Because should you ever need it and it
doesn't have any air then you're really just
wasting your time. One of the reasons why
it doesn't get done all that often
is because in order to fill this up you
have to take it out of the car and
you can do your technician a favor by a
taking all the stuff out of your trunk. I
cant tell you how many times somebody has asked
me to check the air in their spare tire
and they've got you know a hundred
pounds of topsoil,
bag a golf clubs, dirty clothes, phone books,
ak-47s.
No that was an ar-15, sorry. You have all
kinds of things in your trunk so you
want to make sure that if you are having
somebody perform this for you
to remove your personal items from the
trunk ahead of time, that would be very
helpful. A lot of times it'll say right at the
outside of the tire
itself, in this case it says inflict 260
PSI.
A lot of these instructions are also found
in your owner's manuals
and also a list of warnings here. On this
car the jack is kind of in a goofy place but
I'm gonna show you how to get it out
of here.
It's located in the back here or by
where the tire was.
Now what you can do is look for the side
with the adjuster
like this and then just twist it and this should
bring it down you can take it out.
Now that you have the tire out of the
vehicle what you need to do is you need to get
the damaged tire off of the car.
Get your lug wrench out and
this little guy, you'll need this too. The
next thing you need to do is
loosen the lug nuts. You don't wanna jack
the car up first thing. You want to
loosen the lug nuts.
If you get this wheel up ahead of time, let me
show you what will happen.
So the first thing we're going to do is
we're going to try to
take the lug nuts off. Now this seems rudimentary
to say.
In order to loosen things you turn them
counterclockwise. In order to tighten
things you turn clockwise.
These lug nuts may be on very very tight
so you may not be able to get
these loose. Like this. In fact
it's not very likely that you will. So
there's one or two methods that I'm gonna show you.
The first method is to stand on. Thats
method one.
Now you may not have the weight to
overcome this so I'm gonna show you
something that
if you're very careful about doing you
can do this.
But if you're in a pinch you can use the
weight of the car
on the lug wrench and your jack. Now what
you wanna do
is position the jack in such a way
its gonna come in contact with the
bottom of the lug wrench
like this. Try to make sure that
this fits in this little notch right here.
What that's gonna do in effect
is use the weight of the car to overcome
how tight the lug nut is. Now if you wonder
what this little hookey thing is for.
See how this is getting towards the end?
Keep an eye here to make sure this
doesn't come flying off it may get
violent.
But that is that is an alternative
method using no strength
but gravity to loosen the lug nut.
You may have to try this more than once
because you're gonna need to get it in
just the right position in order for
this to work. You're gonna
loosen the rest of these in the
conventional foot method.
Now that you have all the lugnuts loose
its time to jack the car up.
Now there's a couple of points on cars.
Modern cars
usually seem to have these points and some
vehicles actually have arrows pointing to
these areas
and there's also diagrams in some cases
that show you
where the jack points are for the car.
In this case
see this reinforced area right here right
here
is another area. What you want to do
is position the Jack under this area so
that
this notch fits right under
this so it kinda cradles itself in there.
This is called the scissor jack.
Usually a good way to get these off
to give them a little
hit but sometimes wheels get stuck
on hubs and sometimes you have to
kick them pretty hard. If you're unable
to get the wheel off a car
which does happen sometimes particularly
with aluminum wheels.
What you can do is you can put the
lugnuts back on
but don't tighten them all the way. Let
them a little bit loose
drive the car for a few feet or whatever
you have to do and
a lot of times the weight of the car will
break them loose. These scissor jacks can be
very precarious. You wanna be very careful
not to knock the car of the jack because
if you do it will hurt you
pretty bad and you don't want a bad
situation to get worse.
The next step is to put the wheel
on.
Okay now that you have
the new tire on you want to
let the weight of the vehicle off the jack so you
want to bring the Jack down.
Okay now that you've got the vehicle
back down on the ground it's solid, you wanna
tighten the lug nuts one final time. Tighten
in a clockwise direction.
You don't need to tighten these thing so
much that you are never gonna be able to get
the wheel off again.
Just make them snug you've got enough
leverage with with the lug wrench that it
should be okay.
Now that you have the spare
tire mounted it and take the other tire
and putting it in your trunk is probably the most
logical place to put it.