Step 1: when changing a tire it is
important to pick a location with a
solid level ground to ensure the
stability of the vehicle when being
jacked up.
In our situation we are on concrete so
we will not have to worry about that.
However if you are in an emergency
situation
like your tire blew on the highway call
over to the right hand shoulder of the
road and turn your hazard lights on.
Make sure that your vehicle remains
on the concrete portion.
If a car is jacked up on the sand or
dirt portion of the shoulder
the jack will sink which can cause
damage to the vehicle as well as
threatening your safety.
If you drive an automatic put the
vehicle in park
and apply the emergency brake. If you
drive a standard vehicle
place the car in first gear and apply
the emergency brake.
Step 2: locate the necessary
tools needed to change your tire on your
vehicle.
Some vehicle require
a locking wheel nut key. Before traveling
ensure that you are aware of the location
location of this tool.
Without it you will not be able to
remove the lock on the lug nuts.
The most common storage area for
these materials is the trunk of the
vehicle.
Lift the carpet and proceed to remove the
spare tire
and the tire items. Most vehicles will have the
jack assembly
underneath the carpet as well. But in the
case of this vehicle
they are stored in a compartment left hand side.
Step 3: start with the jack by placing
it under the frame
closed to the tire that need to be
changed. It is important to ensure is
contacting the frame
directly to avoid damage to the side
scured. The majority of modern vehicles
have a designated area
near each wheel. The designated area is usually
a pinch weld. In this case it is an indet. If you drive
a truck or older vehicle
there may not be a pinch weld available.
If this is the case jack the vehicle up
from the frame. Step 4:
Proceed to raise the jack onto the pinch
weld or frame until the car is firmly
supported without
actually being raised into the air. At this
time
make sure that the jack is firmly
planted onto the ground so that it will
not shift. Step 5:
locate the lug nuts on your vehicle. If
your vehicle has hub cap or a center cap
you may have to pry them off depending
on the design. From here
lug nut should be loosened but not
completely removed. As you can see
the lug nut on the far right is a
locking lug nut. This is why you will need
the locking key
enabling to remove it. From here lug nut
should be loosened but not completely
removed.
Breaking their resistance of the
lug nuts may take quite a bit of force
depending on how tight they are.
Step 6:
Fully raise the car of the ground by
pumping or in this case
cranking the jack. The amount of clearance
that you want between your tire and the
ground
should be enough so that you can freely remove
the tire.
Step 7:
Remove the lug nuts completely of the hub
of the vehicle.
This may take some time, be patient.
A quick tip is to ensure that you
remember where you put
the lug nuts. There's nothing worse than
losing the lugnuts
when you try to put the tire back on.
Step 8: Remove the tire there may be
some resistance when trying to take off
the tire.
This is often the case when it is winter
and water freezes between the wheel and
the hub.
Don't be afraid to give it a good ludge
or kick.
step 9: Take the spare tire and place it
on to the hub
matching the holes on the wheel to the
wheels nut.
Step 10 : place the lugs onto the stud of
your tire.
Proceed to hand tighten the lug nuts
until they are snugged. Again
this may take some time, be patient.
Step 11 : tighten the lug nut securely.
For this five lug assembly the procedure
in tightening the lug nuts
will be a star pattern to ensure that
the wheel is flushed with the hub
assembly.
If you don't do the star pattern
you could run the risk of your wheel
falling off.
Step 12 : lower the jack to bring the car
onto the ground.
And fully tighting the lug nuts. Tight them  as
much as you can
but not over tighten them preventing you
from removing the lug nuts in the future.
If you purchase a new wheel assembly it
is best to have it installed
professionally
so that you can tighten the wheel to
specifications.
step 13 :
put all the materials and tools back in
there location.