The first thing that we are going to do is
actually loosen the nuts on the wheel.
So we are going to loosen them diagonally
across and just enough so that we can
have what we call then
hand loose. Once we've got the
nuts loose, we then going to actually
jack up the car. We've already looked in
the log book to find the correct
jack point under the car. Place
the jack underneath
so that the jack almost close not quite
open enough
and we slip them under the point.
What we're going to do is slowly jack up
the car until the jack is actually
touching
the point in the vehicle where it's touching
and we slowly will start to jack up
the car. You'll notice the whole car will
start to lift.
If we put the jack in the wrong spot you
might notice that the car is not lifting
properly
and also you'll notice that it might start
making some cracking noises.
Once we've jack the car up enough and
everyone always says how do I know it's
enough.
Jack it up until you've got a bad of
inch or two
from the tire above the actual ground
or
until the jack won't go up any further.
Now what we're going to do
is loosen the nuts even more taking
them all off and we always say put them
into your pocket so you don't lose the
nuts. If you lose one or two you can
always take
one of each other wheel to pull back
onto the spare.
So we put the nut into our pocket. Now
what we gonna do is
actually carefully take the wheel off.
Sustaining not to lie
staying fairly close to the car and we
going to lift the wheel off.
Rolling the wheel onto the ground
and we're going to grab the spare tire.
so what we're going to do now is stand very
close to the
car. I actually put my body
against the car
and we have to make sure that the actual
holes
in the wheel lineup with the nuts on
the car. So what we are going to do is
do that before we actually have to lift
the tire. So I have aligned all the holes up.
We're going to lift it onto the wheel
and
sometimes it takes a little bit of a
jiggle just to get them on.
I hold it with my leg while I slowly
put the
nut back on diagonally across from each
other.
So that way you don't have just the top
ones on in the bottom of the wheel is
spoking out all the other way around.
So I put the nut back on I
tighten them by hand.
I can then lower the car, remove the jack
out carefully
and then I'm going to grab the wrench and
tighten
the nut top again until there's tight as
I can get them. Have a check around to
make sure there is nothing that I've left
behind
and then pack everything back into
the bot.