First things first, to get your tools out of your trunk.
Put the jack and it should be twisting
to your right to extend it.
Should be able to easily twist it by hand
until you get to the
actual car when you want to put it on
this little lift point which is a little
rectangular point where you lift it up.
Then you take your hook, you put into your actual Jack.
Put your jack
on the end here. Now make sure the tires
always clear the ground and your e-brake is
set.
So that you can loosen the lug nuts
fairly
easily.
Pull your tire off, open your trunk lid
spin your actual
spare tire holder off.
Pull your tire out.
It helps to put your foot underneath it
to help lift it up. Line up your studs.
Put all your lug nuts back on.
Make sure they're tight.
Preferably in a star pattern. Now take your Jack off,
just do the reverse order to what we did
prior,
spin it to the left.