The spare wheel and the toolkit is generally underneath the
boot floor like this is the spare wheel
and in this car the tools are inside
this little compartment here.
Just take that out, here we've got the jack
and
the wheel brace and a little tool to help us take
the
wheel trims off. The wheel is normally
held down by
a clamp of some sort. You have to take this
off to take the wheel out.
The wheel is quite heavy so just careful
as you take it out.
Before you go through all the trouble of
taking off the wheel and putting on the new
one just make sure
that there's plenty of air in in the one you putting on.
If you don't have a gauge
you can usually check by bouncing the wheel.
Give it a bit of a
push and see does it feel fairly
solid. If you have a gauge
you can just check the pressure quickly.
On this car which has steel wheels we
have to take the plastic wheel trims off
here
to get access to the wheel nuts. On
cars with aluminium wheels
you would probably use a tool like this
which takes the
pulls the center cap off the wheel so we can get
to the wheel nuts. So let's take the
wheel trim off. Just prize it off
gently as you can with
a screwdriver there and it just pops off. Now you can
see the wheel
and the wheel nuts. this is the factory
supplied wheel brace.
As you can see it's not very long and it
doesn't allow you to get a great deal
of leverage on to the wheel nuts. We'll give it a
try and see how we get on.
Using all
of my weight there that isn't budging an
inch. So
there are two options. You can either use
an aftermarket item like this
which is extendable and I always use
something like this to be honest coz these really are not great. The
other option is
and this isn't great for my health and
safety point of view I'm sure is to
stand on it
and literally bounce.
You might have noticed we started
undoing the wheel nuts before we've
jacked the car up. The reason for this is
that it's much easier to just
undo the nuts one half a turn
before the car is up in the air and it's
safer as well because you're putting
less
pressure on to the jack and you're
moving the car around less
when it's still on the ground. I'm
actually going to change from the
factory wrench to the extendable one
just to make my life easier
to undo the rest of the wheel nuts. What I
forgot to mention
earlier on is that it's left to loosen
right to tighten. We're just doing
each wheel nut one half a turn and then
we can jack the car up. Don't loosen
these
more than half a turn because we
don't want the wheel to be
loose on the car before we jack it up. Now
we're going to jack the car up.
It's really important you need to find
the jacking points on the car.
These will be in your hadn book. But usually there is one they are on
both sides of the car. One just behind the
front wheel and one just in front
of the rear wheel. It's really important
that you jack the car at the jacking points otherwise
the jack might go straight through the floor
which is not what you want.
Another thing we're using the
the factory supplied Jack here. I don't
like them at all, I don't think
they are great and I'd much rather use something
like this.
oaks and two ton trolley Jack. They have a much wider
footprint, it is much more stable.
I'll show you what I mean when this car is
jacked up.
We've just got the front wheel off the ground
there
but we need to go a little bit higher
because this tire is flat
and the new one isn't flat so we need to
allow for that
bit of space there. Show you what I mean. There's quite a bit a
movement
there with the standard Jack. This is
a much more stable job
and something I much rather use
one of these than one of these guys. Something I should
have just mentioned before I jacked the car
up.
You must have the car in gear and handbrake on.
It's really very important to do that.
Very unsafe if you don't. Now ready to take the
wheel nuts off.
We've loosened them half a turn already
so they should come off pretty easily
and
take out the studs like that. We don't
want to be
swinging off the wheel wrench while the
car is
up in the air on the jack because as you
saw there it's a
little bit unstable with the the factory
supplied
Jack. I always try to take off the
lower wheel nuts first and
just try to leave one on a at the top the last one.
Just seems to make it easier so
that wheel so you can just have it out
like that. So
just hold it in place. That's the last one
and the wheel can come off. We've got the wheel
off,
we've got the spare here this tire's not
the best but it'll get us out of trouble and
get us home
until we can get to the garage to change it.
Now
I'll show you two tricks to getting this
wheel back on
safely and as easily as possible. Look
where your
stud holes are and look at the position
of them.
You need to get the wheel holes
in that same position. The second
thing
is this is very very heavy probably
weighs at least 20 kilos
so lifting this into position is
half the key to getting it on
quickly and easily so roll the wheel in
into place and just shimmy around
until you have the stud holes roughly in
the same position
as the stud holes on the brake
disc on the hub.
Get into a crouching position like
this and then
put your elbows on to your thighs and you
literally
just use your thighs to support
the weight of the wheel it's not the most
flattering or glamorous of positions
but it saves your back and it makes the job
much easier.
Now you can just rotate the wheel a
fraction
until the stud holes and the wheel
lineup.
And literally just wiggle the studs in
one by one.
Just do them half a turn get them all in
and that's it. Now do two
studs opposite of each other finger
tight.
There you go, do them as tight as you can by hand
and then tighten the rest of them up.
Doing them finger tight on first just ensures
that you have the wheel
on flat and true you don't want to have to
tightened one stud or nut up before all
the others and
you know the wheel could be wonky.
And we just tighten them
half a tuirn with our wrench.
Just nip them up like that and then
we can lower the car back down on the
jack
and we will tighten them up properly once the
car and wheel is back on the ground.
Now we can lower the jack again it's
left to loosen
right to tighten or have to lower in
this case and
right to raise.
Now we can tighten up the wheel nuts. To tighten
the wheel nuts I'm gonna use the
extended bar again don't need to be
swinging off this, jumping up and down on
it so
just around in a circle,
just nip them up.
And that is it. All we need to do now is
put the plastic hub cap back on.