Tires come in different sizes. Your spare maybe a
little donut size
or it could be a full size tire like
this. One of the things to remember
is if you have a flat tire on the front
you're gonna want to take
the rear tire and put it up front if
you are front wheel drive
or vice versa if it's the other way
around where you have a rear wheel drive
vehicle.
So let's get started. Most of your
vehicles today
actually have the tools to actually
raise your vehicle
located underneath the hood or under the
seat or maybe in the trunk. Our vehicle
jack and jack tools are located
behind the rear seat here. You know it's
a good idea
to check your owner's manual and locate
your tools before you
are in a situation where you need to
find them quick. Let's just go ahead and
lift up our seat.
our Jack is right here and looks like our
jacking tools are right here.
So let's just go ahead and take a look
at what we have here.
These are chocks we're gonna place those
in the front tires.
Here's our jack. This is actually our lug nut
wrench. We're gonna take those off with that
and these are going to be to get
to our jack and to our spare so let's just go
ahead and get prepared for this.
what we want to do is we wanna raise our tire
our axle up just a little bit and now
what we're gonna do is we're gonna go back
and loosen our lug nuts.
so let's just go ahead this first nut is
a cap on this vehicle.
so we're just gonna loosen those up.
removing the cap will
expose our lug nuts. we wanna just loosen
them up a little bit.
what we want to do is we want to push down.
don't try to pull up. use your weight.
let's just go ahead
access our spare
tire.
we're gonna lower it.
so we're just gonna remove our lug nuts
now. rock your tire.
Pull it off.
Our spare.
now we can lower our vehicle
and continue tightening our nuts. now that
we have our tire back on the ground
we wanna make sure that our lug nuts
are tight. we're gonna tighten them in a
staggered motion.