the essential tools you will need
to change a spare tire on your car and
the tools you
always and I mean always have to have in
your car are
a emergency signal or a triangle
you have to have a tire ranch you have to
have a car jack
and of course you have to have a spare
tire.
the first thing you do when you get a
flat tire
is get yourself off the road. the
most important thing
in experiencing
a car problem is car safety. so
safety is first.
the first thing you have to do is to get
your car off the road.
so if you're on a highway a freeway
or a remote country road like we
are here
always get your car off the road in a
safe place so other
people in traffic can go by you or stop
and help you. you do that by
stopping your car turning off the engine
pulling the handbrake
turning on the
emergency lights like that
and using the emergency signals or
the triangle as I have told you.
you put the triangle in a distance
from the car that is safe so that
the other people that are coming
your way in your lane will be able to
stop
in a safe distance and not cause a car
accident because you
have a flat tire. so remember make
yourself
visible and safety is first.
so we have stopped the car
turned on the emergency lights put the
emergency signals at a safe
distance.
now we are safe on the road.
so now we're gonna change the tire. this of
course as you see is not a flat
tire but since this is the simulation
you will get
a pretty good idea what you have to do
to change a tire.
the first thing we do is take off the
rim cap.
it usually goes by hand
if it doesn't use a screwdriver. we put
the rim cap
aside and here are the tire screws.
the second thing we do is take the
car wrench.
so take the car wrench put it on
the tire screw and
apply pressure. in this case
we have a tire wrench which has many
levers.
in case you have one lever which goes
like this you can use one hand
in this case we're using two hands.
in case you have
a tire screw which you can't turn loose
with the strength of your hands do
not
despair. many men
and women have problem with this because
the tire screws
in this part here have corrosion which
does not let them
to be loosened by the strength
of your hands.
so you put be tire wrench here on
the screw.
if you can't do it with the
strength
of your hands use the strength
of your body.
the the weight of your body. put a
hand here
put a leg here and simply jump on it.
so this can actually really help you
when it the tire screws
do not want to budge.
okay now we've loosened the tire screws.
now we take the carjack. always
remember
to pull your handbrake.
you do not want your car to go
right or left when it is on the carjack.
put the car jack in the place on the
floor
where the car jack is supposed to go.
every car has
an appropriate place where the car jack
should be put. and we turn.
always try to put the jack
in a straight position and be sure that the
foot of the car jack is on a firm
surface. so
in this condition this is a country road
which has gravel
and it does not matter because it is a
firm surface. so don't put it in mud
or oil or in anything that will
cause the car to slide off the jack.
we lever it up.
as you can see
the tire is up.
so the car is up.
the tire is free. it is in the air. you
take
the tire wrench and take the screws off.
you can take them off by hand you can
take him off with the tire wrench
whatever you like. hold it a bit.
don't be shy to get yourself
a bit dirty. take off the tire. take off
the spare
and put it on.
these holes should match
the holes on the car wheel.
put the screws on as far as they go
by hand.
we take the tire wrench and
we tighten the tire so much as it goes
with small pressure.
most people make a big mistake by
tightening
the
tire on the car while the jack
is up. what you get by doing
something like that the car goes right
or left or far
falls out the jack cause you
many problems
you know and perhaps can badly injure
you.
so tighten it just so the tire stays. the
tire
is on the vehicle. now
of course we lever it down.
make
enough space for the car jack to go out.
and we proceed to
tighten the spare tire.
so we go like this and like this
this and this.
we apply some pressure. always remember
when tightening the screws go
diagonally. do not go circling
around.
go like an X.
you apply as much
pressure as you can
with your hands so tighten them up.
always tighten them up good because you
don't want
to risk your wheel from falling off
the car. you can put
the rim cap back on or you don't have
to.