Right, on this particular car the first job
we have to do is to remove these plastic caps
that go over the actual nuts. Yes, they do
look like the actual nuts themselves but they're
not. Right, they're off! Don't jack your
car up without loosening the nuts because
when you try and undo them, the wheel will
just turn round and round. It sounds obvious.
I've done it.
This was in the tool kit. It's the adapter
key for the one locking wheel nut which we
need to release first so let's make sure that's
in position. Now I could have used the standard
wheel brace, this lightweight one that came
with the car, this is a standard issue. You
need to have had a decent
breakfast if you're going to use one of these!
I'm a reasonably robust lad but what I'm going
to do is rely instead on what I think is safer
which is one of these after market wheel
braces. You can get two hands on it and we
can exert some real leverage. So let's get
this one off first.
There we are! Right, so I'm going
to loosen these off but
I'm not going to take them off completely
because I do not want this wheel to come off
when I don't want it to. There would normally
be almost always there are instructions in
various languages on here as to how to use
this jack and where it goes, most importantly
where it goes. If you try and raise the whole
weight of this vehicle by putting this in
the wrong place, it can puncture the body
work and you really don't want to do that
and worse still, it can be a danger to you,
the person who is changing the wheel.
So I've had a look and it tells me that there
is on the sill here, there's a depression
where that goes so there it is. So I've got
that in nice and tight, just finger tight
there. Right!
One thing as well, if you do
have other people with you for godness sake
make them get out of the car or if they are
in the car, if they are children and they
are in the car make sure they stay in the
car. The last thing you want when you're jacking
up a car is people opening and closing doors
unnecessarily and getting in and out of the
vehicle.
Right, let's get this wheel off. Just put
these to one side there is nothing worse
than getting half way through this job and
finding out that you have lost one of the
wheel bolts!
Right, let's stick the space saver on. There
was quite a bit of resistance to space saver
tyres when they first came out a few years
ago but as well as having the advantage of
liberating space inside the car and reducing
weight which reduces your fuel consumption
and improves your performance, they are also
much easier to handle. Wheels and tyres have
got bigger and bigger and bigger and heavier
and so the space saver has all kinds of advantage
but for goodness sake, look at it. It's perfectly
safe but don't leave it on your car for a
few weeks. I don't want to see you in the
car park at the supermarket loading up the
car with one of these things on. Once you
have got one of these on, the only place you
need to be going is the tyre specialist or
your dealershop.
Just tighten these up now. I don't think
I'll put the plastic caps back on because
I'm only going to be leaving it on for as
long as it takes me to get to a dealer now
aren't I? So you've seen me put them on finger
tight at first and that's a good way of starting
them off so that you're going into the existing
thread; you're not as they say cross threading
the hub. You don't want to force these bolts
in to start with. However, once you've got
them all finger tight it is good practice
to get hold of the tyre at the top here if
it's this space
saver like this and just give them a twist
in turn with the wheel brace so that the wheel
isn't moving around at all. The wheel is nice
and secure, I can let the jack down and then
I'll properly tighten those five bolts and
make sure the wheel is on right.
Right, let's take the jack out. Now that the
wheel is firmly on the ground, tighten these
nuts; as much pressure as you can apply on
one of these four way wheel braces, that's
probably about as tight as it needs to be.
When you're tightening these up by the way,
try and tighten opposite to opposite instead
of going round the clock to make sure that
it's squarely on the hub.
Right, they're all tightened; the wheel is
secure; it's pumped up and ready for the road
again.