We'll now loosen it with the wheel down and
give it a couple good rams.
Make sure its full of air, worst thing you
want to do is put on a flat spare.
Then you pull out this tire, careful this can be
quite heavy.
We have our spare tire and our jack we have set our
reflective warning signal out.
We've also chocked the wheel on the
opposite side of the flat tire.
So we are ready to start changing it. The first
thing we will do, is jack the vehicle up.
You have to loosen the jack a little bit
in order to get the handle off.
This particular model has the lug wrench
built right in. Before we jack though
we would want to loosen the lug nuts
because once is jacked up it's going to
be very difficult to get those lug nuts
off.
This particular model has a hubcap which
we will just loosen those up.
Doesn't take much because they are made out of
plastic.
Set the hubcap out of the way.
Now you have access to the lugnuts. Loosen
the lug nuts.
Position yourself firmly, pressing
counterclockwise loosen the lug nuts.
Not too loose, just enough the crack them.
If they are a little stubborn, position
yourself over
using your knee or your foot you can
gain leverage.
Now we are ready to jack it up. This is a common
scissors jack
the screws move in and out allowing the mechanism to move up and down and lift
your car.
So as you turn it to the right it'll go
up, as you loosen it
the jack will collapse allowing the car to
come down. Now we'll position the Jack,
you want to be sure to get the Jack under a
good part of the frame.
Your owners manual is a good place to find
where to properly jack the vehicle.
You can raise it up by hand
till it contacts the frame and is in a good position.
We use the jack handle to raise the
vehicle.
Insert the end of the jack handle into
the jack,
using it as leverage it'll help make the
car go up easier.
Remember turn it clockwise to go up and
counterclockwise to go down.
Carefully jack the car up. Never stick
your hands or legs
under the vehicle as the car can fall and cause damage.
Jacking can take a while so be patient
cautious as you jack.
Okay now that the car's jacked up now
take the lug nuts loose.
Remember we already pre loosened them when the
car was on the ground making it easy.
Notice they will come right off now. Trying to do
that while the car was jacked up would
be very difficult.
Remember to keep your lug nuts in close
hand you don't want them rolling away in
the grass because it will be hard to find and that's what holds your tire on.
Again we're turning them
counterclockwise to get them loose
or to the left. We'll remove the
flat tire set it over here out of the way.
Now if there's heavy traffic in the area you wouldn't
want to leave it in the street you might
want to put it to the rear of the car.
Grab the spare tire put it in position.
You are gonna Center the spare tire on the
wheel studs,
that's where the lug nuts go. So go ahead and do that.
Lining it up. You will see it lines up pretty
easy.
Then install your lug nuts. Again,
clockwise is tight, counterclockwise is
loose.
So we'll tighten them up by hand
as far as they'll go.
Once the tire is centered,
lug nuts are hand tight, take the lug
wrench,
again turning it clockwise
tighten the lug nuts till they are firm.
Not too tight because remember your car is up
on a jack. We wouldn't want it falling off with
too much leverage or force.
Insert the jack handle back into the jack
turning it counterclockwise again we're
gonna lower the vehicle.
Again this'll take some time but going
down is a lot easier than going up.
If it seems to go down easy you can just
do it like this by doing it straight
instead having an angle.
But if it's too tough you can angle it
and get the leverage that you need to
lower the jack
or to raise the jack. Turn the Jack low
enough
you can do it by hand now that it doesn't
have contact with the frame.
And we can remove it. Now that the tires are
on the ground we'll go ahead and give them that
final tight.
We're gonna start down here then move
to the top one then back down
over and baki again, a little star pattern,
making sure we have equal torque
on the wheel studs.
Okay well we have our spare tire on, it's aired up,
we're ready to go. Couple of things to
remember though is you want to put everything back in
the trunk.