Once you've got your car in a safe place
off the road make sure the handbrake is firmly
applied
and the car is on a flat surface so it doesn't
roll away.
Have a look in the boot of the car, you
should find a spare tire and the tools
you need to use.
A few cars like this one have a cradle under
the back of the car.
The instructions following the cradle to
release the tire
can be found in your owner's manual.
The tools you need
are jack to raise the car off the ground and
a wrench that you need to remove the wheel
nuts
that are tightly screwed onto the tire.
Most cars
have alloy wheels but some models have
plastic wheel trims
which you'll need to pop off to see the exposed
wheel nuts.
Before you jack the car up, use the wrench
to loosen the wheel nuts
just slightly. They're going to be
really stiff so use your foot if you need to.
A lot of cars have one nut that's different
from the rest which requires a special key
to remove.
This  "taught" people being able to
take the alloy wheel
off the car without the locking wheel nut
key that came with your car.
The key fullfills into the wheel wrench. To jack the
car up you need to find the jacking point
which can be found underneath the car
near the tyre that need replacing.
Position the jack underneath the jacking point
and then raise the car until the tyre is
about 10 centimetres clear of the
ground. If you don't raise it high enough
then you may struggle to get the new
spare tyre on. And it's not safe to raise it
while the wheel is off.
Once the car is safely raised take the wheel nuts
off completelely,
remove the tyre and replace it with the spare.
Line the new tire up with the corresponding
screw holes on the car.
Once lined up screw the wheel nuts back
into place.
You need your wrench again here to tighten the
wheel nuts started enough of each others
to make sure that they're not unbalanced. Don't
try to charge them fully
jsut yet though.
Lower the car back to the ground surface
with you jack tool until the tyre touches
the ground.
Once it is safely on the ground tighten the wheel
nuts firmly.
If your car wear trims pop the trims back on making sure
that secure all the way around.
You are now ready to finish lower the car
to
the ground completely.
Remove the jack, put your tools away and
get back onto the road.