For automatic you want them in park. Next
take off the hub cap if your
car has one. Then use your wrench
to partially loosen the lug nuts.
If you are not sure how to remove the
hub cap, just check your owner's manual.
Also check to see if your car has
plastic covers over the lug nuts like
this one.
If so, then take them off first.
Your log nut wrench probably won't fit
over them.
And make sure you put them somewhere
safe so you don't lose any of them.
Now to take the lug nuts off, go in a
a star pattern loosening one of the lug nut
a half turn and then loosening the one
opposite ot it. Walk your way accross the
tire
until all the lug nuts are unscrewed
a half turn.
Before you jack up the car,
put a heavy object like a brick in front of the
wheel diagonally opposite to the flat tire
to prevent the car from slipping. Here is
where the jack comes in.
Put it under the car's frame  near the wheel
with the flat. There is a thin lip that run
along
the side of the car,
that's usually where the jack is. It can
be different though so just check
your owner's manual for the safest place
to put your jack under the car.
Remember it is possible for the car
to slip of its jack,
so never get underneath the car that
is only support by a jack.
Okay so now you've got the
jack in place. Now enter the
handle
and turn it clockwise to
lift the jack up. If it lowers
the car a wrong
turn, try turning the handle the other
way. Make sure you raise the jack high
enough to replace your flat tire.
The new tire will be fully there so
you will need more room anything.
Remember those lug nuts you
loosen earlier. Now you can
take them off
completely.
Once the lug nuts are off, you can pull
off the flat tire.
To make sure you put the new tire on the right
way, look at the air valve,
it should be facing out. To replace the
lug nut, go into the same order
you loosen them.
Tight one nut a few turns and then do
one opposite until each lug nut
is partially tighten.
Then go back accross your star pattern
to tighten them completely.
To lower the jack
turn the handle slowly counterclockwise
until the tire just makes contact with the
ground.
And watch out for you feet as
you lower the jack.
A flat foot is even worst than
a flat tire.
Make sure each lug nut is completely
tighten before you remove the jack.
Don't forget to put your jack and
the object with the flat tire back
in your before you drive off.