In most cars, you'll find everything you need to
put on a spare tire, in your trunk. Just lift up this back panel
you'll see we've got spare tire
this is a donut. Other cars  have
full-size spare that's really nice but
this'll do for the time being until you
can
get a brand new tire. Also got a jack
This device is used for actually cranking
the jack
the and a tire iron and so we'll get these out
and then get started on removing the tire
which currently isn't flat but just for
the sake of
showing you how to do it we're gonna remove it and
we're gonna install the spare.
We've got all our tools out here. We've got the tire iron.
What I wanna do is before using
the jack at all, I wanna loosen up these lug nuts
because once the wheel is off the
ground you're not gonna get
the same amount of leverage.
Just loose enough.
So now that they are all
loose
I'm gonna grab this jack and see this
right here with the hole? You crank that by
hand so
get to the point where there's little
groove down here
for the jackpoint. So I've put a glove on
because
you can get pretty dirty and some of these parts
cna be sharp and you can cut your fingers possibly.
See these two grooves right there?
That's indicating where you can put this
jack.
And you wanna put this metal piece in between
this part right here.
okay so just
tighten it up by hand or turn it by hand.
Make sure it's nice and straight and once it's
touching the bottom
of the car here at the jackpoint it
starts to get tight,
then you wanna get that tool so just
hook it in there.
And so,
it's a little bit off but then you kind of just do one of these things.
And then you go until that tire lifts off the
ground it doesn't need to be
more than a couple inches off the ground.
You just want enough space
enough clearance to get the tire off. So
tire's lifting up.
You can use the jack anywhere unless
you're on a very very steep incline
because then it's going to be very very
difficult to keep it steady but
these are built to be used anywhere. Okay
so as you can see
got the tire off the ground got enough clear
that I cna put my whole hand under it.
So now I'm gonna loosen up these lug nuts by
hand.
Make sure they don't roll away.
Sometimes you have to angle the wheel a
certain way to loosen up the lug nut.
Alright let's just take the wheel off, very simple
set it aside.
And now we can go get
the spare tire out of the back and I'll show you how to do that.
Alright so we got the
donut back on the here. For security you wanna
make sure that they're
not floating around loose in the back of your
car.
One thing that's important to check
is that the tire pressure, recommended tire
pressure on the spare.
Right here it says sixty pounds maximum
pressure.
You cna go a little bit less than that but the idea
for using
a donut is not to use it permanently.
It is just a quick fix until you're able to
get a brand new tire.
Another thing to note that you're not supposed to
go over 65 miles per hour
on a donut. Alright so, pretty
straightforward
just just lift it up by two hands, if you need to get
leverage
put your knee down or whatever just do
that. Make sure it's all the way on.
Use the same exact lug nuts
that you took off off your full size tire then tighten them by
hand.
There's no rule
about how to put lug nuts on but in most
cases
if you have four or five, general idea is just kinda skip
every other one.
I think it just promotes an even tightening
all around.
So that's nice and snug.
Just notice how much smaller that is
than the
full size tire.	What I'm gonna do
is give it a quick little tightening
with my hand not like
too crazy yet. Okay
and now we go back to our jack here hook
that in but reverse the motion
until we get that tire touching the
ground again.
And now we give that one last tightening and make
sure it's secure and then you can hit the
road
with a tire that actually has air in it.
Things are really handy
when you have this tool you can get
this motion going.
Alright so see this is loose now which
means
the tire is supporting the car.
Bring that out. Get my tire iron.
So great we have our spare tire
installed and
I made a point of using the things that
come with the car that go underneath the
panel in your trunk.
Because you're not gonna have access to
all the tools you have in a toolbox at
home. The last step is to take your full
size tire which should be flat otherwise
there's really no need to change it and all
tools came with car
put them all back where you took everything out,
close that off and you're ready to roll.