Fixing a flat tire
is easy. If you're on the road
pull your car over to a safe flat
spot.
Next, put your vehicle into park or 1st
gear
and apply the emergency brake. Now locate
your spare tire.
On most of today's SUV's and trucks
the spare is
under the vehicle. Retrieve it following
the steps in your owner's manual.
It's a good idea to check the spare's
pressure before you go any further.
If your spare's pressure is good continue
on with changing your flat
by popping off the cover to access the
lug nuts with a flat into the tire iron
or supplied tool. Start to loosen the
lug nuts just enough to make them
easy to turn by hand. If they're too
tight try using your foot for added
leverage.
Now place the jack under your car in a
line it so that it lifts the car by the
frame.
To raise the jack connect the handle piece
and insert it into the jack
turning clockwise until it lifts the
vehicle. Once you've raised the vehicle so that the
flat tire is off the ground, remove
the log nuts and put them in a safe place
such as the wheel cover so you don't
lose one.
Now remove the flat tire and lay it on
the ground away from the car.
Line up the spare and ligt it to place.
Put the log nuts back on and tied  them
by hand.
Then tighten down each nut with the
tire iron. Start with one lug nut then
tighten the lug nut farthest away.
And so on until they are all tight. To
finish up, slowly lower the vehicle
remove the jack and make sure the lug
nuts are tight one last time. That's it!