This one is probable gonna come out pretty easily because I just got
it from the grower like a month ago.
so you ease it out of the pot.
you might have to cut the
pot off if it's really potbound.
so don't be afraid of that.
you sort of loosen it up. you can see the
roots right here.
It's sure loosened up.
Looks like some of it fell off. so i am gonna put some more
of this soil in here to raise it up.
because I want it up about half an inch
above the pot because it is gonna sink down.
so. a little bit more here.
there we go. that's gonna get it. you
can just hold it together if it starts to
fall apart you can
hold that together up here. I love
worm castings and compost.
it's what I meant by plantings
wiz. so I'm gonna go in and put a few
handfuls of that
around here before I go ahead and fill
it in.
then I'm gonna in
and fill around so the
plant will be supported in the pot. I'm just
gonna go around. I'm gonna fill in
with
soil all of the way around said so
it's nice and even up here.