what we're doing first is putting some
rocks in the bottom so that's gonna let the
water at the bottom drain out more
easily and
again it won't drown the roots of the
plant.
we put this synthetic fabric over those
rocks
and then a little bit of this organic
potting soil that you see on the left.
we're gonna put that in next and create a
nice
level foundation. so here we are just
pouring this in. I'm gonna smooth this out a
little bit with my hands
and make it level. so the next
important step
is taking the plant out of it's old pot.
don't water it because otherwise it'll be wet.
let it dry out a little bit. you can
see that the roots there
they're all bunched up they are root bound
and this plant definitely needs to be
repotted.
so turn the pot sideways. grab it by the
top firmly as you see there
and just pull the plant out of the pot. it should just slide out.
so here it is and you can see how much
smaller
the volume of the old pot was versus
the new one. now what I'm doing is I'm
using my fingers to break up the roots and
separate them out so that
they won't all be tied up in knots. it's gonna
help the plan adapt
and get nutrients and water in its
new
pot home. there we go. I am just
stringing them out getting a little bit dirty.
then i am setting it right in the middle
and not too high. I am leaving about an inch
between the top of the
soil here and the rin of this new pot.
my friend here is just going around
the edge puttin potting soil along the sides.