select a pot that is slightly larger. one or two sizes
larger
than the existing pot and put a layer of
horticultural grit in the bottom.
this helps with the drainage. then
take a piece of paper and place that
over-the-top
of the gravel. cut a circle out and put it
over the top of the gravel.
this stops the soil from falling through
from being washed through the pot when you
water the plant. place some compost
into the bottom of the pot.
just firm it down slightly. take the
plant
and tap it out of it's pot. this one's
really grown into the pot. It's very loose. you can see
all the roots
filling the entire base of the pot. I'm just gonna remove
the top bits of the compost. you can
hear them actually breaking up
some of the roots. be quite gentle but
nonetheless take the top
centimeter
of this plant out. It's actually very wet as well.
gently tease some of the roots out from
the side of the plant
with your fingers. don't worry too much about it but
be careful not to break the plant too much.
but don't worry too much about
damaging the plant. just loosen it up so that
the roots are encouraged to grow
towards the outside rather than just
branch around in circles.
just make sure that the plant is going to sit
correctly
in its new pot. I'm going to fill
in round the sides of the plants with some
new compost.
be quite gentle with this plant. It is quite
brittle.
I don't want to break it off.
I want to make sure that it's in the
center of the pot.
I'm firming the new soil down the
sides
of the plant. make sure there's no air pockets.
just cover the top of the soil
surface where you removed that top one
centimeter
of the soil before.
firm the soil a bit. I like to put a little
bit
more grit around the plants just
to dress the surface.
Makes it look a bit pretty.