The first step in repotting our pepper plant is of course to have a good container
and some good soil. normally you're gonna
wanna step it up into a
container that is at least one size larger
then what something came from.
with pepper plant you might start off
with something small like this and then
go directly into maybe a gallon
a five-gallon or maybe into something like
an earth box.
make sure you've got a good soil and a
good container.
now for repotting your little plant
we're going to take the plant. we're
going to
remove it from its beginning container.
we're gonna take the
the root system and gently pull the  root
system apart if it is rootbound and almost
every little container plant is.
the next stage after we pull all
roots apart
we're gonna put it into the container
and plant it about the same dept level it
was before
and maybe add a little bit of dirt
around it. then kinda packet it in with
our fingers.
just a little pressure.
the next step
is going to be watering. we are gonna put water
in here and make sure there's no air
pockets in the container.
and it gives our little botanical buddy
a nice drink.