this came out fairly easily but if it does
not and its
stuck in there, simply turning it
upside down
and tapping it either on the pot or on
the table will
release the pot and then you can go from
there.
the next step would be to carefully
break up that root system.
it's a good thing for the plant because it's
going to force it to send out new growth.
if we don't break up the roots they wont
branch out into the surrounding soil.
our next step is going to be to select a potting soil. there are a number that are
out there on the market.
it's a good idea to use a pre-packaged
soil mix that you buy from the store
rather than using garden soil
because garden soil is very heavy it stays
very wet
and can often at times contain pathogens
that can cause disease problems on your
plants.
you want it set at the same level
that it was originally.
also keeping in mind that you want about
a half an inch to an inch
of space between the top of the container
and the top of the the soil ball.
I'm gonna fill in with the rest my soil
and if the soil is very light very
fluffy
you wanna make sure that you pat it
down as it goes in that container.
you do not want to leave the top of the
soil ball exposed where there are roots
because what will happen is those roots
will kinda act like air wicks
and draw moisture out from the soils. the
final step would be to
water the plants thoroughly so that that soil mix gets saturated.