I usually have my trash bucket and my
good soil bucket. being very gentle, pull the pot out.
move the old pot out of the way.
and kind of crumble
the roots.
taking care not to damage the roots
but try to get as much soil out.
for the most part it's gonna rip all
so i think im just gonna leave it alone.
make sure to even it out there at the bottom a
little bit.
take your new pot and here's the
trick.
when you put him in make
sure that you get it all in the rungs
being very careful. having two people do
this is better than one.
make sure that it goes in. now it didn't go in
all the way.
okay so what we're going to have to do is to
have to take it back out.
being very careful. you can take
it out just a little bit.
since I already have some mix in there
I can take some of it out.
being very careful not to break the
branches.
like so.
I didn't say it was going to be easy.
so then we will try it again. put it in
there.
okay. perfect.
put your soil in there.
see this wire shelf idea is really good
because you can just sit there and shake
all the dirt in here. throw it in there.
and then pat it.
now don't worry about the branches falling
out right now.
you don't really need to be concerned
about that.
but your main concern is getting that soil dow in
the root area.
okay. That's good.