Loosen your compost so it's nice and airy. each container
should be three-quarters full and match
the size of your plant.
remove plant from the pot and loosen
the old soil
away from the roots. the aloe plant
has very shallow roots so don't be
alarmed at it's very small size.
tease away
any small daughter plants from the main
one. again don't worry
about the amount of roots on each small plant.
make a hole in your compost
and firm the plant in place. once the
plant is in place
top off with more compost and firm ion again.
the small plants
can be planted together in a large
shallow pot.
Aloe plants prefer space to spread
out sideways rather than going down in the pot.