when adding in the soil
just keep in mind that youare gonna be putting a
somewhat mature plant in there. so give enough
space to grow.
and enough space to grow upwards. so don't fill
this too high or too low.
we are going to be moving this one
to a separate pot today. as you can see it is quite mature.
it has somewhat of a
woody kind of feel on the outside. the roots on this one are
maybe 20 centimeters down. so what you do is you grab a
shovel and just cut into it.
once the roots come out, it'll be easier to pull out.
nope.
it's not coming out. Dig it again.
what you can do is twist it.
once your pot is ready all you do is dig out a hole for your
plant. just make sure it's not too deep
because you do actually want the roots to grow downwards to get
more structure
and support.
okay.
put it in there and just bury it.