okay so I've chosen this nice
clay pot.
It's got a nice glaze on it. It's really pretty. it's
got a nice big big drain hole in the bottom.
you wanna make sure that it has a nice big
drain hole so that the water has a
chance to run away.
so it's not sitting in moisture. I'm putting a
piece of paper towel on the bottom.
you might choose to use some stones or
a sponge or whatever you want
to keep some soil in.
Let's add some soil to this.
first let's check this out. take the
paper towel off. she was nice enough to
put it in some damp paper towel which is
nice because
it's been sitting out for about a week.
she did this last Saturday
and I'm on Saturday again.
you might see this at a different time
but it's been about a week
sitting out. it still looks good. Its
got some roots going on here this is
where it was probably attached to the main plant.
as you can see there's another one here.
some healthy root systems going on.
they'll get much better when
they reach the soil.
just gonna take off some of these damage
leaves.
fantastic.
so I just wanna see where they'll fit in
here.
I don't wanna plant them too deep. I
wanna plan to maybe to this point right
here.
if I plant them too Deep they will rot.
if I plan them too shallow they won't do well.
so maybe this one I'll plant to this
level here.
Alright hope you could see that. so I'm gonna add
a little bit more soil.
I am surprise I haven't had an aloe vera
plant in a very long time. It's one of those
things they
say I need to get but I never do
get.
it's one of those things. I always seem
to have all the crazy stuff but nothing
really common.
so anyway I
think we've got deep enough here now.
I'm gonna plant these
sort of separate but kinda in the center
of the pot.
kinda criss-crossing each other.
I have a bucket for my soil.
I wanna add enough soil in around here
to support them. I'm using a pre moistened
soil.
when dealing with cactus and succulents
it's not necessary to use a premoistened
soil.
sometimes it's better to not use a
premoistened soil because
you need a few days for them to callous over
before you water them in. but this
has been sitting out for a week so
premoistened soil isn't gonna do any
damage.
the root system has already calloused
itself over. things are
on their way to recovery. I'm sure it's
already thinking new growth new growth
new growth.
so we should be good. smoothing the stuff
around to where I want it.
packing the soil in firmly around
the base of the plants.
adding a little bit more soil here. trying
not to make them too deep.