Use an old tee shirt or towel to cover the top of the plant and then you're able to turn it upside down.
so I'll pull it out of it's pot. i
wanna break up the root ball just a
little bit
the roots can work their way into the new
soil.
then
go ahead and put it into a new pot. I'll put a
little bit of soil
at the bottom to start out. you want
to keep the
the base of the plant at the same
level it was in the original soil.
if you bury your plant too deep down in
it actually can cause
the plant to rot more easily. trying to
get it
into the position I want and then
add soil around.
then you can use the piece of
wooden rod to press the soil down
in.
add just a little bit more soil.
then I like to top dress
my soil with granite gravel. it really
is just an aesthetic choice.
just put it up around the top of the soil.
you can use the large tweezers
to press it in around the base of the plant.