place the coffee filter in the pot making
sure that you cover
any drainage holes that are in the pot.
then put a thin layer of soil
in the new home. now the amount of soil that
you put
in the pot will depend on the size of
the pot that you're using.
you never want to increase the size by more
than two times the original size of the
container that
gerbera daisy is in. once you have that
layer of soil in
you will need to remove your gerbera daisy
from its
old home. to do this you can simply
cut away the plastic pot.
if you don't want to do that gently tip
down your
gerbera daisy upside down and simply tap
on the bottom
and squeeze on the sides. the next step
is to tease the roots. teasing those
roots are giving them permission and
telling them they can grow out
well and your root ball to fill up its
new home in no time.
then put your gerbera daisy in the
container. fill in with soil
making sure that you don't overfill with
soil.
you want the soil level that the plant
was in originally
to be the exact same soil level in the
new pot. once you have done that gently
tap on it and then water.