I've taken a piece of a coffee filter and I just put it over
the bottom
drain hole in here and it just keeps all
this loose soil from coming
out the bottom at first until it gets
nice and
a lil bit more compact in there. till then it
is very very loose.
this is a succulent and
a cactus mix. it has a lot of perlite
it has some crushed rock in it.
sometimes it has horticultural sand
because the succulents wanna be
really really really dry so it's
important to use
a cactus and succulent mix when
doing this. so
what you're gonna do is you are going to
Press the sides of the pot if it's really rootbound.
I know that this one is not partuicularly
pot bound. if it's really pot bound you can
use the heel of your hand and you can
really press and go around and then you can
pull the plant out.
you have to be a little careful with that
because these paddles can
break off. there we go.
there.
there are the roots there. so I need to
add a little bit more
into here cuz I like to leave it up. a
little bit
above the
edge of the pot there.
it is gonna sink down and also
this is gonna pop. it's going to get a
lot of babies off of here.
now I'm gonna use my favorite thing
to condition the soil which is
worm castings and compost. I just work a
little bit of that in there because
succulents really don't need fertilizer
at all. they're so tough and so strong.
then I'm just gonna go back in and I'm
gonna fill around with
this nice loose soil. gonna work it
all around here. press it down
a little bit. fill it up a little bit
more because the soil is
so loose it is going to sink down
a bit.
so what I do is I will keep this plant
dry
for about 3 to 7 days just so it can settle
in.
and then I'll give it a really good
watering. it takes a while for
this really loose mix to get wet
and then it's gonna sink down a little
bit. then I will go through and I
will add
a little bit more of this on the top.