then next a pottery shard. notice this one is slightly angled.
this goes over the holes.
what it does is it keeps the soil
in
but it allows the water
to drain out.
first off
few handfuls of soil.
so the next thing we do is we remove
the plant from the container.
carefully turn it upside down.
grasp the trunk firmly and look at
that great
soil ball. look at all those roots.
keep your hand on the bottom
and gently lower her into the container.
centralize that.
in goes the soil. we've got a great
soil here.
it's
a little bit of native soil
it's some organic mulch
for this primarily pea moss
and coco fibre.
make sure when you plug the plant
that the original soil level
is not lower or deeper. everything needs to
remain the same.
slow release fertilizer.
I do this about every forty days.
little bit more mulch.
and hey presto it's as easy as that.
the last thing. I couldn't find my watering can.
the last thing we need to do is to give
her a good watering.