I take an old piece, you know I have pots that I broke when they drop on the floor. you could take a stone
and you just wanna put that in the
bottom. what that will do is it will stop
the soil from running out as you water
it but it is not going to stop
the water from running out. this pot is
about an inch higher than the old one so
if I were to put this
in the bottom what's going to happen is
it's going to be too deep.
you want the plant sitting at the same
level
that it was in your previous pot. so how
we gonna do that. well we're gonna put
some soil
in the bottom and we're gonna raise the
soil level up
so that when I place this plant in the
pot it will be just as high.
a general all-purpose soil is pretty good
for a plant like this prayer plant that
we're using. we're gonna estimate about how
high up
I want this and one of the things you want
to do if you really wanna pack that
down.
one step before I finally put this in
I wanna
tease the roots. we want to encourage some
growth. so now
we put this in. I've got a little bit of a
room there at the top of the
plant so that when I do water it's not
going to run out the sides or
over-the-top. you have your soil
and what you are gonna do is you are gonna pack
this in and it's very important
that you pack it in very tightly.
if you have like a little tool like this, a
small spade
you could use that to help get the soil
down in there. And the final step isyou want to water it.