wiht this plant
we've got a lot
of lateral roots. this is very
ruootbound.
we've excluded much of the soil that
contains the nutrients. so what we
need to do is prune away some of these
older roots that gives us space
to develop some more root hairs.
at the same time we'll replace some
of this old soil with some fresh
potting soil.
so to begin we're just gonna take off
about ten to twenty percent
of that actual root mass with some pruners.
so I'm just gonna go in here and take
off some of this
bottom most root mass.
now as I clip making sure that I don't
get
too close to the actual crown of the
planet. if we do any damage up here
we're likely to lose the plant. but
surprisingly
we can do quite a bit of pruning on these
roots. from the bottom part
the plant is very resistant to this kind
of
change. so I'm gonna remove
a large portion of those bottom roots.
I am also gonna make some cuts up the side of
the pot.
it promotes those roots to take hold
in the new
potting soil medium.
so now I'm gonna rip some of that apart.
begin to give more space for
new development or development of new
roots.
I'm gonna look for any diseases any
insects that may have gotten into my
pots over the
few months that we have taken it in and
out of the house.
okay and I'm gonna get rid of some
of this potting soil that's
from the past few years.
I'm gonna take a look inside my old pot
and make sure that there's no insects
in here. it is dirty.
you you can feel free to wash these
and reuse them.
I'm gonna reuse the same pot.
some would increase the size of the pot.
the problem with that is then it's a
larger plant I have to take in and out
of my house every day. okay so at this
point I'm ready to
to repot this plant. I'm gonna put some
fresh soil in the bottom of my pot.
I'm gonna press it down a little bit
so I have got all of the air pockets out.
I'm gonna place my plant back into
its original pot and fill in the sides.
now over the next several weeks
I'll make sure to keep this plant
well-watered.
I'll make use of a water-soluble
liquid fertilizer like Miracle grow over
the next week.
or once a week for the next few
weeks.