We'll see how rootbound they are. actually that's not
too bad.
sure if you can see it. this one is the duster.
it's got a good amount of
roots but it's not
horrible. so I already took out the
first
set of starter leaves off of it and we'll
plant this
probably a little bit further down.
so this'll actually grow roots. anything
that you put under
the dirt will grow more roots.
so I am going to add just a little bit of soil
here
to my potting mix into the bottom. I'm gonna
add
about one teaspoon
of bleach fertilizer. so i will do the organo bloom first.
Take a teaspoon of that. Put
it in the bottom. I will add a little bit
more
soyo. mix it up a little bit.
we're gonna break up these roots
just a little bit.
Alright.
Then we'll put that as far down as we can.
so while I hold the stem with one hand
I'm gonna pour the soil in with the other
just to keep it straight and centered.
you want to pack it down a little bit.
I've already pre moistened this
potting mix which is miracle grow
organic potting mix that was at Costco
from $9.99 for 55 court bag.
so it's a really good deal. I have already
gone through
probably three bags of it already. so that
is all it takes.