Step 1. Before transplanting a plant into a new pot, even out its shape
by trimming away any excess growth around
the top of the plant. Transfer your plants
outside, or lay down a tarp or sheet so that
you can easily clean up excess soil. Step
2. Sterilize the new container by using rubbing
alcohol to avoid the spread of any disease.
Once it's dry, fill about one-third of it
with potting soil. It isn't always necessary
to buy new containers. Old containers may
fit a different plant. Just be sure to sterilize
them first. Step 3. While holding the plant
at the base of the stem with one hand, use
your other hand to tip the old container upside
down. Make sure to support the soil surrounding
the plant as you tip it upside down. Tap the
bottom and sides of the container to release
the plant from it. Once the plant slides out
of the container, turn it upright. Tapping
a stick around the edges of the pot can help
to loosen the soil and give the plant some
breathing room. Step 4. With the plant still
in your hand, gently pull away the old soil
until only the roots and plant are left in
your hand. Step 5. Now place the plant in
the new container, filling and packing soil
around it until the soil is even and about
a half inch from the top of the pot. Step
6. Give the plant a good watering. You're