so we have chosen a really nice terra cota container. That's probably about twice the size of the ruble. we carefully remove the plant from the container.
look at that great root system.
keeping your hand on the bottom of the
plant
placing her really gently.
you can hear her squeal. alright. once she is
settled nicely in the container
important to remember that in the
bottom of all the containers there is a hole.
so put a few broken pottery shards
or a few stones over that and it'll stop
the soil running out onto your patio
deck. so with nice rich
organic soil fill up the sides
to the original soil level of the plant.
really important to remember.
as you fill the container up with the
soil don't forget to use some slow
release fertilizer in there
which you will do about every 30-40
days. this will keep the plant really well
fed and ensure you get lots of blooms and fresh new growth.