it's important to use new soil when repotting.
Although a new plant comes in a
container not only are these
fearly unattractive but the plant will
quickly outgrow it.
so you want to choose a different container.
of course you can buy containers in every
size
shape and color. think outside the box too. get
creative and recycle. if someone
is amazing at bowling
use a bowling ball bag. in all instances
you will have to drill or
cut a hole in the bottom of the container
to allow for proper drainage. some people
mix their own potting soil.
you can find recipes online or
simply pick up
potting soil at a garden centre. you want to provide
optimum drainage so the plant will thrive. people have used  all
types of materials for drainage
such as rocks broken pottery pieces and
even packing peanuts.
however now there's better than rocks.
its a 100 percent recycled plastic
mesh that is placed at the bottom
of the container. it improves drainage, prevents the
drain hole from getting clogged
and it helps oxygen reach the roots which is
necessary for the plant to absorb
nutrients.
therefore you will grow healthier plants.
better than rocks it is
also practically weightless making your
containers much lighter.
after providing adequate drainage add
potting soil.
add small amounts in the bottom. add a
little water.
then place the plant in the center and place more soil
around the sides
of the plant. press the soil down and add more
soil as needed until there is about an inch left
between the soil and the top of the
container. water thoroughly.