First thing I'm gonna do is take a shard and place it over the hole
in the bottom of the pot
making sure that you don't completely
block up the hole. water still needs to
be able to get out of it else you plant
will drown.
next you take a look at how big the pot
is that the plant is currently in and
how big the pot
is that you're gonna put it in. you want
to make sure that the plant is going to
be sitting
at about the same height in the
soil so you need probably to put some
soil on the bottom the hole
first. add some soil.
that looks like about enough soil. the
next step is to take the plant out of the
pot it's currently in.
this is a plastic pot so it's going to
be pretty easy to do.
if it were a terra cotta pot it's a
little harder. you have to really
use some elbow grease and sometimes if
it's been in there a long time
you even have to break the pot. with this
plastic pot though
it's simple. give it a couple of good thumps
to loosen the pot. Then
out the plant pops.
you wanna loosen the soil on the bottom.
check. turn the plant around. make sure
there aren't any roots
going all the way around the pot.
if there are you need to tease them out
or sometimes even just cut them. it won't
hurt the plant at all.
they'll just grow some new roots. now
it's time to pop it in its pot. pop it in
and that look like about the right
height.
when you're putting a plant in a pot you
don't wanna put it
right up to the top level of the pot. or
when you try to water it
the water will just run right out. I'm
gonna
back fill with our potting soil making
sure to push it down in loosely. you don't
want to pack it in cuz that'll
get all the air out of the soil but you
do want to make sure there aren't any
big
giant holes down in there. give the plant
a shake and a tap to settle it in there.
now the last step
is to give the plant a drink of water. you
want to make sure that you water it
thoroughly until water is coming out of
the holes in the bottom of the pot.
it's much better to water fewer times
thoroughly than to just water frequently and a little bit.