you don't realise that the moss is actually killing the plant because it retains so much moisture
that the plant can't breathe. so what
you want to do first
is go ahead and remove all of this moss.
you don't want all of this moss. you want to clean it all out.
you want to be kind of careful of the roots. The
roots are usually on the
outer side. the middle part is where the moss is.
there are some
roots that kinda hide inside
but usually it's always on the
outer part because orchid likes to breathe.
it like to have a lot of air.
but the Moss compacts it. because of shipping
purposes
the moss is used so that it can retain a lot of
the water and moisture
for the plant. but in time it actually
drowns
the orchid if it doesn't get enough air to
dry out that moisture that it has retained.
and that is why the orchids always die. so you wanna remove
all of this mossy material here.
after you remove all of this moss it's pretty
basically simple. look at these roots.
this is
still in a very good condition to rescue.
a lot of times the roots have been rotted all the way and it's
really
kinda too late to rescue them.
now that we have it all opened up most of
the moss has been cleaned out you want to go ahead
and put some of that bark
into that pot. Probably like halfway or so. And you want to go ahead
and gently place the
orchid and wrapping those roots around the place giving it a
sturdy kind of sitting inside the pot.
then go ahead and start adding more of that bark all inside
compacting the plant inside the pot. Basically this keeps the stability so the plant doesn't move around.
It likes to be stable, not wobbly.
yet at the same time give it that air to
aereate. the roots like a lot of circulating air and stability.
you can see that the bark is bigger
so that the air can
go insude and all of these wonderful
medium. tricko is actually
to rpevent fungus from growing and it's very nice to have as part of the medium.
Pearlite kind of opens up that medium. Kind of gives it that air flow inside the pot.
you want to use a clay pot
because the plant can actually breathe in clay rather than plastic.
Plastic actually suffocates. And now the secret to
keep your orchids happy and healthy. Don't use regular water.
because tap water
is filled with calcium, a lot
of toxins and chemicals. it is not really
good for the plant.
you want to use distilled water. this
is very pure. It is like
rainforest water. you kind of want
to drench it with distilled water.
you can go to the market and buy it on sale.
usually it's like seventy nine
cents per gallon. a gallon lasts a long
time because you are gonna realise that orchids don't really need that much water.
it just likes to keep moist. It doesn't like to be
soaked in water. but because this is a new medium
the bark will retain a lot of the water at first.
so you want drench it.