Start by carefully pulling your plant out of
the pot.
if it is really rootbound this might be a little
bit of a challenge.
feel free to squeeze pretty hard. once it
slides out of its pot.
check to see if the plant is rootbound.
if it was rebound you want to massage the
roots
and spread them out so they're not growing
in a tight circle. once you
massage your roots place your plant in
its pot
and then start to fill it in with high
quality potting mix.
now this is important. use high quality
potting mix. you don't want to use garden
soil.
garden soil can cause the plant to rot
and can also introduced pests diseases like
insects in your home.
you don't want that. one other helpful
tip is that as you are filling your pot
with soil
make sure the plant is at the same level
it was going in before.
you don't want to plant it too deep.
otherwise you can also cause rotting
issues. after you fill your pot with soil and
pack it in really well give your
plans a really good drink of water.
once your pot is filled in, water well.