so the first thing you need to do
is take your plant out of the pot and sometimes
that can be pretty tricky to get the plant
out of the pot. if it's in a plastic nursery
container
you can give the pot a few squeezes to loosen it up.
if that's not working
you can flip the pot upside down
support it with one hand and then bang it on the side.
that usually lets you
pull it off.
when you have roots that are really
rootbound like this we need to loosen them
up so they are not all coiled. if you
just go ahead and plant it in the next pot
they will keep coiling around. so what
you do is you just start to
gently begin to work them apart. shake
out that soil from the middle
and just loosen up those roots.
ideally you want them all to be
hanging down nice and loose.
because then when you put them into
the new pot
you can spread them out and they won't be
growing
in that tight circle. when you choose a
new pot there's a couple things you want
to look for.
first you want a pot that is only an inch or two in
diameter bigger
than the container that
the plant was in already.
the reason why is if you put a plant into a
huge pot
there's a lot of excess soil and when
you water there's so much soil that the plant
can't take up all the water that's in the soil.
so the soil
stays wet longer than it should and that
can cause root rot problems and
other things can go wrong with your plant. so
you want a Pot
that is the right size for the plant. so I'm
gonna go ahead and put this
little plant into its new pot. the first
thing
is you just add some soil up till about
the bottom third of the pot. then
you take your plant and stick it in
flaring out the roots and see how deep
it is in the pot.
you want the crown of the plant where the roots come out of the plant
to be about an inch below the
surface and that
give you plenty of space to water when
you're watering.
so just double check that
and then you can go ahead and fill i with
soil
just around the edge of the plant. gently tap
it into place. you don't want to pack the soil
but you also want to try and get rid of any air
pockets that are down there.
so get the soil in nice and smooth.
kinda smooth it out. then to really
settle the soil
the key is to water it. That will really
get any air pockets that are there out
and get your plant all
settled into its new pot.