so to do this prepare a clean dry pot
that is no more than two sizes larger than
the old one.
place a piece of broken clay pot or wire
mesh
over the drainage hole. now this prevents
the soil from running out when you're
watering but it still allows the water
to escape.
then add a layer potting mix to the
Bottom.
now to remove the plant from its current
container you want to place the plant stem
between your fingers like
this just to support the plant and then
turn the pot
upside down. now gently
tap the pot on the bottom. if it still sticks you
can
tap it in other areas around the sides as well.
then gently just remove the pot.
remove any dead or damaged roots
and then gently break up the roots from
the side
and the bottom of the root system.
then finally
remove any loose old soil from the top
to a depth of about a half inch.
place the plant into the new pot and add
more soil.
now gently tap the soil with your
fingers but don't pack it too tightly.
fill the pot with soil until it's about
half an inch to an inch from the rim
of the new container. then water the
repotted plants thoroughly and you're done.