so the first thing i am going to do is fill
the pot about one third of the way with
the potting mix.
I'm going to remove my plant from its old
pot.
I wanna separate the roots so that they're
able to
settle in and spread out into the new
larger pot.
you can also use a garden knife for this.
place the plant into the new pot and
then continue filling with more potting
mix
up to about one inch below the rim of
the pot. after you finish filling your
pot with the potting mix
you wanna lightly pack it down. and now
it's time to water.
you wanna water a newly repotted plant
pretty thoroughly so it is able to settle
into the new pot and you want to make sure that the water soaks all the wy through the potting mix.