what we're doing first is putting some
rocks in the bottom sets gonna let the
water at the bottom conjuring up more
easily and
again it won't drown the route to the
plan and
we put this synthetic fabric over those
rocks
and then a little bit and this organic
potting soil that you see the left
we're gonna put that in next entry and
nice
level foundation so here we are just
porn this in an ominous knew that a
little bit with my hands in
and make it an make it level so the next
important step
is taking the plan at its all
putting usually you can you know don't
water it because otherwise it'll be
let let it dry out a little bit you can
see that the roots there
they're all bunched up through pound
investment definitely need to be
repotted
to turn the pot sideways grab it by the
top firmly as you see there
and just pull the pot out or pull the
plan to the park should use landau
so here it is and you can see how much
smaller the old
the volume of the old part was versus
the new one now when I'm doing is I'm
using my fingers to break up the routine
can separate them out so that they can
they wanna be tied up in knots its can
help the plan adapt
and and get nutrients and water in its
new
pa home they're gone just
stringing out getting all the dirty in
and setting it right in the middle
and not too high and leaving a man inch
between the top and the
swell here and the RAM love this new pot
and and my friend here she's gone around
the edge