by carefully pulling in bikers out of
the pot
is really rebound this might be a little
bit of a challenge
feel free to squeeze pretty hard once it
slides out a bit spot
check to see if the plant is rebound
if it was rebound in 10 massage the
roots
spread them out so they're not growing
in a tight circle once you
massage your roots place your plant in
that spot
and then start to fill it in with high
quality potting mix
now this is important use high quality
potting mix you don't want to use garden
soil
garden soil can cause the plan to rot
and also introduced pests diseases like
insects in the home
you don't want that one other helpful
tip is that as you feeling your partner
so I'll
make sure the implants at the same level
it was going in before
you don't want to plant it too deep
otherwise you can also called running
issues Avenue you fill your partner so
I'll
and packaging really well give your
plans a really good drinking water
was here pappas filled in water well