you know I parts I broke in the drop on
the floor you could take a stone
and you just wanna put that in the
bottom what that will do is it will stop
the soil from running out as you water
it but it is not going to stop
the water from running out this part
about an inch higher than the old one so
if I were to put this
in the bottom what's going to happen is
it's going to be too deep
you want the plant sitting at the same
level
that it was in your previous pop so how
we gonna do that what we're gonna put
some soil
in the bottom and we're gonna raise the
soil level up
so that when I place this plant in the
pot it will be just as high
a general all-purpose oil is pretty good
for a plant like this prayer plant that
we're using when it estimate about how
high up
I want that's and where things you want
to do if you really wanna pack that
doubt
one step before I finally put the seine
I wanna
keys the route we want to encourage some
growth so now
we put this n I've got a little bit of a
room there at the top of the
plant so that when I do water it's not
going to run out the sides are
over-the-top you have your soil
and what you gonna do if your gonna pack
this in and it's very important
you pocket in very tightly
he have like a little who like this a
small spade
you could use that to help get the soil
down in there