pretty easy because I just I just got
back from the grower like a month ago
so you even out the pot
their North you might have to cut the
pot of if it's really if it's really pop
found so don't be afraid of that
and certain loosen it up you can see the
roots right here group oh boy
too sure loosened up has the what I've
done is I put enough
so I O in the pot so that loops
his mother fell off some input from
where the soil in here to to raise it up
a gear
because I wanted up about happen inch
above the pocket is gonna sink down
cell little bit more here so I'll
here
there we go that's gonna get it any you
can just hold it together hipsters to
fall apart you can
all that together appear and I love
Warren castings in Compostela
it to what what I meant by plantings
with so I'm gonna go in and put a few
handfuls of that
around here before I go ahead and fill
it in
and then I'm gonna win
and Phil around soda
plan to be supported in the pot I'm just
gonna go around and I'm gonna fill in
with
so I owe all all the way around said so
it's nice and