a coffee filter and I just put it over
the bottom hole the bottom
drain hole in here and I just keeps all
this loose soil from coming
out the bottom at first until it gets
nice and
a lil bit more compact in their kick it
is very very loose
and this I'm is a succulent and
cactus mix has a has a lot of perlite
it has arm a system crash rockin it
sometimes that as horticulture of and
because the succulents wanna be
really really really dry so it's
important to use our
I a cactus and succulent makes when
doing this so
what you're gonna do use your going to
Press aside the pot if it's really
I I know that this one is not critically
pop out if it's really pop and you can
you think he love your hand and you can
write press go around and then you can
Paul the plant out
me to be a little careful with that
because these paddles can
kick panels can break off there we go
there
there there the roots there so I need to
add a little bit more
into here cuz I like to leave it up a
little bit
about that the
edge up at their baby because it is is
it is gonna think down also to
this is gonna pop it's going to get a
lot of babies of here
and now I'm gonna use my favorite thing
to condition the soil which is
worm castings and compost I just work a
little better that in there because
succulents really don't need fertilizer
at all they're so tough and so strong
and then I'm just gonna go back in I'm
gonna fill around with
nice loose soil gonna work it
all around here press it down
a little bit fill it up a little bit
more because the soil is
solu- is going to it is gonna sink down
a bit so
so what I do is I I will keep this plant
dry
for about 337 days just so I can settle
in
and then I'll give it a really good
watering it it takes a while for their
this really loose mix to get wet
and then it's gonna think down a little
bit and then I will go through when I
will add
a little bit a more a bit on the top