okay so I've chosen this this nice I
clay pot
gourmets glaze on its really pretty it's
kinda makes big drain hole in the bottom
you wanna make sure that has a nice big
drain hole so that the water had a
chance to run away
so it's not sitting in and moisture and
bring peace a paper towel on the bottom
you might choose do some stones or
a sponge or whatever you want for a I
have to keep some soil and
and a but absence or over this
first let's check this out take that
paper towel off she was nice enough to
put it in some damp paper towel which is
nice because
it's been sitting out for about a week I
am
she did this last Saturday
and I'm on Saturday again
you might see this I at a different time
but it's been about a week
sitting out and it still looks good I we
got some routes going on here this is
world problems attach the main plant
as you can see there's another one here
some healthy root systems going on
they'll get much better when they when
they reach the soho
just gonna take off some of these damage
leaves
fantastic
so I just wanna see where they'll fit in
here
I don't wanna plant them too deep I
wanna plan to maybe to this point right
here
I if I plan to Deepdale wrought
if I plan to shallow they won't do well
so I wanna maybe this 10 plan to this
level here
already could see that so I'm gonna add
a little bit more soil
a surprise I haven't had an aloe vera
a plant in a very long time so those
things they
I a I say I need to get but I'd never do
get
and yeah
it's one of those things I always seem
to have all the crazy stuff but nothing
nothing really common
so anyway I
think we've got a deep enough here now
under plant these
sorta separate but kinda in the center
the pot
kinda criss-crossing each other
me move where's my
they have a
I have a bucket for my soil
I wanna add enough soil around here too
to support my I'm using a pre Morrison
soil
when dealing with cactus and succulents
it's not necessary to use a primo since
oil
I am sometimes it's better to not use a
pre voice is so because
you need a few days for the big powers
over
before you well water the ENP but this
has been sitting out for a week so
Primos and soil wasn't gonna do any
damage
the root system has already calloused
itself over things are
on their way to recovery I'm sure it's
already thinking new growth new growth
new growth
so we should be good smoothing the stuff
around where wanna
packing the soil in I firmly around
the base in the planet's you
adding a little bit more so here trying
not to make them too deep