from the container
look at that great route system
keeping your hand on the bottom of the
plan
placing her really journalist rule
you can hear a squeal alright why she
settled nicely in the container
important to have I remember that in the
bottom of all the containers as a whole
and so put a few a broken pottery shards
or a few stones over that and it'll stop
the soil running out onto your patio
deck so with nice ridge
organic soil fill up the sides
to the original soil level of the plug
really important to remember
as you fill the container up with the
soil don't forget to use some slow
release fertilizer and a
which he will do about every the 30-40
days this will keep the plug really well
fed