actually kick because it retains so much
my share
that the plant which can breed so what
you redo fares
is go ahead olive if
ask you don't want clean it out you when
you can it be careful that the real
Riteish and
outer side metal pipes with them loss is
there some
let's get kinda high behind im inside
but you she's always I'm
outer part because orchid likes to breed
have a lot
but the Maas compacted because shipping
purposes
mosses you so that you can eat a lot of
the water my share
for the plant but in time actually
trails
orchid if it doesn't get enough air to
try out that moisture that has retain
nestle orchid Ali hi and so you wanna be
all see
chale show
after you remove all speedy
basically them and like it holiday nice
this is
very still a good condition to rescue
a lotta times have all way and it's
really
kinda Chile to rescue K
that we have it all and most all
mas has been clean out you mind going
hi and put I half
chant
or I can happy story
stack
ac I hi
compaq I basically just keep
town lack up
yet time that to
Carey like believed
you can see that the like a huge future
where you
up air I share and can
going and like
me like it right track shakopee
funk have pack
ok mic
F hi you want to use a clay pot
at the plant sheep claim Cape
happy and a secret now seek
keep orchid happy and healthy speak
because tap water
to hold water it feels calcium lot
toxins chemical really
XP he could I
yet you want to use distilled okay this
is a piece here effect
rainforest why kind of money
transhipment still
and you can put it in my queue sale
usually it's like
cents per gallon gallon that's a long
time because you relied
just like to keep life just like you P
soaked but because this is ATM
the park retain the water first
so you want drenching bikini