every pound they are actually that's not
too bad
sure you can see it the Sun is the the
Dexter
so it it's a little bit said Amanda
roots but it's not
not horrible so I really took out the
first
said i've star leaves up a bit and will
plant this
probably a little bit further down
so this'll actually grew roots anything
that you put under
under the dirt will grow more reads
something at just a little bit %uh soil
here
my party mix the bottom and I'm gonna
add
gonna do bout twenty spin
the beach fertilizer Saudi they are
gonna blinkers that
it in the bottom an eye out a little bit
more
so mix it up a little bit
and we're gonna break up these routes
just a little bit
right
but that spun down as we can
so while I hold the stem with one hand
nanopores the the soil and not the other
just to keep it straight and centered
anywhere pack it down a little bit and
ivory cream ice and dust
potting mix which is Merkel grew
forget party mix that was that at Costco
from $9.99 for 55 QuickPay
so it's a really good deal have already
gone through
how the three bags if it already so that
is our heartaches