is make sure
do
then I usually have a trash spoken in
like up
got so hot it finger gel whole hothouse
love the okay
crumble you can see the
the hell Russ
taking care not to damage gross
but I try to get as much hotel out I
yet but most are starting to drive also
i think im just gonna leave it alone
Fisher even it out there at the bottom a
little bit
yes taking a bus ahead and here's the
trick
can you put him
sure okay did you get it all in overalls
being very careful happen to people do
this is better than one
hi and make sure goes it now then going
all less
okay so we're going to have to do is to
have to take it back al
being here your whole and you can take
it out just a little bit
I think I already have some next and
their I can take some Italian
being very careful not to break the
branches
flag so
I didn't sales going to be easy
I their
haha for them all try again clinic and
their
okay perfect how another thing that
you'll see two
do I get home after and also on wire
basket are a liar show on top of it that
so I can set them plus a little
in a and they'll drop down back to the
bucket shops hype this up a little bit
double
pushes oil another
status wire shelf ideas really good
because you can just sit there and shake
although there can hear thrown in there
for antonio so
Hyundai Pat
I don't worry about the branches falling
out right now
you don't really need to be concerned
about that
guy has getting a hotel
yeah the road area
home okay