is take chartres place it over the hole
in the bottom of the pot
making sure that you don't completely
block up the whole water still needs to
be able to get out of it are you plant
will drown
next to take a look at how big the pot
is that the plant is currently in and
how big the pot
is that you're gonna put it in you want
to make sure that the plant is going to
be sitting
in about at about the same height in the
soil so you need probably to put some
soil on the bottom the whole
first had some soil
that looks like a bad enough soil the
next step is to take the plant at the
pot it's currently in
this is a plastic pot so it's going to
be pretty easy to do
if it were a terra cotta pot it's a
little harder you have to really
use some elbow grease and sometimes if
it's been in there a long time
even have to break the pop with this
plastic pot
with simple given a couple good bumps
to loosen the park net
help her plant pots
you wanna loosen the soil on the bottom
check turned the plant around make sure
there aren't any roots
better going all the way around the pot
if there are you need to tease them out
or sometimes even just cut them it won't
hurt the plant at all
they'll just grow some new routes now
it's time to pop it in its popping in
and that look like about the right
height
when you're putting a plant in a pot you
don't wanna put it
right up to the top level the pot or
when you try to water it
the water with this run right out I'm
gonna
back bill with our potting soil making
sure that push it down in loosely don't
want to pack it in cuz that'll
get all the air out of the soil but you
do want to make sure there aren't any
big
giant holes down in there the plant
shake tap settle it in there
not the last step
is to give the plan to drink water you
want to make sure that you water it
thoroughly until water is coming out of
the holes in the bottom up the pot
it's much better to water fewer times
thoroughly