this slightly larger while two sizes
larger
than the existing parts and put away
horticultural Chris in the bank
Hall house for the drainage then
take a piece of paper a place that
over-the-top
a proper classical circle out put it
over the top the grapple
stop soil from falling through
being washed through the park when you
watch the plant priceline.com possum
just using
ordinary potting compost into the bottom
of the pot
just permit down slightly take the
plants
and tap it ass if it's pop this one's
really
really grown into the pot very least see
all the routes
filling the entire base the parts and
skin removed
just the top it's a comp costs you can
hear him actually breaking up
some other race beat quite gentle but
nonetheless take the top out top
centimeter
of this plan citing very wet as well
gently to you some other routes out from
the side plant
your fingers don't worry too much but it
be careful not to break the plan tonight
but don't worry too much about to
about damaging just listen up so that
the roots are encouraged to grow
towards the outside rather than just
friends around in circles
just make sure the pots going to sit
correctly
the plant could sit correctly in its new
part I'm going to fill
in round the size the plants with some
new compost
be quite gentle with this plant is quite
brittle
I don't want to break it off
want to make sure that it's it's in the
center the pots
I'm affirming the new soil down the
sides
plant make sure there's no air pockets
just cover the top of the so I'll
surface where you remove that top one
centimeter
a soil before
firm the soil in my lights put a little
bit
more Chris around the plants just
address the surface
expect that protect