and then you're able to turn it upside
down
so I'll pull it out a bit spot and i
wanna break up the root ball just a
little bit
so that it can this it can work the
roots can work their way into the new
soil
and then
go ahead and put it into a new part up a
little bit of soil
down to the bottom to start out you want
to keep the
plant the base of the plant at the same
level it was a reason the original soil
if you bear your plant too deep down in
it actually can cause
the plant to rock more easily trying to
get it
position where I want and then
had soil around
and then you can use that ok piece of
wooden dowel rod to press the soil down
in
had just a little bit more soil
and then I like to top dress
my soil with a granite gravel it really
is just an aesthetic choice
and
to split up around the top of the soil
and you can use the large tweezers the
precedent around the base of the plant