place the copy soldier in the pot making
sure that you can for
any drainage holes that are in the pot
and then put a thin layer of soil
in the new home now did amana so that
you could
in the pot will depend on the size of
the pot that you're using
the number 12 increase the size by more
than two times the original size and the
container that
gerber daisy is an once you have that
layer of soil in
you will need to remove her gerber daisy
from its
old home and to do this you can simply
cut away the plastic pot
you don't want to do that gently tip
down your
gerber daisy upside down in simply tap
on the bottom
and squeeze on the sides the next step
is to change the rate easing those
roots are giving them permission and
telling them they can grow out
well and your root ball to fill at its
new home in no time
the poacher gerber daisy in the
container still it was so well
making sure that you don't our still was
so well
you want this to a level that the plant
was in originally
to be the exact same so a level in the
new pot once you have done that gently
tap on it