paper plant is a course to have a good
container
and a some good soil normal you're gonna
wanna step it up into a
container this at least one size larger
then what something came from
with pepper plant you might start off
with something small like this and then
go directly into maybe a gallon
five-gallon or maybe into something like
a North park's
make sure you've got a good soil and a
good container
now for repotting your little plant
we're going to take the plant we're
going to
remove it from its beginning container
we're a little
the root system and gently pull at root
system apart if is rebounding almost
every little container plant is
and the next stage after we polls all
routes apart
we're gonna put it into the container
and planted about the same dept level it
was before
and maybe add a little bit of dirt
around it and then kinda packet in with
her fingers
just like pressure
and the next step
is going to be watering corporal water
in here and make sure there's no air
pockets in the container
and it gives our little botanical body
and nice during