repot
so to do this prepare a clean drive hot
it's no more than two sizes larger than
the old one
place a piece to broken clay pot or wire
mesh
over the drainage hole and it prevents
the soil from running out when you're
watering but it still allows the water
to escape
and then add a layer potting mix to the
Bob
have to remove the plan from its current
container he won a place to plant them
between your fingers like
this just to support the plan and then
turn the pot
upside down now gently
tap hot on the bottom and still fix you
can
happen in other areas around 25 as well
then gently just from New the pot
remove any dead or damaged roots
and then gently break up the roots from
the side
and the bottom I've the root system and
then finally
remove any loose old soil from the top
to depth about a half inch
plate plant into the new pot and add
more soil
and gently have the soil with your
fingers but don't packet too tightly
fill the pot with soil and tillage about
half an inch to an inch from the RAM
the new container then water the
repotting plants early