so at the first thing you need to do
with take a pat on the hot and something
that can be pretty tricky to get up
rattle
hot are if it's an automatic nursery
container
you can give the pot Heath needed can
only thing it up
and then also that's not working
conflict hot upside down
support it with one hand and then being
uptight
that usually lets you
plan of so now
when you have roots that are really
rebound like this we need to loosen them
%uh and for their knowledge oil if you
just go ahead and put it on the next hot
armed of keep playing around cell what
you do is you just started
general begin to work come apart shake
out from there that
a lil in the middle and just listen up
30 ideally 14 all be
hanging down my family is
im because then when you put them into
the new hot
people spread them out and they won't be
growing
in that tight circle when you choose a
new hot there's a couple things you want
to look for
pursuer hot that only an inch or two in
diameter bigger
and the pot that day container that that
wasn't already
and the reason why is a few plant into a
huge pot
there's a lot that s the oil and when
you water there's so much to help
can take up all the water well for the
file
stay wet longer than it should and that
can cause real problems and
other things can go around your plans so
you want a Papa
the right height plans and so I'm a
little help with this
little plan to its new pot the first
thing
if the Jets add both the Wellington
about
the bottom third hot and then
take your plans and stick it in
flaring out the truth and see how deep
it is in the pot
many were the crown a rather rude come
out the planner
out to be about 10 inch below the
surface and that
give you plenty of faith to water when
you're walking
without having the water delivered at so
just double check that
and then you can go ahead and Selim from
soil
just around added a pair and gently tap
into place you know what impact the file
but he also won a tank at Red any air
pockets that are down there
so get the soil in nice estimated
kinda with it out and then to really
handle the file
a key if to water at and that are really
getting your facts better
out and are here
of settled into its new pots ok