planet
we've got her for we got a lot
love I lateral roots this is very
rubdown
we've excluded much of the soil that
that contains the nutrients so what we
need to do is prune away some of these
re
these older routes that gives us space
to develop some more Andrew hairs
are at the same time will replace some
love this older soil with some fresh
potting soil
so to begin we're just gonna take off
about ten to twenty percent
that actual root mass with some pruners
so I'm just gonna go in here and take
off summer this
bottom most root mass
now as I clip making sure that I don't
get
too close to the actual crown on the
planet if we do any damage up here
we're likely to lose the plan but
surprisingly
we can do quite a bit uprooting on these
routes from the bottom part
the plan is very resistant to this kind
of
a this kind of change so I'm gonna
remove
a large portion those those bottom roots
also gonna make some cuts up the side of
the pot
begin promotes those routes to take hold
in the new
in the new plant I'm new potting soil
medium
K
so now I'm gonna rip someone that apart
begin to give more space for
a for new development or development new
routes
I'm gonna look for any diseases any in
any insects that may have gotten into my
pots over the
over the few months that we take in a
day in and out of the house
okay and I'm gonna get a rhythm some
love this potting soil that's
from the past few years K
I'm gonna take a look inside a mild pot
and make sure that there's no insects
and here it is dirty
com you you can feel free to wash these
and reuse them
I'm gonna reuse the same pot so arm
some wood increase the size in the pot
the problem with that is then it's a
larger plant I have to take in and out
out of my house every day okay so this
point I'm ready to
to repot this plant I'm gonna put some
fresh soil in the bottom of my pot
when a press it down a little bit so a
so I got follow the air pockets out
and I'm gonna place my plant back into
its original pot and fill in the sides
from
now over the next several weeks
all make sure to keep this planet I'm
well-watered
all IOU's 0 I A a water-soluble
liquid fertilizer like Merkel grow over
the next week
I'm are once a week for the next few
weeks