then next pottery shot now does this one
is slightly and gold
this goes over the holes
on what it does is it keeps the soil
then
allows the water
to drain out okay
first off
few hunt for the sole
so the next thing we did three remove
the plucked from the container
caffrey tanner upside down
grasped the trunk family and look at
that great
so i'll go look at all those routes
katya handle about them
and gently lower her into the container
centralize that
and then there's the soil regatta grade
so i'll have
itself
a little bit of native soil
add some organic mulch
that is primarily paid months
and coco fibre
make sure when you plug the pond
that the original thought a level
is not loaded for everything needs to
remain the same
so i really start lies there
parliamentarians and ideas about every
forty days
little bit and uh... little bit more
mulch
and hey presto it's is it is is that
the last thing confine our watering can
the last thing we need to do is to give
her a good watering and in the content