first remove the spare wheel
Jack and we'll Bryce from the decor if
the vehicle
use equipped with the wheel chock use it
to chalk the diagonally opposite Lille
loosen the will not spur for jacking
if you're having a hard time trying to
get them undone
use your body white ass
fonda jacking point the jacking point is
different on
all makes and models sorry for TR owners
manual make sure the jackie is lifting
naw since qua
if not lower and reposition do not risky
jack the car up slightly and place the
spare wheel
under the car just in case the car falls
of the jack
and remember to check the Carroll little
bit higher
allowing for the fully inflated tire
went wrong to remove the willie you may
find it fused on with Los Ross
some force might be needed remove the
flat tire
and placed under the car just in case
that the Eagle falls
when changing the tire
never sit with your legs under the CAF
or put your hands at the bottom up the
little
before you fit the spare wheel make sure
the hob
and will start acclaim free of dirt
finger on
fit the spare wheel make sure the wheel
is located correctly
on the hob this is extremely important
some will not
don't want to lives always remember to
put the Thai food particles will not
towards the wheel itself
then put all will not so on and taught
them by hand
before mixing them up with the price
once the will not send nipped up with
the price
you can start lowering the jack then you
can tighten them properly
when the calories down on the ground
totten opposing will not
after each other don't go around in a
circle use a stop at
now remember if your car was equipped
with this face saver
the full-size flat tire may not fit
correctly in the region so there you go
now if you have a spice overlook gonna
do it's important to remember that
you cannot travel other ID kilometers
per hour with
now with you have a spy save up for a
full size face
remember to get the original flat fixed
stride a wife
if you think this was inconvenient
imagine getting a flat tire
and having a FlexPay this
hmm