I
least expect flat tire can cause your
day to come to a screeching halt
instead relying on it Notre to bail you
out consider changing a flat on your own
the only
a Karcher mug reel Chuks spare tire
tire pressure gauge road flares or
reflective trying
hey turn off the engine and engage the
emergency brake
put your hazard lights on in place road
flares or reflective triangles on the
ground
to make yourself visible 21 coming
traffic who's your tire gauge to check
if your spare tire has enough
air pressure if it doesn't try to get
another tire called roadside assistance
place a wheel chock or something heavy
under the senator each tire
before you jack the car up off the
ground remove the hubcap
necessary then use the lug wrench to
loosen the lug nuts
most vehicles have a marker in the
bottom panel indicating we're
carjackings once is placed in the proper
spot
user jack to lift your vehicle until the
flat tire clears the ground removed to
loosen the lug nuts
once the lug nuts are of all the flat
tire of the real
store all the lug nuts in a secure pile
so you don't lose the before moaning new
tire
line at the wheel holes with the bolt-on
wheel bearings
slide the tires far back on the wheel
base as it can go
in place you look months back to like
each night until there's resistance
use the car jack to lower your vehicle
until the tires back on the ground
then remove the jack use your lug wrench
to rotate each not clockwise
until they're completely tight now put
away your tools
place the flat tire on your trunks
designated tires but for disposal later
nothing puts a stop your trip like a
flat tire
but that particular setback will barely
be a bump in the road now that you know
how to fix it yourself