first thing that we going to do is
actually loosen the nuts on the wheel
so we going to loosen them diagonally
across and just enough so that we can
have what we call them
handlers once we've got that
not flirt with then going to actually
jack up the comp we've already looked in
the log book to find the correct
checkpoint on the comp I was that the
Jack in under nato
so that the jack almost close not quite
open and I'll
and would slip them under the points
what we're going to do is slowly jack up
the car into the jack is actually
touching
that point in the Beagle words touching
and we slightly will start to jack up
the car you'll notice the whole cow will
stop silly
if we put the jack in the wrong spot you
might notice that the cops not lifting
probably
and also United that might make start
making some cracking noises
once with jack the car up enough and
everyone always says how do I know it's
enough
jack it up until you've got a bad and
inch or two
from the tire above the actual ground
all
until the Jaquan go up any further now
what we going to do
is loose in the not even more taking
them all off and we always stay put then
into your pocket so you don't lose the
not if you lose one or two you can
always take
one of each other we'll to pull back
onto the spare
so it but they're not to now pocket now
what we gonna do with
actually carefully take the wheel of
sustaining not to lie
staying fairly close to the con and we
going to lift the wheel
all rolling the wheel onto the ground
and we're going to grab the spare tire
so what we're going to do now stand very
close to the
the comp and I actually put my body
against the comp
and we have to make sure that the actual
hold
in the wheel lineup read the knots on
the comp so what we going to do is
do that before we actually have to lift
the time I saw blind all the holdup
we're going to lift it onto the whale
and
sometimes it takes a little bit of a
jingle just to get them on
I hold it with my Lake while I slowly
put the
not back on diagonally across from each
other
so that way you don't have just the top
ones on in the bottom of the wheel is
parking out all the other way around
like what they're not back on and I
tighten them by hand
I can then law when the comp room if the
check out carefully
and then I'm going to grab the range and
heightened
the not top again until there's tired as
I can get them have a check around to
make sure this not think that I've left
behind
and then pack everything away back into
the big game
so now we've got the spare tire on
couple things to point out
it says temper use only spare tires are
designed to get you to a service centre
not feed to keep driving for the next
few months on
and if you see the sticky here at its
maximum 80 kilometers per hour
you know Latics say that speed limit
with this time want you going to the
time I sent
they gonna putting it higher on for you
and then you're going to get will
balance now will align
that'll make sure that you can handle
the cop prickly especially in a breaking
emergency
all when you're turning a corner and
perfect for fuel economy
so it's important that weiss et spare
tires on that you get back into a tie
service center and get a correct i back
go