ok
getting but I was a real pain if you can
change itself it's like a whole lot more
the lawn frustration once you've got the
cast slightly to the side of the road
you'll need to find the spare wheel and
tools replace the plant
in moscow has the spare wheel and
replacement tools located together
under the floor in the back the
replacement tools consistent Jack
to raise the comps so you can remove and
replace the wheel
and arrange to take up the wheel nuts
that attach the wheel to the comps
before you start to change will always
make sure the handbrake is on
and the carries on a firm flat surface
to count move
to begin with find the jacking point
closest to the wheel
that you need to replace
you can find it easily check the Owner's
Manual which usually located
in the glove compartment if the car has
a hubcap use the tool provided to remove
it
loosen up the wheel much just a little
before you start checking the comp
will not should be quite tight say only
to you some strength to remove them
if you can't do it by hand try using it
would
the next step is the checkup aka until a
flat tire he's weeklies the road
ok
up
intake to loosen will much right of
remove the wheel
up and replace it with this man up
this might be the clearly the 1 seed
lined up the holes in the wheel
with the corresponding screw holes on
the counter fixing the wheel nuts back
on should be relatively easy
up
tighten the wheel much opposite each
other and to let them
in lower the comps until the wheel makes
contact with the ground
and tighten them firmly good
when you done that love the cock
completely remove the jack
and remember to put all the tools back
where they came from
with the wheel with the fact I somewhere
handy so you can take it out to the
garage door repair
up
good
finally his couple useful tips
personally always keep comin
what hands out the finished secondly
there's not much point in replacing one
flight tie with another
south from time to time check the
pressure in the spare tire
make shortstop are by the way if you buy
used always check to see its copper
tools you need
the change the time