scale
K
Hey
low
I in this installment we're going to be
covering is how to change a tire with
tools in your car
I took the initiative in called The Ohio
State Patrol on this just to find out
with the safest way to do this is
should you find yourself in a situation
where you have a blowout on the highway
most highly recommend a course of action
is to get off the highway completely
you don't want to be doing this on the
side of the road especially on a highway
where people are traveling at a high
rate of speed
if you absolutely have to pull off the
road what you want to do is get over as
far to the right as possible
first thing to do is to pressure hazard
switch that's usually located on the
dashboard has a red triangle
a in addition to that you can purchase
reflectors
or road flares that you could put out
just to alert other drivers that yes
there is somebody with a disabled
vehicle
and the don't get them gold hit me and
if you have AAA or
you know really big boy friend ur then
yeah by all means contact them and have
them do it for you if you don't feel
comfortable doing this
but should you be in a situation where
you absolutely have to do this
and I would go about this another thing
you want to consider before jacking up
the vehicle is putting the parking brake
on
normally spare tires are located in the
truck or
cases this car they're located the hatch
reason located under some kinda
access Peninsula good
this is normally where you would find
your spare time these are the tools
the you will need to work the jack and
to get the wheel of never attended this
tires flat
that now here's
something else to know and that is that
many times when you get your vehicle
serviced
check the air pressure not only in all
your tires but also in your spare tire
unfortunately there's rarely gets done
see may have a special request this
in some cases you may have to pay a
little more to have it done
cuz should you ever need it and its
doesn't have any area he really just
waste your time want the reasons why
doesn't get done all that often
is because in order to fill this up you
have to take it out of the car and
you can do your technician a favor by a
taking all the stuff I love your trunk I
i cant say how many times so he's asked
me to check the air their spare tire
and they've got you know a hundred
pounds topsoil
back a golf club stern close phone books
ak-47s
now that was an ar-15 sorry yeah all
kinds of things in your truck so you we
want to make sure that if you are having
somebody performers for you
to remove your personal items from the
truck ahead of time that would be very
helpful %uh times I'll say right at me
out so the tire
itself in this case it says inflict 260
PSI
love these instructions are also found
in your owner's manuals
and also listed warnings here on this
car the jack is kinda goofy place but
I'm gonna show you how to get it out
here
it's located in the back here or by
where the tire was
the way you can do is fight for the side
with the adjuster
this and then just twisted in this shit
bring it down you can take it out
now that you have the tire out of the
vehicle we need to do is you need to get
the damaged tire of the car
you look great show and
this little guy you'll need us to the
next thing you need to do is
loosen the lug nuts you don't wanna jack
the car up first thing you will always
love it
if you get this we are headed to your
show you have a slick lol
so the first they were going to do is
we're going to try to
take a look into the scenes rudimentary
to say
in order to loosen things you turn them
counterclockwise in order to tighten
things you turn clockwise
these logos may be on a very very tight
see you may not be able to get
lose like this in fact
it's not very likely that you will so
there's 12 methods and gonna show you
the first message is to stay in a thats
method one
now you may not have the wat to
overcome this so I'm gonna show you
something that
if you're very careful about dealing you
can do this
but if you're in a pinch you can use the
way to the car
and the leverage and you jack know what
you wanna do
is position the jack key such a way
its gonna come in contact with the
bottom of the lug wrench
like this don't try to make sure that
this fits in this little not rehear
what that's gonna do in effect
as use the way to the car overcome
how title lug nuts now if you wonder
what this little hokey thing is for
show this again towards the end
keep an eye here to make sure this
doesn't come flying off it make it
violent
but that is that is an alternative
method using no strength
but gravity to listen to Loughner
you may have to try this more than once
because you're gonna need to get it in
just the right position in order for
this to work gonna
loosen the rest these in the
conventional footpath
now that you have all the lugnuts lose
its time to jack the car up
now there's a couple points on cars
mater motorcars
usually seen have these points and some
vehicles actually had a responding to
these areas
and there's also diagrams in some cases
that show you
where the jack points are for the core
in this case
see this reinforced area right here ray
here
is another area what you want to do
his position at Jack under this area so
that
this not fits rate under
this so it kinda cradles itself in there
this is called the scissor jack the
usually a good way to get these officers
to give a little
will hit but sometimes wheels get stuck
on herbs and sometimes you have to
kick them pretty hard if you're unable
to get the wheel of a car
which does happen sometimes particular
with aluminum wheels
what you can do is you can put the
lugnuts back on
but don't tighten them all the way we
them a little bit loose
drive the car for a few feet or whatever
you have to do and
a lot of times the way to the car will
break them loose the scissor jacks me
very precarious wanna be very careful
not to knock the car of the jack because
if you do it will hurt you
pretty bad and you don't want a bad
situation to get worse
but the next step is to put the wheel of
on
do
the okay now you have
a the new tire on you want to
let the way the vehicle of the jack see
want to bring the Jack downing
this
the
T
okay now that you've got the vehicle
back down on the ground it solidly wanna
tighten the lug nuts one final time sign
in a clockwise direction
you don't need the time this thing so
much that you never gonna be able to get
the wheel off again
just make them snug you got enough
leverage with with the leverage that it
should be okay
you know that you are have any spare
tire mount it and take the other tire
putting your truck is probably most
logical place to put it hope this helps
you should you be stranded with a flat
tire at some time just the bullet points
get off the highway if it's at all
possible
dropped off the highway listen let us be
four you jack or
tight looked at after you let the cargo
using the jack to
possibly lose located me too don't drive
around for an extended period of time
when the spares they're not designed to
be tires they're designed to get you
some place to where you can either get
your tire repaired or replaced by I hope
that this
that information was helpful to you if
you have any questions or comments
we've been down here or you can visit me
at Air
cargo dot com i think im a great day
this is gonna be fun
you might just learn something K