owners manual thing can learn where and
how
to use your spare tire the tires are
having
that
these are you tools to help you jack up
your car
and to take the old flat tire
in Hansen
it up to me right here the gap some
using the wheel wrench you're going to
loosen the not perhaps expert
remember
lefty loosey right inside it
and you can see the jacking point is
this part right here on the frame
do it
now as you remember we first loosen the
wheel nut I have turned
all the way around for weed jack the car
so now we're going to do is come
fully remove the wheel not and take off
the wheel pattern
and its I their website
editing thing
there's nothing you can do the sweetest
do
here be wanting it to you higher job
yet me the first question you may have
is which side they said out
and the easiest way to check that the
a rebel Lodi right here
always been outside then
take the wheel wrench course very
important to get these on
as tight as you can see you make it
safely to a tire shop
sign out going too slowly to lower the
car backed up
you're gonna get dirty I hate Italia
lab clean job art if you remember
the trunk is where we found the spare
and now we're gonna put the flat iron
here with all of our equipment and head
down the road to the tire shop
to have an expert check things out after
packing the bad tire in the trunk
I carefully throw over a in our tires
and then Monica
where tony took us through how
professional checks for damage
been rotated tired
what's happening here but I replaced
with another wild night
and then he has been in touch you had to
find out the mobs of
want to see the most part but they don't
show you where the whole earth
how of in should people change their
tires
I just looked at how much you've got
that right you know
and maybe baby monitors numbered anti so
my
yeah time ago over 25,000 or
the view the only driver and from the
time I realize maybe sixty
visited by thousands who right now the
balance check from
this computer thank you know I was when
exactly how tickling
okay C span the entire when it stops
it'll tell you
how much weight you need handle who re
going to be
the same hole in the center here
lingering you
yet with me when you get 000 here
that will tire is the food good ever
okay
I authority thank you very much your
writing how you like that
you the clean way I
thank you so much for more information
go to Mahalo dot com slash
how to change a tire table that was easy
it took less than an hour for me to get
new tires put on my car
and i learn a little bit about tire
safety to if it's been a while since
you've had your tires changed be sure
you go very soon
you can either schedule appointment or
just show up like I did today
I'm we're the Millers my holiday leave
we'll see you next time
done