the her on Stanley
rowdy need account in a segment we'll be
talking about changing a flat tire
certainly is inconvenient but we're
gonna walk you through it step by step
the don't discover to access the spare
tire ok
well or listen it got the whole down and
give it a couple good ramp-up
make sure its full-year where so you
want to do is put on a flat spare
the new rule on the tire campus can be
quite happy
well have a spare tire jack we set a
reflective warning signal out
we've all sold talk the wheel on the
opposite side of the flat tire
so ready to start changing it the first
thing will do is jacked the vehicle a
you have to loosen the jack a little bit
in order to get the handle of
this particular model has La Grange
built rate inched before we jacked they
would want to loosen the lug nuts
because once is jacked up it's going to
be very difficult to get those lug nuts
are
this particular model has a hubcap which
will just loosen those up
Oct doesn't take much to the made out of
plastic
took the hubcap hardware
now have access to the lugnuts loosen
the lug nuts
this yourself permalink pressing
counterclockwise loosen the lug nuts
not to lose just enough the crack up
there's a little stubborn position
yourself over
using your knee or your foot you can
gain leverage
now ready to jack it up this is a common
scissors check
the screws in and out allowing the Matt
mechanism to move up and down and lift
your car
so as you turn it to the right it'll go
up as you listen it
the jackal collapse allowing the car to
come down now opposition to Jack
you want to be sure to get the Jacka a
good part of the frame
the owners manuals a good place to find
where to properly checked the vehicle
crew can raise it up by hand
to contact the frame is in good position
will use the jack handle to raise the
vehicle
insert the end of the jack handle into
the jet
using it as leverage it'll help make the
car go up easier
member turn it clockwise to go up and
counterclockwise to go down
carefully jack the car up never stick
your hands or legs
under the vehicle as the car can fall on
'cause damaged
checking can take a while so be patient
cautious as you jack
okay now that the car's jacked up no
take the lead not salutes
remember we are you pre lucinda when the
car was on the ground making it easy
know so come right off now trying to do
that while the car was jacked up would
be very difficult
member to keep your lug nuts and close
hand you don't wanna roll away and
addressed it will be hard to find that
will hold retire on
again we're turning them
counterclockwise to get them lose
or to the left will remove the
flat tire said it over here are the way
now there's heavy traffic area you would
want to leave it in the street you might
want to put it to the rear of the car
grab the spare tire put it in position
you gonna Center the spare tire on the
wheel stud
let alone its go to go ahead and do that
up
on lining it up you see lines are pretty
easy
finished all your lug nuts again
clockwise just take on a clockwise is
loose
so what item up by hand
as far as logo just
once a tire center
look not so hang tight take the lug
wrench
again turning it clockwise
tighten the lug tiller firm
not too tight because really occurs up
on a jet we would wanna falling off with
too much leverage a force
Oct
insert the jack and a back into the jack
turning it counterclockwise again we're
gonna lower the vehicle
again it'll take some time but going
down a lot easier than going up
if it seems to go down easy you can just
do it like this by doing it straight
instead having an angled
but if it's too tough you can angle at
and get the leverage that you need to
lower the jack
to raise the jacked Turner Jack low
enough
he can do it by hand now that it doesn't
have contact with the frame
and we can remove it now that the tires
on the ground we'll go ahead given that
final tight
we're gonna start down here then moved
to the top one then back down
over and bakie get a little star pattern
making sure we have equal torque
on the wheel stud
okay well we have a spare tire on a tear
it up
we're ready to go couple things to
remember those who are producing back in
the trunk
you know one XE highway speed on this
temporary spare make sure you get the
big tire fixed
you get you back on the road as soon as
possible amounts family
for Houdini dot com show