burst make sure your emergency brake is
engaged
this will prevent the vehicle from
rolling
next locate your spare and Jack
is can usually be found in the trunk did
play all your tools so they're easy
reach did
locate the pinch weld for the body in
frame meet
tried to Jack underneath and raise it
until it touches the welded
loosen the lug nuts just a bit then jack
up the car
did
make sure the tire completely lifted off
the ground
then remove the lug nuts
and the flat tire did
well on the spare and replace the
lugnuts
did
lower the car into the tire makes
contact with the ground did
I'm not super star pattern this ensures
that the tire goes on straight
you
drop the car down the rest of the way
and you're good to go
did
remember engage the e-brake place the
jack
under the pinch weld make sure the tire
has cleared the ground
and tighten the lug nuts in a star
pattern for more tips
busy YouTube dot com slash on the West
EP that