flat tire
if these eighteen if you're on the road
pull your car over to SA flat
by next budget vehicle and a part 1 1st
gear
and apply the emergency brake now locate
your spare tire
on most of today's SUV's and trucks
despair is
under the vehicle retrieve it following
the steps in your owner's manual
it's a good idea to check the spares
pressure before you go any farther
if your spares pressure is good continue
on with changing your plan
by popping off the cover to access the
lug nuts but the plan into the tire iron
or supplied tool and start to loosen the
lug nuts just enough to make them
easy to turn by hand if they're too
tight try using your foot for added
leverage
now place the Jag under your card in a
line it so that it lifts the car by the
frame
to raise the jack connect to handle he's
been inserted into the jack
turning clockwise until it lifts the
vehicle one she praised the big also the
flat tires off the ground remote
love knots and put them in a safe place
such as the wheel cover so you don't
lose one
now remove the flat tire in laying on
the ground away from the car
line up the spare and lived into place
but the one that's back on and tied my
hands
been tightened down each not with the
tire iron start with one lug nut the
tighten the lug nut farthest away
and so on until they are all tight to
finish up slowly lower the vehicle
remove the jack and make sure the lug
nuts for tight one last time bad said
I remember spares are designed for low
speed travel
so it's important that you have your
original repaired or replaced as soon as
possible
for more information on this project or
any
other do it yourself projects just askin
Advance Auto Parts team member for
assistance
at Advance Auto Parts we're ready
with answers