turn on your hazard lights and if you
have growth like players are reflective
triangle
use them to warn other drivers that
you're working on your vehicle didn't he
entire feeling in your emergency kit if
your tire has only been slightly
compromised
the only patch long enough to get you to
the service station with Deb
tale find heavy object like bricks
around
to blunt the wheel placed them in brand
up in behind the tired diagonally across
from the one that when planning
if you happen to iraq block both wheels
on the opposite
if you have a digital camera or cell
phone with a built-in camera
yeah pick you before you start
dissembling everything that way
still have a ready reference guide how
things should not let me go back
together
down three lay out your spare tire jack
and my breasts
many tires feature a locking lug nut to
guard against that
to remove use the special key tool the
car's manual specify where it's located
step 4: most flood not follow the right
take the lefty loosey will
attach the lug wrench to a night and
turn the wench counterclockwise
repeat with each lug until of another
listing
def by refer to the owner's manual for
the best spot to place the jack
typically along the frame very close to
flat tire jack the car up until the
wheeling of the great
never get under the car with Ana Jack
the fairly unstable in the position
keep other people away until the quiet
lately on the ground
Dept that remove the lug nuts one at a
time
and keep it together in a spot where
they won't pull away I didn't appear
then remove the flag depth 7 now
spare tire onto that we like you may
need to jack the car up the morning clip
on the spare tire
check the tire pressure in your spare
regularly
that way it won't be flat we need it Deb
8 replace someone like night at a time
begin tightening
each by hand then continue with the
language lower your car to the ground
infinity tighten the lug
opposite pairs to ensure uniform
pressure once you're done
replace the hubcap step 9 remove the
object Barton we'll
in place the tools in the flat tire in
your trunk dept and
your wheel is ready but you won't be
able to drive is quickly on a spare
check your owner's manual for the tyre
itself to determine its very top
be and get yourself to the US garage the
camp at your place retired
did you know in texas holdem a flat tire
means you were initially dealt with Jack
in a
or anything good