for automatic steel one in park next
take have capital has one and use a
wrench to partially removed from the
Lightning did not sure how to remove the
hat cap just check your owner's manual
also check to see if your car has
plastic covers over the line at like to
find out
itself been taken off first you like
Iran's probably won't head over them
and make sure you put in Somerset say
don't need any of them
now to take a look back at all gold star
pattern listening one of the last night
have turned and understanding one of the
city way work you way across the tyrant
Obama line at entry to have turned
way to hide
the object like a brick in front of the
wheel diagonally opposite the flat tire
to prevent the car from slipping his
with Jack comes in
the car's frame you to deal with the
flat visibility that went along with
sidecar
that's usually where the Jackass you can
might be different that's just check
your owner's manual for the safest place
to put your tap into the car
remember it possible for the cards for
Pocket Jack
it's never going to cart it only
supported by attack
okay tonight Jack in place now in to
handle
internet clockwise to let the Jacka if
it lowers the car
turn try turning the handle the other
way make sure you read the jack high
enough to replace a flat tire
the military will be followed their so
you mean more to me than anything
remember don't like that see this and
earlier might even take them off
completely
want to like matter of you can pull off
a flat tire
to make she put a new tire on the right
way look at the air about
should be thinking out to replace the
like Matt's going to see more than you
do stand them
10,001+ a few turned an 81% of it into
each like that especially tightened
they go back to prosecute star pattern
to tighten them completely
to lower the jack
tribunal slowly counterclockwise until
the tire just makes contact with the
ground
and what a creepy healers attack for
it didn't work from flat tire makes
each right now it's completely Titans
before you remove the jack dripping tap
any object width 100 opera tired back in
your car for a drive off CIA for that
one
you want to learn more about to have
your card
take her other I'm 11 videos you can
find them
it sa Busa dot com Splashtop cast