you can change the way your cell
everything in a dozen the boat
spare wheel Jack and we'll price there's
also a socket to fit a locking bolts on
other whales
stop by flak in NH bout by halftime
like eight the jacket the mounting point
a sign in the owners manual and left the
car so the wheel
is clear ground remove the bolts and
then the whale
much to the spares nowadays off by
savers
I must only be used to get to the
nearest car repair a
and a maximum speed limit applies place
a spare wheel imposition
and hand tighten the bolts moderately
tight match boat using the wheel brakes
lower the car and from a project now
fully tighten the bolts in across
sequences shine and they have it back
alright
just a few points to mention the call
must be on level solid ground the hand
brake applied
and ideally free if passengers and pets
because any internal movement could
cause the vehicle to become unstable
if you're on the highway then use the
hazard warning lights
and a warning triangle if you have fun
butts if you're not busy mine wrote on
my 2i
your personal safety is going to be at
risk and don't attempt to change the way
yourself call for recovery services
instead