he locates the spare wheel and DJ
removed hubcap to expose the wheel nuts
while the cat has not been raised to
drive a slightly loosens the wheel nuts
positions the jack in the appropriate
location
at this stage the car is being raised to
a safe high
to allow the wheel to be removed
no real nuts them completely removed and
placed in a secure spot
stopping them from ruling the way
the real is then removed and replaced
with the spare wheel
it might take a little bit of fiddling
around
to align the spare wheel use the wheel
nuts
to fasten the yield
while the car is still raised tighten
the wheel nuts
firmly
once the check has been removed you must
insure
you retention the wheel nuts again use
the criss-cross
method to fasten the yield
you have safely executed changing a
higher
if you personally feel you are not
capable
of changing highest safely remove
yourself from
danger game call for assistance make
sure
you be here and execute every step of
the way