do is to remove these plastic
caps that go over the actual knots yes
they do not like the actual not
themselves
but they're not right there off
don't check out with at least in the
Knox but
his when you try and do them the wheel
would just turn on red
it sounds obvious I've done it this was
in its okay
its 3.2 K for the wall locking wheel not
which we need to release first so let's
make sure that same position
now I could have used the standard will
grace is lightweight one that came with
the Cal
this is a standard issue on you need to
have had
a decent breakfast if you can use one of
these I'm a reasonably robust lot but
what I'm gonna do is rely instead
and what i think is safer which is one
of these aftermarket wheel brakes is we
can get two hands on a
and we can exert some real leverage so
let's get this one of first
F
the write some loose in these of
but I'm not mad set them off completely
because I do not want this whale to come
off
when I don't want it to
the normally Bay almost always
those instructions in various languages
on here
sio2 use this jack where it goes most
importantly where it goes
you tryin raise the whole way to this
vehicle
by putting this in the wrong place
component to the bodywork you really
don't want to do that
was stale taken the a danger to see if
the person is changing the oil
so about a look and it tells me that
there's a
on the sale hey a that's depression
where that goes
so there it is some got that in
nice and tie just think it's right there
ripe
one thing as well if you are you need of
other people
with you for goodness sake make them get
out the car
or if they're in the car the children
and their in the car make sure they stay
in the car
the last thing you on when you check in
for cars
people in closing doors unnecessarily
getting in and out to the vehicle
right let's get this way of
just put least one side is nothing worse
again offer to his job in fine at the
applause from the oval
right let's take the space ever on
this crime resistance the space efforts
I is
I'm wheels when they first came out a
few years ago well as well as having the
advantage is liberated space
inside the car I'm reducing weight which
reduces your fuel consumption and
improve your performance
they're all so much easier to handle
wheels and tires have got bigger and
bigger and bigger
I'm heavier and so the space evas all
kinds advantage but for goodness sake
look at it it's perfectly safe ball
don't leave it on your car for a few
weeks
I don't wanna see you in the car park at
the supermarket loading up the car with
one of these things on
once you go into the zone the only place
you need to be going
is tie specialist for your dealership
just cite names of an eye
I don't think I'll put the plastic cups
back on because I'm only going to be
leaving it on for as long as it takes me
to get to a dealer
now on site are all on see simply put
them on think it's I
first and that's a good way stocks in
them off so that you going into the
existing thread you're not
eyes it's a cross threading the hope you
don't want to force the ball seemed to
start with however once you've got the
whole thing it's I
it is good practice get hola tyo atop a
ABC space ever like this
just give them a twist intern
with the wheel brace so that the wheel
isn't moving around its all the wheels
nice and secure
and let the Jak II and then I'll
probably tighten those
five boats make sure these wheels on
right
I still a jack i night at the wheel
aids family legrand Chinese knots
as much pressure as you can apply what
are these away a
will dresses only about ties it needs
today
retrying these up by the way tryin Titan
opposite to opposite instead of going
round the clock
to make sure that it's squarely on the
hope
right that all Titan the really secure
is pumped up I'm ready for the road
again