step 1: when changing a tire it is
important to pick a location with a
solid level ground to ensure the
stability of the vehicle when he nap
time
in our situation we are on concrete so
we will not have to worry about
ok however if you are in an emergency
situation
like your tire blew on the highway call
over to the right hand shoulder on the
road and turn your hazard lights on
I ok make sure that your vehicle remains
on the concrete work
if a car is jacked up on the sand or
dirt portion of the shoulder
the jack will sink which can cause
damage to the vehicle as well as
threatening you're sick
if you drive an automatic put the
vehicle in park ok
and apply the emergency brake ok if you
drive a standard vehicle
place the car in first year and apply
the emergency brake
ok step to you locate the necessary
tools needed to change a tire on your
some vehicles require
locking wheel nut before traveling
ensure that you are aware that the
location of this
without it you will not be able to
remove the law
like the most common story care for
these materials is the trunk of the
vehicle
left the carpet and procedure move the
spare tire
and the tire most vehicles will have the
jacket family
underneath the carpet as well but in the
case of this vehicle
stored I on the left hand side
step 3: start with the jack by placing
it under the frame
fire that K it's important to ensure
that the jackets contact in the frame
directly to avoid damage to the site
scared the majority of modern vehicles
have a designated area
near you well designated area is usually
a
in 12 in this case it'd ended she got a
truck or older people
there may not be a controlled available
if this is the case jack the vehicle up
from a friend step toward
proceed to raise the jack onto the pinch
welds or frame into the car is firmly
supported
actually being lazy into the air at this
time
make sure that the jack is firmly
planted on the ground so that it will
not ship do step 5:
locate the love not on your vehicle if
your vehicle has hubcaps or a center cap
you may have to pry them off depending
on the design from here
not not should be loosened but not
completely removed and you can see
the lot not on the far right is a
locking lug nut this is why you want me
but locking key
in able to remove from here love not
should be loosened but not completely
removed
breaking their insistence that the
lugnuts may take quite a bit of course
depending on how tight they are
ok
step 6:
full erase the car of the gallon by
pumping or in this case
cranking the CAC the amount of clearance
that you want between your tire and the
ground
should be enough you can freely remove
the tire
step 7:
removed a lot not completely off the hub
the people
this may take some time be patient
a quick can't is to ensure that you
remember where you put
the lugnuts there's nothing worse than
losing the lugnuts
when you try to put the tire back on
stat 8 from movie tired there may be
some resistance when trying to take off
the tire
this is often the case when it is winter
and water freezes between the wheel and
hub
don't be afraid to give it a good night
sharking ok
step 9: take the spare tire and place it
on to the hob
matching the holes on the wall to the
weekend no debt
10 place the logs onto the stud that
you're tired
tricky to hand tighten the lug nuts
until they are snug again
this may take some time be patient
child
the
step 11 tighten a lot not securely
for this five lug assembly the procedure
in tightening the lugnuts
will be a star pattern to ensure that
the bill is flushed with the hub
assembly
if you don't do the star pattern
you could run the risk that the only off
on off
step 12 lower the jack bringing the car
onto the ground
we tighten the lug nuts find them as
much as you can
but not overtaking them preventing you
from removing the lug nuts in the future
if you purchase a new wheel assembly it
is best to have it installed
professionally
so that you can tighten the wheel to
specifications
for
step 13:
but all the materials and tools back in
there location