here's a few tips for changing your tire
first have it in part
in on level ground also set your
emergency brake
once a break is set each car has a spare
tire somewhere hidden hand to check this
one's underneath the liner in the trunk
you can use your tire
to take up the hubcaps be careful they
can break on the other side to your
irons the socket
and loosen all the ball stone removal
just loosen 'em and slipped the hook
into the Jharkhand if you look at your
jack
there's some markings underneath it on
Toyota's to show you where
to put your jack is too low markings
reach will
then left the tire off the ground about
one inch
and take off all the bolts
and placed the name pair on
and put both on by hand once
each bolt is little bit snug you're
tired
and then tightened diagonally from pole
to pole
to get all live contain all the more to
the same amount of force
12 ton of 5 start over from the first
against
give it a little bit more but week the
lower the jack till the tires on the
ground
and tighten the bolts the rest away
again going on
star pattern diagonally give it a lot of
force and lastly when you put up cap
back on
don't block the valve stem the part
where you fill in your tires
with their and that's it hope that
helped
thanks