and the congress either in GUI offer an
automatic
impact if you have a safety triangle
place it will be four your vehicle to
alert oncoming motorists
remove the jack
jack handle wheel brace in spare time
from the car
and place on the ground this is to avoid
any unnecessary movement to become a
once a toasted finally before lifting
the car
loosen the wheel not slightly but don't
remove them
entirely different jacks have different
instructions and every car
has a specified jacking point be certain
to familiarize yourself
with days before hosting the vehicle
instructions
must be followed exactly and nearby
place yourself
under a vehicle that is hoisted by a
check jack the car up slightly to secure
the jack
under the car but not to raise the wheel
off the ground been
once he sure looked at continue jacking
the car up
until the tire is approximately five to
ten centimeters
off the ground remove all the wheel nuts
from the stands
and store them in a handy place remove
the flat tire
rallied at the white enlai it down on
its side
so doesn't roll away Rawal the
replacement on a
up to the vehicle the time now needs to
be lined up with the wheel studs
these can be a little tricky but with
the added benefit
it should sleep on without too much
hassle when placing the replacement
wheel on
trying to keep it as upright as possible
this will help the studs along with the
halls in the wheel rim
first cup once the wheels like I did
replace the wheel not
onto the top stud as this will help to
keep the other studs located
on the rim all wheel nuts can now be
sick you would
finger talk using the wheel Bryce
slightly firm up the wheel nuts
they don't need to be completely
tightened at this stage but the wheel
does need to be positioned correctly
lower the jack
and legal the wheel nuts should then be
fully tightened
using the wheel Bryce there's no need to
stand or jump on the wheel price:
the correct or can be achieved using arm
strength
replace the wheel cover if necessary
collect the flat tire
wheel brace Jack and safety triangle and
store them securely
you can get back on the ride but done
waited too long before you get damaged
tire repaired or replaced
you never know when it can happen again
and driving for too long run flats
a temporarily repaired tire or spice
either can be dangerous
and remember on here to help