to make sure the car is in park make
sure they're emergency brake is applied
we don't want the car rolled away when
we get it off the jet second thing we
want to do
called is to pop the trunk the other
where the rear
the 2013 Corolla call to lift the
what's in the truck your spare tire
Jack and all the tools to use it are
located under the truck cover
lift the flap gain access to the
tools first thing you want to do
to pull these tools right off the top
and set them aside
second thing you want to do
is to use your hand unscrew the track
in a counter-clockwise motion to loosen
it up
import the checkout the third thing is
to counter clockwise
unscrew the spare tire but
up the
I
in with the spare tire out
know we're gonna pretend that this tires
are flat tire from Scarborough
you with better Jack
their spare tire we've got the tools
that we make
this talks to your car to
this is broken and used to loosen the
lug nuts and tighten the locals
this tool
we're going to use to jack the car
upping their as we need
the next step is to loosen the nuts
at least 14 her because when you jack
the car up
before you lose their nuts that arm I
heard that would be make it here
or here
the next thing we want to do is to jack
the car
safety reasons you need to make sure
that you jack it up from the correct
place
we want to put the jack is right here on
the two notches on the frame
is two notches in the for the rear news
to not just for the front own this part
if the frame
there's a slit in the jack and that's
just gonna do
writer what gold
yea on that piece of the frame
now wanna take the jack handle
with the loop that thing in slide in the
hole on the jack
and turn clockwise until the tire just
list the girl
now the tires off the ground gonna
finish removing the
wheel mouse in in this process you want
to take the bottom knots
of first so the tire doesn't fall
this way as you're taking the nets at K
we have all the lug nuts off this live
the high right now
okay you were installed a spare tire
with this part for the hub sticking out
as saying on
Bush II fair
you gonna put the lid on its own taper
TN on the inside
top first you
up
putting on hand tight
then you go to lower your jack ok
that counterclockwise
it
your name you're gonna tighten in that
mess with your tired
all
it
ok
now that we're done with that staff
everything's tight you wanna
physically check to make sure the tires
got enough air pressure and it
and it's ready to drive now we need to
put the tools back in the way that we
fail
the first thing we want to do is put the
tire back in the compartment
go now the tire in the jack will fit
back in here
but your tools of course wall work to
put them on top
now we're gonna put the check back in
its place
like I mentioned before
the other tools will not fit in there
with the other with full size tire so
we're going to put the tools
right here in the trunk never we put our
tools back
gonna close to trial we've completed
changing tire on the 2013
Toyota Corolla you need to proceed to
the closest
tire store or are great service
department your Toyota West just 20
minutes from anywhere