know everything here on C this is your
time
you know you put your hand between the
people I'm
the other hand on top yet my shoulder
less straight arms locked not like this
like this here and then you're going to
push
and she mentions cast to give them
enough
compression you certainly here your body
your sister
she wants a their orient brain damage
wanna keep up are random at he
another one bites the dust to go did
I last bassirat
I you how person with you that person
hatch rests on this side where fresh you
on this site so after
30 compressions you will allow them to
start everything
they will said head back to open the
airway
anyone knows reads him along
one second dress inches and now and this
can be seen is working when their chest
rise way air cell
one to Media Inc