days the is for damages
subject for the dangers in your
workplace is maybe furniture
all things you can sleep a trooper think
at the end of the Y
%uh is for sports gently shake the
victim shoulders
goldeneye tiny Tony UK tiny
you know check if they respond to a tiny
see how
this he said for health caught up
governor us has someone call for an
ambulance saying he's following day and
I'm
icon celebrating our and if you have a
deferral at a
have been fetched a different light now
I
is for a way check for anything obvious
such as food
that you can remove to the head back
and with the jewel cheap free
be is for brazing book
listen and feel to check if the victim
is breathing normally
this shouldn't take more than 10 seconds
not
suffering drums that of
see is compressions if they're not
operating normally immediately start
chest compressions
place he'll be a hand the center in the
chest
wallkill was in and press hard
to should compress a chest
Fox enemies approximately two-and-a-half
inches the form
30 chest compressions for every too
risky Press
K don't think
I'm to perform 100 chest compressions
per minute