is metromail see staring see quickly
scenes
he higher around or
live that in witness year
here like on a round very important
love he line contacting
yet after-care seen
that preceded we shaking the
there and asking here she from there
a check list is contacting
DNS it stay your day of hot
lol dead hers nearby
kind here net you EMS for me
yes there is no yeah then
you lack EMS that
is MSJ
the ER early mid by
said
and this year %uh acted
shell them in check
a he
stay which stands for a Brady
and circulate hand
up airway any class his math any
sign re the day
rainy role here she and her
anyway medical professional CA by
internet and 3d you will hack
wire CPR with
breeding the best way to get
you for reading and mathematics me start
net
and head back and he didn't
then make an airtight when you now
on the day and get quick Brett and then
check
their polls at
dress instilled from there
then you will have to perform Chester
with here
and Alastair every minute chest and your
am NOT on the chest here are completely
straight
and you 15s check and check all
day
reading India that nasa now
one more time
and 15 compression
n checkered of the day p
I'll Lee times or and
now operating or way internet