I've cappuccino okay okay he didn't
respond to me
meaning he doesn't talk to me he's not
moving
he Rt any breed me signed life
K at that point if I'm by myself
I me yell for help well if someone
called great
I told them to go call I wanna get me it
no one pump
pin I'm gonna go leave to call 911 in
getting eighty
it no one comes and I've saw him fall
eclipse is Jeff and fell on the ground
then
I'm gonna go CAW right away
it I hid see him fall meaning I walked
up into the room and I found them down
after I did they hear you okay I'm going
to
K MEDC PR for two minutes before any
K so he saw him click this doesn't fall
you leave first if you didn't see him
clutches chest and fall
you mean you found lying on the ground
18 is a CPR first
then call but only if your buyer sup
that the thing I
your help well as other people around
your
than 10 then to go call i won get the
eighty
K so without a shot I sent the one to go
calling one
get me I'm gonna check make sure he's
not breathing
he doesn't appear to be breeding i'm
looking for. chest rise and fall
cp3 I'll teach us rise in pollen if
many came here I'm gonna say he's not
reading
from there I'm going to start with
my compression morning put the he'll
love my palm
on the lower half up his breath bomb so
that big bomb right in the middle of
their chest
lower half ovett K interlocking my
fingers
I'm going to press down 30 compressions
Press at least two inches in an adult so
if this guy weighs 400 pounds it might
be four inches
if they weigh only 120 about two inches
K you're going to do it at a rate of at
least a hundred beats
per minute that's pretty bad the 100
beats per minute
so we know the song stayin alive you can
do that
if not you know about 30 compressions in
eighteen seconds
that would be a great K and you always
want to lock up a requirement in HS have
to come back
all the way with natural position to let
the Hartree fill with blood
sup might their impressions are gonna
look like this
one to 3 4 back 6 7
8 9 10 levin 12 13 14 15 16 17
18 1920 120 33
important part 617 389
30 any given to press
care POC in math remember it has a
teardrop shape
sometimes they'll be so nice and only if
they know that the top that goes
already know around now make congenital
downward pressure you don't want to
squeeze you know one in mass
just dental canceled our pressure any to
tilt the open airway deliver to breath
I just need to teach us rise and fall
you need to blow up too much
people not too much it causes air to go
to their stomach in a person is gonna
balmy
we don't want that that would be not so
good for him or you
so to breath there's one where
noted CCHS I don't bother looking at
cedar chest right and then fall
then I'm gonna go directly back into
doing
30 more compression point to 3
for by 6 7 a 9
10 level 12 13 14 15 16 17
eighty 19 20 21 22 3 fortune five to six
with them
839 very go right back into giving to
breath