check to make sure there is no immediate
or further danger to the rescuer
other personnel or the casualty check
for a response
try two-week the casualty
raise an alarm and call 911 immediately
and see if the casualty is breathing if
the casualties breathing normally
place them in the recovery position
wait for medical attention to arrive and
monitor their condition regularly
if the casualties
breathing normally you will have to
immediately commence
CPR for demonstration purposes
we will use this manikin first
you should kneel alongside the casualty
in a position that will allow you to
comfortably apply
vertical pressure during compressions
next visualize where the center the
casualties chest is
then place the he love one hand on that
point in the center of the chest
this achieves our aim of placing the he
loved one hand on the chest
above the heart keep that hand in
position
and police say he love the other hand on
top of the first hand
and interlock your fingers at the hands
like this
alternatively you can grasp around the
wrist up the first and
like this either method is acceptable be
sure not to apply any pressure over the
casualties ribs
abdomen or the bottom end up there
sternum
as this can cause damage to internal
organs when performing compressions
you should pivot from the hips that is
you should not be rocking back and forth
position yourself so that you are
directly above the casualties chest
you're compressing arm should be kept
straight
your bottom hand should remain in
contact with the casualties chest
and your shoulder will be directly above
the chest
when compressions are delivered
compressions should be rhythmic
with equal time for compression and
relaxation
and you should allow the chest to recall
oil completely