So in a situation like this, we see that the person is here.
We don't have our gloves on, but keep in mind that we're going to,
in the practice session that we're going to follow this up with.
We'll have our gloves on,
we need to make sure we have our personal protective equipment,
the scene is safe, and now we're ready to rescue.
We call out to the patient - they do not respond.
We tap and shout on the collar bone.
Are you okay? There is no response.
At that same time, we are now looking for
normal breathing, or abnormal breathing, no breathing.
Abnormal breathing, again, meaning agonal gasp for breath.
This is not respirations. This is a drive to breathe
that's not getting oxygen circulating into the bloodstream.
This person is unresponsive, not moving, not breathing.
We're going to activate emergency medical services or call a code
and then we're going to check for a carotid pulse for no more than 10 seconds.
This patient does not have a pulse, is not moving, not breathing.
I'm going to find the center of the chest and start my 2-inch plus compressions.
We're going to do this 30 times.
The rescuing partner is going to then do the head-tilt chin-lift.
Really get that head back far.
Cover the mouth and nose with their one-way valve mask.
And they're going to give two full ventilations.
About a one-second breath each.
We're going to check for chest rise and chest fall.
Chest rise and chest fall.
If it doesn't rise and fall, we probably have to re-adjust the head.
Because the #1 obstruction in an unconscious patient is the tongue.
Normally this corrects it. They're going to try again.
Then we get chest rise and fall. We know the air went in.
We can continue our chest compressions.
We're going to do this until an AED arrives,
or emergency medical services,
or the code team comes and relieves us.
When I get exhausted, I need to indicate to my partner:
we need to change, I'm getting tired.
So after these compressions, let's switch.
25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30.
He gives two more ventilations.
Comes around carefully.
I reposition myself with my mask.
and 5, and 6, and 7, and 8 and 9 and 10, and 11, and 12, and 13...
In this case, I've got a bag valve mask.
If you as a rescuer, or you're in a clinical setting,
have a bag valve mask, this is optimally the thing you're going to use.
It doesn't even matter if it doesn't have oxygen.
There is some science now showing us that that's not as emphasized
anymore in resuscitation cases.
But if I have a bag valve mask, I can now use this,
do my C-E method of sealing the mask,
give two nice, slow, full breaths,
get chest rise and fall while the rescuer on the compressions continues.
And again, we do this until the next level of care comes and relieves us.
And we'll keep switching on and off every couple minutes