got Joe graphic Joe and he doesn't
respond so we need to move on
to the next step the next step is
calling 911
when you call 911 you need to make sure
that you give them as much information
as possible
so they are able to help you you also
should never
here operator first because if you do
they may know
%uh might not have all information that
they need to come to that
rescue also if there are other people
around you should have them call 911 and
tell them what to do
so you are able to move on to the next
step more efficiently
and quicker the next three steps
have an acronym no to see AB or cat the
first
letter for that see and you do
compressions
to do compressions you here handout
see it use your call and then you
wrapped around your fingers
you locate the lower breast on other
percent and bring your hands there units
do
30 compressions at a rate of 100
compressions per minute
the Dept the compression should be at
least two inches
so if this occurs gradual this is what
happened and you should also count aloud
when you do it so
you know whenever you are at want to
jury
or type laptop
think 21 22 23 24
52 extractor and at your computer with
impressions
you do the next part of cap which is a
airway to check the airway you should
put your cheek against his mouth
we do this you feel moisture on your
cheek
listen for noises that breathing from
his nose now
and right look for chess prizes so
offices cramped Joe
we would call it s look at Chester as be
over moisture
and listened for noise next step
after that is to breed and to grab a
chill
do this you need to make sure that
Airways not obstructed unita put your
finger and earning his chance
so it's not clogged or anything you
should get
the patient two brass and these press
should be at a normal rate
when you are reading about right now
make she plays knows also so there's no
excuse for the nasal passage
so this is crap Joe go light
after a completed
with the Bret Hart you go back
impressions European compressions brat
compressions brat
and tell the medical providers arrive