check for danger before approaching a
casualty
find out if they're conscious by Jim
shoulders and speaking to them
if they don't respond check whether
they're breathing normally
open the airway by putting one hand on
their forehead
and gently tilting the head back lift
the chain by placing two fingers on the
point
taking care not to put any pressure on
their neck
which could block anyway look for
movements have their chest
feel for breath on your cheek and listen
for signs a briefing for 10 seconds
if they're not breathing normally place
your hands in the middle of their chest
and gave 30 chest compressions peep
you need to push them water pong
sentences
and duties to rate 100 permanent
after thirty open the airway by tilting
the head back
and lifting the chain page then use
seal your mouth and there's Android for
about a second
give to rescue breaths and then repeat
another
30 chest compressions continue cycles
30 chest compressions and to rescue
breaths