Check for responsiveness
by shaking and shouting
at the person or rubbing
their chest bone hard
with your knuckles.
The person's clothing
is not removed.
Next, command someone to
call 911(or country's emergency number)
-- "Call 911."
-- or make the call yourself.
Then begin chest compressions.
>> You aim for the
Center of the chest,
usually between the nipples.
Put the heel of one hand there.
You put the heel of the
other hand on top of there.
And you lock your elbows.
And the reason for that is
that no one is strong enough
to do 100 compressions a minute.
And then you put your shoulders
directly over the center
of the chest and you fall,
compressing it about 2 inches.
>> It's important that the
hands are lifted from the chest
after each compression.
>> That's because the
recoil of the chest --
that causes a little
vacuum in the chest --
causes air to go in
and blood to come back.
It's also important to pump
on the chest fast at a rate
of 100 times per minute.
An easy way to maintain that
beat is to think of a disco song
like "Stayin' Alive"
by the Bee Gees.
>> It turns out if you try
to do 100 times a minute,
even if you're not perfect,
you have the best chance
of getting the most flow.
>> It is a jab-jab-jab-jab
rapid pumping action to move
that blood forward to the brain.