step 1: check when you check the scene
you want to make sure that is the for
you wanna make sure you did not come
into
so i'll check for safety then check for
the number vacant how many victims you
have
clues as to what could have happened
head
look around for other bystanders who can
help you go
to the victim and find out if they are
unconscious this way to find out
fitness conscious or not is you talk to
them they don't stop
show up and see if they respond to you
step 2 call
if they are unconscious or any other
life-threatening condition
you are going to you automatically go to
the next step
which is calling 911 preferably
if you have somebody yell wanna be
bystanders you can send them
to call 911
step 3: care
the third step that we're going to
follow is that cares to care for the
condition
fine this is where we going to refer to
the ABC's
care the airway breeding in circulation
step 4: a for airway
I'm going to open air able to the airway
till the head back this teacher
I only know love you worry me
Warner warrant has a I want
31 more mild
when acid
step 5: be for breathing
there is no breeding able to might be
step
which is the two rescue breaths 3 shield
on their
from barrier between myself to take me
again
avoiding contact with anyone was a date
engine OSA
killed the head back 50 GN and you
to breast those press about one
once they long now the breast when here
that tells me there's no blockage
I am going to look over the body see if
there's any bleeding
and begin CPR if the brats did not go in
the victim is choking and the airways
obstructed attempt to remove the
obstruction
and follow the steps for unconscious
choking step 6:
seed for circulation the Red Cross
prefers that lay persons no longer
checked for a pulse on an adult
so checking for circulation in a victim
involves watching them for coughing
movement or normal breathing if there
are no visible signs rescuers should
begin CPR
step 7 CPR
we begin CPR compressions on the adult
we're going to do 30 compressions and to
press
we're going to do the other five times
in two minutes
to perform chest compressions on an
adult place that he loved one hand on
the center the person's chest
between the Naples keeping your elbows
straight place your other hand on top of
the first hand
with your shoulders above your hand push
straight down and compress the chest
about one and a half to two inches
step 8 stopping CPR
was weak we began CPR we never stop
we do not stop to recheck we just
continue without stopping
until week notice life picked up
amazing in this movie causing breathing
I'll moaning anything that would
indicate that the person is alive do not
confuse bonding with us on a life that's
nice I'm
step 9 recovery now we are going to
get this are so that it supports his way
here
and in the media this case the victim
from continuing to roll
and the the speed away from the floor
if they happen to vomit or past-life
throughout
all that will drano now wait for rescue
personnel to arrive