sir it the victim does not respond and
the victims not breathing
were not breathing normal line 110 for
someone to call 911 okay
and have been getting a TD an AED is a
portable electronic device
that helps the heart returned to its
normal rhythm if you're alone
call 911 and get the ED yourself then
follow the ET's boys proms
it now ED is available immediately start
CPR
beginning with compressions doing CPR is
not hard
anyone can do it and now the American
Heart Association
is making CPR easier than ever we used
to tell people
that the proper steps for CPR are airway
reaping compressions
or ABC we change that order
to the compressions come first it's now
compressions
airway reading RCA be this new order
makes it easier
because anybody can start out with
compression even with no CPR training
just push hard and fast from the center
the chest
if you haven't trained keep pushing
until help arrives
when you give compressions make sure you
push the chest down
at least 2 inches and allow a little
time for the chest to come back up
pushes hard and fast as you can the
perfect
rate per compressions is at least 100
per minute at the same speed
as the Beatles song stayin alive so try
to keep that in your head that helps
if you've been trained in CPR push in
the chest
thirty times in open the airway by
tilting head back
and lifting the chair is how to reach
the lines
next give to mouth to mouth brass over
one second preach braque
and watch for the chance to rise here
continue to see a b-cycle
until help porn a derives use the same
CA be cycle for adults