so check to make sure there's no danger
on the bicycle be electrical wire
could be some gloss and feel anything
you can see the dangers
that's the first thing remove that next
we move on to
of a response such talk in touch you
question I'm there's no response okay
now we know there's no response we move
on
it switches San for help so you have
someone a he say
can you please go to call the ambulance
let them know we have an unconscious
patient
if you're the only one here and have a
fun pick up the phone
call triple-0 and let them know what's
happening so someone's on their way
while you're working on question okay
now we move on
I I is for a way so we have to check
year was plain first when a little bit
ahead to buy this
that last edited in stride why secondly
we open up
have a lot to make sure is a wise planes
in this case it is
it's nothing it struck me
getting in or out okay now I checked he
say why we may want to pay for brazing
so I have to say these breeding so open
up
firstly what i do to have a listen in a
deal can i watch the chest
nothing's going up and down on not feel
anything coming out of his mouth I can't
hear anything either
so he's not bringing now that we know
he's not breathing
we a shame he's going to date Cpl so in
this strike into center the chest
he'll on the hand Center the chest and
compressing
from here now with CPR
we need to do ratio 30 compressions to
two Brits
and the right of those 30 compressions
that one hundred per minute
so that's not quite two per second site
let's get started is a thirty
one to 3 for fun 6
safe night knowing tape 637 28 gone
30 we immediately get cigarettes Joe
support and head to the game
strike back to 30 compressions one to 3
for 5 6 7 I nope
back for round two rates there with SEP
I
and a 30 compressions into press we
continued eyes into we get a response
until normal trading resumes