assess the scene look around make sure
the scene is a
are their safety hazards a chemical
spill
electrical wires gas fumes for anything
dangerous
you can't help anyone if you become a
victim to
if the scene is safe check the person
for a response
tap or shake the victim on shoulder and
shout
are you okay if you do not get a
response from the victim
yell for help next tell a specific
bystander to phone 911
or the emergency response number and
getting eighty
and very importantly to come back to
help many facilities store schools
airports conventions in sports arenas
will have eighteens available
next check the victim for breeding
are only gasping
need to scan the victim's body back in
porn
from head to abdomen for at least five
seconds but no more than 10 sec
I can all breathing sounds like gurgling
casting it is not bring you must
start CPR now check for a pulse
to locate a crowded polls on an adult
for child place your two fingers on the
center
the victim's neck slide your fingers
down
the side of the neck and at the notch
between the muscles
you should feel a strong holes there if
the victim how's the polls
but is not breathing give one rescue BRE
every five seconds
then recheck the victims polls every two
minutes
to perform a rescue breaths gently till
the victim's forehead back with one hand
and with your other hand
with the victims Chen this position
opens the airway
pinch the nose closed and cover the
victims now
with your mail breathing life giving air
into the Big Dome if you have a one-way
mouthguard
use it as directed the mouth guard has a
one-way valve
and protects the rescuer from contact
with Mom it
secretions infectious fluids et cetera
place the elastic bands around the
victim's ears
to hold it in position well
give to rescue breaths one second for
each BRE
look for chest rise if you don't see the
chest rise
reposition if needed if the victim has
no polls
start the CPR cycle 30 compressions
to breath 30 compressions to Bretts
until help arrives are you can no longer
perform
effective CPO let me show you how to do
this
first if possible remove clothing
out of the way of the victim's chest
next
locate your hand placement for
compression with your hand
draw a line from armpit to center chest
replacement place that he loved one hand
on the lower half the sternum breastbone
now placer other hand over the first
interlacing your fingers for support
with your arms straight
and your shoulders positioned over the
victim's chest push down
on the victim's chest porn adult
you will want to push down at least two
inches of ice enemies
now watch as I perform 30 deep
compressions
in 18 seconds or less you want to be
able to give
at least 100 compressions in a minute
you may lift your hands slightly off the
chest
between compressions to allow performed
me to keep your hand placement keep
interruptions to a minimum
it helps to count out loud some say
humming the tune to the nineteen
eighties pop tunes stayin alive
is good for keeping the right temple
I'll give 30 compressions
in 18 seconds or less counting out well
230 after 30 compressions
get to grab west
look for the chest to rise between
breaths
if there was no one available to help
after performing five cycles a CPR
call 911 and/or get an AED