No response, call 911. I'm going to open the
airway; look, listen and feel for ten seconds.
I don't see or feel any breathing, I'm going
to go ahead and give a ventilation now. And
I have adequate chest rise, I will give a
second ventilation. Again adequate chest rise.
I'm going to go ahead and reassess for carotid
pulse for five to ten seconds. No pulse. I'm
going to now begin CPR. I want to make sure
that I move my patient to a hard surface,
still maintaining my airway, find my one third;
4 and 5 and 6 and 7 and 8, 9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23,
24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30. (giving breaths
and start pumping again) 5, 6, 7, 8 and 9
and 10, and 11, and 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17,
18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28,
29, 30. (giving breaths) I have just completed
two cycles of my ratio of thirty two compressions.
You want to do approximately four of those
which will take about two minutes. At the
end of that I am now going to reassess my
patient. I don't need to check for responsiveness
cause I can tell my patient don't have no
change in it. I do though want to look listen
and feel. Still no response. It didn't get
my first ventilation in. I want to make sure
I reposition the head.
Two adequate ventilations, assess for a pulse.
If still no pulse, I will continue CPR and
wait for EMS to arrive. If there was a pulse
it is safe to say that you should give another
round of CPR for at least two more minutes
just to kind of help the heart, it has just
been restarted and it could use your help
assisting it while pumping. If the patient
does at any point wake up though it safe to
say you can stop your CPR.