check for danger step 2 check for
response
tap shoulders for me and say hello hello
are you okay
step 3: if there's no response shout for
help
shout call ambulance 995 and
getting AEG step for open airway
had killed should lift method. one hand
on forehead to tilt the head
two fingers up the other hand on side
near it to you to lift up chin
step 5: check for breeding look to see
if just rises
listen to breathing sound and feel
Brett's on cheek
if only gasping or not breeding stock
chest compressions
step 6: chest compressions locate the
lowermost
read nearer to you and slide middle
finger longer rib
to the not shoot the lowest into the
breastbone place index finger besides
the middle finger
and the she love the other hand next to
the index finger lock your elbows
and with the home straightened stopped
30 chest compressions at the rate of
$100 per minute
1 and two and three and four and five
and one
and two and three and four in 10 and one
and two and three and four and 15 one
and two and three and four and twenty
one and two and three and four and
twenty five
one in two and three and four in 30
allow chance to return to normal
position after each compression
perform to ventilation shaft every 30
chest compressions
maintain the head coach in that position
and use your thumb and index finger
to pinch the nostrils closed take a
quick breath
and she'll your mouth over the
casualties mouth and deliver to
quick short pretzel one second each
taking in a breath in between
release the nose after each breath
then continue CPR if an AED is brought
to the casualty
continue CPR without interruption listen
and follow the AED instructions
the AED may prompt you to stop CPR
temporarily