then check the ABC's
open the airway checked the breathing
and checked the circulation or the pulse
first
open the airway take the hand that's
closest to the victim's head
and put it on their forehead next take
two fingers
up the other hand and put it on the bony
part of their chin tailback
next check for breathing look
listen and feel for the breath look for
the chest rising and falling
listen for the breath in your ear and
feel the breath on your cheek
do that for about five seconds
if there is no breeding you must give to
full breasts right away
take two fingers that the hand that's on
the victim's forehead
a pinch the nose shot then take your
mouth
and seal the victim's mouth giving to
for breast so that no air escapes why
you trying to breed
then checked the circulation or check
the pulse
take two fingers and put it on the
center the victim's throat
and slide it into the groove that's next
to the throat
do this for about five seconds and if
there is no pulse
chest compressions must be started right
away
first position the position your hands
on the victim's chest
take two fingers at the hand that's
closest to the victims feet
and slide it up the bottom at the rib
cage to you reach the notch
that is directly beneath the breastbone
then take your other hand and placed
right next year two fingers
we've your fingers inside your other
hand according to the American Red Cross
what keeping the correct and position
straighten your arms and lock your elbow
so that your shoulders are directly over
your hands
while in this position enough pressure
will be created to compress the chest
one-and-a-half to two inches for an
adult
do this fifteen times County out loud
want and to it 3 at four it fight
in six and continue the cycles a
breathing and compressions four times
after the fourth time
check the victims pasta get and if
they're is still no calls
continue the cycles until the victim
breeze again
or Intel trained medical professionals
arrive