my neighborhood at the working hard as
close as possible to the one with a dead
battery
to make sure they're not touching next
for parts and put them in part also turn
off and unplug
anything in either car that runs on the
battery like headlamp
radio air conditioning and everything
plugged into the power outlet
like mp3 players are South okay
best really important I
battery is crashed in making do not
attach the jumper cables to it
the battery Creek colo inquiry after
delivering
not paying now locate the positive and
negative terminal
to the battery conveniently enough every
battery is labeled
so he shouldn't have too much trouble
determining which is which
if you don't see the marking it's
probably because the battery terminals
our journey
just wipe off any corrosion our battery
acid near the terminals
with the rag now
you're ready to connect the cables
she is an easy way to remember how to
connect them you're looking for a
positive outcome to the situation
fell you want the highest number
positive connections possible
as for the cable themselves the positive
cable
usually read and the negative cable is
usually black but
not a jumper cables a color-coded the
same way to read the instructions that
came with them before you start attach
the positive cable
to the positive battery terminal in the
car with a dead battery 1st
and then connect the other end of the
positive cable
to the positive battery terminal and
working hard nackt
connect the negative cable to the
negative battery terminal
the working part
then find a solid metal part of the
engine
on the dead car to attach the other end
up a negative cable to make sure it's
not a part of the battery
and the painted
it should be a clean shiny metal like
I'm not on the engine block
if if 30 oily clean up first
when you connect the negative cable wooo
fired
normal to think about as a replacement
for your morning coffee
not the cables are set up
you're ready to start jumping first turn
on a good cars engine
and let it run for a minute or two
before you try to start dead battery
if you wanna check that you have the
cable setup correctly
turn on the dome light in a dead car if
it comes on
the cable there right now you can try
turning on the debt card
if the engine sounds like trying to
crank but won't turn over completely
give it a few more minutes and then read
the engine a bit
on the good car want the engine in the
dead cartoonist over
you can remove the cables but be sure to
read the engine running out
it takes a while for the battery to
fully retired
when you remove the cables be careful
not to let the clamped tight each other
he could be in for quite a shock
disconnect the cables and