vehicle very important knowledge she
never does 20 damage daddy
hanks
your first let's get another year of the
working battery
important message others to the barriers
are near each other she can reach them
with jumper cables
the next step is to use of a nice show
jumper cables you could probably just
the vehicles
you've got the red positive side to the
dead battery
did you do the red positive side on the
good battery then you do the black
a negative on the good battery then
you take the black I for the dead
battery and he got the some kind of
ground on the engine Detmer won
its best foot off the ground is valid
for a better response was he don't love
the circuit
first fresh start they do not like this
sometimes
it's not that bad it will still be able
to finish the like this
that does work start to live with the
battery and let the church he dead
battery for a few minutes before you
start
dash to them green
I think I have a Coast Guard you i'll
arrive allow the charge up the dead
battery before coming to start the other
guy
on for
for
the only thing the cables you doing here
were scored a hit with the muffin
he sure you can not to touch the table
and together