okay step 1: this is a car with a dead
battery and this is that I was a
professional
you need to pack them as close together
as you can but without him touching
because I could cause a spark
turn ignition of in both cars first of
the move the battery cover
and you're looking for the positive term
in office is usually marks
read like this when they all have a
little plus sign me connect the
read John played to the positive battery
terminal on the desktop
step 2 connect the other end up the read
complete to the positive
terminal on the good cup on this car the
positive terminal isn't
colored red but it does have a a close
sign here sorry
we know that's the right one step 3:
connect the black complete
to the negative terminal on the donut
set for
connect the other end to the black
complete to Center of the Earth point
on the dadka
step by leave a jumper cables connected
for about three minutes
the backing both can equalize make sure
that's the cables a
move when away from anything moving in
the engine as well
and make sure you remove the back cover
at the engine compartment
step 6: started at a Cairo to run for a
minute
then what is still running start the
dead car and lead both running for about
10 minutes
don't remove jump leads personal cars
engines are running
step 7 turn the ignition both kinds of
and remove the comp in the reverse order
that you put them on