sore start by connecting possible the
cable
to the positive posed to the dead
battery they will connect
this positive then to the positive post
alive that up
now for the negative 20 connect negative
to negative
so take the black and the negative and
connect this
to the negative terminal on the live
better
and then the negative cable here
to the post on the dead there now as an
option
you can connect this the negative in
to either the engine block or the frame
to the car says it really that important
the
did the cables in that exact order
you're full of questions today aren't
you
actually you're asking great questions
it is important to connect positive to
positive
negative to negative cuz I batteries
current is designed to only flow in one
direction
that current is interrupted we could
have a battery explosion
I wouldn't want that and the reason we
can connect the negative into the cable
to the cars engine block or the frame on
the car the dead battery
is that this helps keep the positive and
negative cable separated
and maximize the chance affective
grounding we've got the car separated
think we're ready to start the car with
a live battery
jump car that saw me in
why do you have to start this car first
well that's a good question
by starting at the car with the light
that refers to creates
a more efficient flow of current in the
alternator at this car
is already recharging the battery here
so that the flow to the car the dead
battery
is going to be stronger that if we did
not have this current got
okay I think array to start this one up
relax go ahead
now we've got the cables collected
properly in the live car running
leave let this situation set for just a
couple minutes
let the current flow from the good
battery into the bath
couple minutes should do it
done
the the
okay I think you're ready to start the
car
with the dead that
okay we've got the car with a dead
battery started now we remove the cable
want to do that reverse order source RI
removing the negative
little under the positive cable
I make sure you're removing the cables
another illness touch
like a result in a spark maybe even a
fire