this is our
donor car it's important to get them
parked beside each other but make sure
they're not touching and ensure that
ignition is off both cars
so depending on your car make and model
there might be color identifiers
to indicate whether it's the positive or
negative terminal of the battery
to go to connect the red cable to the
positive terminal of the dead car
and then you're going to connect the
opposite end up the red cable
to the positive terminal on the donor
card
Sonex I'm gonna place the black cable
on the negative terminal up the donor
card and lastly I'm gonna place the
other end up the black cable
on an unpainted acted point on the dead
car
now once you have the cables connected
to both cars leave it for about three
minutes that hello
devoted to the battery see equalized
between the cars
in that time it's a good idea just to
make sure that the cables are
outside the engine bay and not near any
the moving parts after the three minutes
start the engine of the donor card lead
at lunch foreign minister for sacking
get to start the engine up the dead car
I want sided let's hope I
million ten-minute so after the 10
minutes make sure you turn off the
ignition in both cars before removing
the clip
eclipse will be removed in the reverse
order that they were placed initially
so firstly remove the black cable from
the earth point on the date card next
we're gonna remove the other and the
black cable from
the donor car so third on going to
remove the red cable
from the donor card and finally I'm
gonna remove the red cable from the dead
pack
with the cables are removed from the car
you can start the engine in your dead
car