with your good vehicle with the bathtube
vehicle to get battery
gonna hook up I'll are positive cable
we're going to use the red color coat
fast
it again good clamp on our positive
cable here
and then on our negative cable here
at this point RK before class or wanna
make sure
that we don't touch it and we come to
the vehicle with a dead battery what's
gonna happen is
when you make this connection it'll
generate spark
that's why Warner spark a way for the
battery so wanna start here
but the positive sad pick up here
and they want to find a good point
somewhere away from the battery
of its metal own give us a good ground
%uh
the other thing you need to be aware of
is where the belt is where the police
are going to be turning I you don't want
to create
a and interference with your cables and
the running vehicle
so this point okay was a fucked up got
the battery it up on the on a good
vehicle got positive cable on the dead
battery
and a good gramm point away from the
battery now will start are
dollar for car make sure the make sure
that all make sense
part of the battery homemade dedicated
charged up for
really did you let me what's right for
me
lol charge the battery from the All Nite
they had a camera SK like I do it exact
same for the first quarter
get our ground cable of disconnect are
back a positive
the dead battery make sure we keep them
separate