started
Park both cars in mutual next to each
other so the close but not such an
and put the ham break some you don't
want to roll away
next should pop open both car bonnets
and secured them
than check that the jump leads can reach
from one car but she to the other
stunned over by the car with a good
battery
the red gym late is the past late so
find the positive terminal
on the work in bad shape now this should
have some kind of Lost Symbol
all with a red cap all red markings
connect to this terminal using the click
the end the read complete
check in at the teeth gripped the
terminal properly than go back to the
car with the flat battery and cannot be
other end
this red completed the positive terminal
on the flat battery you don't need to
switch back to the car with a good
battery
pick up the block complete and connect
it to the negative terminal which should
how to minus symbol
or a black cap now this is the tricky
bit to remember
with the other end to the buck to meet
move back to the car with a dead battery
invest time instead of connecting it to
the negative terminal you need to find a
solid piece of metal
on the engine like a bomb or a bracket
double-checking that its
firmly attached this earthing point has
to be away from the fuel system
on battery and some cause even have a
specific anything but for this purpose
to humble to find out if yours does and
I should be all foreign to the John Lee
is properly connected
now once all the gently the hopes up way
a few minutes for the voltages to
equalize
I want you waited a bit you'll then need
to start the engine of the healthy car
and let it run for minority leave this
engine running and then try and start
the engine at the college had but
battery
if it doesn't work way a bit longer with
the engine to be %uh the car still
running before trying to start the
engine again
the engine does start then leave both
cars running for its hand
minutes now you know is the jump leads
are getting a bit hot then you need to
tell me engines office let them cool
down a bit
after 10 minutes ago the next step is to
turn off both the car engines
than in reverse order you need to
Kathleen remove
me to the jump leads be really cattle
not to touch the clips against each
other
all make contact with any all the metal
such as the car's bodywork
otherwise you cause a bit of a band stop
by Kathleen clicking the black
complete from near pinpoint than on
click the other negative and at the same
lead
do the same with the read complete and
flipping it from the positive terminals
at the donor car