one in the red jumper cable to the
positive terminal on the stalled
battery red on dead remover to the good
battery connect the other red
people claim to the positive terminal on
the good battered right now it's time to
move on to the black jumper cable clamps
or stain on the good battery a jumper
card
as you want to connect one in the black
jumper cable to the negative terminal
on the good battery no might be tempted
to stay connected
black jumper cable to the negative
terminal on the dead battery
but most experts agree to not do this
there's a chance because a Spartan
exclusion
probably won't happen but better safe
than sorry we want to do is
instead disconnect the other black cable
to a clean unpaid in mail servers under
the disabled car's hood
the car's engine blocks a good place or
somewhere along the frame
the car which is what I didn't know what
you wanna do now is
start the car that's doing the job in 10
allowed to run for 2-3 minutes before
starting the date card
basically charging up the dead car's
battery but now
turn the ignition on the dead car and
the car start well done
you jump start the car now what we need
to do is remove the cables in reverse
order
up how we connected so we start of with
the black cable
on the former dead batteries car removed
from that he's a metal
you claim 22 then we moved back over to
the jump in car
remove the black cable from the negative
terminal on the good battery
we go to the Red cable on the good car
remove that from that positive terminal
go back to are formally dead car