over the ignition to prevent damage to
your car's computer teacher booster
cables ready
knowing that this black and red
terminals the first connection
is the red terminal to the did car's
battery that's the red caps terminal on
get car him over to the good car we put
the rent
connection clamp on the red terminal
positive the battery
and then lack clamp on the negative
terminal about
I'm make sure that their own good and
secure before we make our final
connection to
over to the dead car we put our final
connection on the engine
to look good metal surface make sure
it's away from the batteries
you know cause a spark which would cause
the battery to explore I'm
I'm