it's a positive jump late I miss it fast
guy who
on the dyno vehicle I should connect to
the positive terminal
you can mail Catholic type this I the
hon connect this to the positive
terminal
of the catch up to the vehicle next is
the negative and again
the first connection we might be so the
negative terminal of their
found a vehicle I'm being very careful
with the negative come played
this meets the guy who on unearthing
point on the call now this combi
acclaimed metal on the engine or claim
to metal on the chassis
but it doesn't want to go directly onto
the battery itself
when you connect and they're also
consider and be careful you don't
connect it to
near the back tree or any fuel
compartments on the call
so there's a nice claimed and that okay
we could connect
a nest right onto the battery now buyers
late to connect it
we need to white at least three minutes
for the pulpits the side lost between
calls
now but the lead to being connected and
left for a few minutes
week announced all the time the vehicle
we should lead to find a vehicle running
for a few minutes and then stop a
casualty vehicle
we should leave them by priming
for about 15 minutes select the battery
voltages equalize
if during that fifty minutes the late
start getting warm
cocaine haul the shit ton of bicycles
I'm disconnect the lates
yepp don't disconnect the late while the
vehicles running
that this can cause serious damage to
the call
so we start with the negative terminal
which is placed on the engine
of the casualty vehicle and we
disconnect that being careful
I'm disconnected from that are difficult
once disconnected the negative we
commend move on to the positive
and again be careful when you disconnect
them not to talk to network