jump-started powers not difficult but
can be dangerous if not done properly
it's really important you follow the
right procedure just a sec Park the cast
in a safe place
and make sure that the not touching nice
to nyse: what's best
as jumper cables and not very long check
the fight Catherine cock on your child
and that the hand brakes are on then
switch off the engine at the diner power
open the bonnet a page cannot unlike at
the batteries
make sure that by factors a 12 volts if
you're not sure
don't attempt to jump-start the guy is
self the batteries have a positive
terminal and negative terminal
the positive terminal is red with a
positive symbol
and the negative terminal is black with
a negative symbol
you can see these in 98 what why some
other right Ron and battery acid but the
clock now back to yes it's pretty nasty
stuff so avoid getting it on your
and throw away the cost right away first
connect the red jumper late to the
positive return 0
at the flat battery and then attach the
clip on the other end delayed
to the positive rate terminal at the
diner battery then connect the black
jumper late to the negative black
terminal at the diner vehicle
before attaching the free into the cable
to a solid metal past but the cop with a
flat battery
such as the top suspension mount don't
connect the cable to any moving past
ensure that the cables a will clear the
exhaust or drive belts
an easy way to remember what color goes
where is to think afraid
as a bright happy positive color and
black is a negative kala
stop the engine at the diner vehicle and
let it run for a few minutes
about you
thousand brits a minute then stop the
engine at the people with the flat
battery
allow the engine to fast auto from in a
minute two minutes before disconnecting
the jump relates
now carefully remove the jumper late in
the reverse order to the connection