all right sir you want to take your
cables
keeping them separate from each other
both and that your cable
here and gonna go on posited
lifetimes you're mad real have a little
plus mark on it
which indicates positive Armie Hammer
red
cable terminal which indicates fun and
then you have your black
goes on negative as you can see there's
a negative
sign their and a black people as well on
matters like
make sure you keep him hired cable
separate from each other so they don't
sparred
which can be here problem anyhow so
that's how we're hooking up our
batteries and keeping everything
themes everything red and black cock
pp
separated them
you things
world
so notice again this is a different
style a battery
at that what we call a top post are
other vehicle at inside pulse but again
you see a plus mark
you see red here if you
come across a vehicle hanging you're
just not sure
negative your and positive post are two
different signs
the positive polls in a bit larger the
round post here
and the negativism well that's smaller
than the part that so that's another way
you can identify positive and negative
on a battery
group again keeping our gable separate
we're making good contact
book he had just made a mistake that
black teens
nurturing a black blog
dread that could've Google cause a
little bit of a problem
windblown you up but it definitely
because the problem
nothing in the reason why I don't hang
back to the cables connected just yet
I've got everything right now and now
I'm gonna do my last connection between
the two cables
so as you can see I got my comp
cables completely separate from each
other room bring my read to my red
positive deposit near make a contact
here
notice you get one side has your cable
I'm gonna make sure to get both cable
cites jim Kerr
the cable side little cables either all
touching in the middle
that the better contact gabled
cable sized
coming together now we have a good
contact and let it run for a little wild
charge it happen with fire the vehicle
up
black-on-black hangin
head
them
well because the link that the be
collector the hazard
travel we've been here in a minute a
charge the dead battery
and you can tell if your battery
alternator is charging on running car
you can usually hear
little bit of a high pitched noise and
that means that your alternator
the charged connection
good you hear that hyphen one-year
alternator
because it's actually charging act than
normal
we let it run for a minute and then
we'll
go ahead fire Honda the vehicle in the
back in the big the eight
so I had to hire car demery the smaller
Honda
didn't take that much starter
million american Gardiner ha
me
bomb
well it's its run n I'm gonna carefully
disconnect the cable
fish you sure to keep their red and the
black
the positive and negative terminals
separated from each other
its