firstly check a flat battery for any
signs of damage
simpson's tracks or leaks
never try to jumpstart a car
with atomic stop as there can be a risk
of explosion
of fire not we need a fully charge card
to take power from
cars can be jump-started from
any other heart with the seam voltage
battery fitted
most European cars operate a 12-fold
system so check that both the flight on
the charge batteries
much ideally the charge should come from
a similar are larger hired car look keep
the battery position
and both cars them Park the fully charge
card opposite
to the dead car allowing a walking down
between them
and turn off the and we know it connects
the batteries together
using I jump lease which must be done
and
this connect one of the red
keep a lens to the positive terminal on
the dead battery
this will be identified with a plus sign
on is often read and Connor connected
opposite and
of the red cable to the positive
terminal on charged spotted
attach the blacks cable to the negative
terminal
on the charged marked with a minus sign
and finally the opposite and
of the black people to the negative
terminal
on the dead battery and some instances
this can be
connected any middle point with and the
cars
engine bay insurer that the cable
ends I kept part during this process
ensure that all electrical items
with an each car are switched off such
us
lights heaters and radios this makes it
easier to start the car by using less
Park
start the fully charged on
letter mom for three to five minutes
revving the engine as you do so nyse:
attempt to stop the car with Prof laptop
should start straight away if not
leave the cars connected for a few
months to
allowed charge to build up before trying
again
once the car has been started remove
leads in the river sequence take off
the negative on the flat battery phone
by negative on the charged battery in
the positive on charged pottery
and finally positive on the flop