I'm
you want to put them deposits copper
cable
on the dead battery good and go over to
your car
with the good battery and put on your
Patrick a positive cable here then go
with your negative cable
on a good battery and then
well take you may have cable for the bad
battery can apply to a ground
bond the body in the vehicle the engine
something's gonna be grounded
other than the battery terminal at that
point even wanna start the car with the
battery
rev it up a little bit but run for a few
minutes and then go ahead and give it a
crank on the better side
cora all
alright so we got the car the battery
running calls and getting ready to feel
about 2500 rpm sure to let it sit like
that for
dog 10-15 seconds family going to the
car with the faulty battery
thank record over
right now wanna go ahead and crank over
this car the
try to get the car runnin for reverse
the process
with the
jumper cables for
playing in
positive Ste