connected to your positive terminal up
the dead battery
after connect the positive cable to the
positive terminal
love the dead battery you're going to
connect the positive cable
to the positive terminal the charge
battery you will then connect the
negative cable which is black
to the negative terminal up the charge
battery
and then you'll connect the negative
cable
to either your engine block or in this
case we can connect
mare to the bring perfect
I would let it sit there for about 3 to
4 minutes
and then tried turn your car over now
wants the car turns over
you want to reverse the process for you
would take the negative
cable from the frame then you would take
the negative cable
from the charge battery then take the
positive cable
of from the charge battery with the red
one and then take the positive
cable awful positive terminal