on both cars barry on one side battery
on the other side
a should be a problem because the cables
will be long enough
this is the good car
I'm going to start with the good car and
always start by putting on the
positively first
hear something real-life love if these
are laying on the ground and they're
touching
my little incident earlier was because I
had it hooked up to a battery that has
to do things together
you know what these touching so you want
to look these up
one at a time so that both are not
hooked up to one car
and then your got these other two laying
on the ground that could potentially
arc in touch so you start with the
positive battery cable
just give it a little wiggle
when he put it on that way that teeth
from the jumper cables or by 10
a little bit can make a better
connection okay which one positive in
which ones negative
very good question I on top of the
battery
we'll see a lot of times
is a plus sign for positive and a minus
sign for negative
the positive cable will have like
something read-only
think this was read
and then a negative cable is usually
black
puts a case like this you don't know
you don't see a plus sign your negative
sign is kinda hidden
the negative cable usually runs
someplace that touches the body
somewhere you know this is some place on
the body
or someplace on the engine the positive
cable always goes to
starter which is that guy so what you
can do if you don't know which is which
as you can follow the cables and
the one that has anything that goes to
like the body in the car
or the outside the engine that's the one
that's going to be negative
and of course the other was gonna be
positive if you can follow the negative
cable for the positive cable
kid now I'm gonna go to the dead car pin
connector
positive better came once again make
sure that this
the studio not touch next we're going to
hook
the negative cable up on the good car
you go
now here's the tricky part my know
what's coming next
you might not don't hook the negative
jumper cable up to the battery on the
car the trying to jump
a much better way to do this is to find
a good ground
on the engine itself in other words find
a shiny metal spot on the engine
that you know is nice solid metal and
hit the ground cable up there
not to the battery itself K usually like
to look for is like a big hooks sticking
up of the top the engine something like
that
this would be the engine this is where
you would like
to have it mounted the alternator
isn't axle a place to put a cable
if you got it off so how bout rate here
part of the alternator or put that
you wanna make sure to keep it away from
any the spinning stuff
k cables are all hooked up from the good
car the battery
in a bad car and the battery and a good
engine ground now let's start a good car
for the
let the good car run for a little while
the more you intend to start the other
car
the battery time to
to charge up a little bit we'll actually
turning he and try to start the other me
in the other car is not starting
Mearns be really really dead which might
want to do it you might want to raise
the I love when the car then
is a good car and let it run into higher
I'll that will
allow the alternator to work a little
bit better in charge battery up
even more that it would just by sitting
idle alright now I'm gonna go with the
dead car
been running for a little while tried
started please please please don't
believe
like
day finally both cars running disconnect
the cables
on both cars the sooner the better your
early Mon
too long tight you want to start with
taking ground cable
of for T
low