the red and black, other end of these cables
to the car that has the good battery. The
red usually goes on the positive side of the
battery, the black usually goes on the negative
side of the battery. And we're going to hook
these two ends up to this battery to jump
start it the same way. You never cross the
wires, you always put red to positive and
black to negative. There are exceptions, those
exceptions would be mentioned in your manual.
In this case, we're going to hook the red
up first, we always hook the red up and then
the black, it eliminates the possibility of
having an explosion. Best situation is that
this battery is not too dead and we just hook
the two batteries together from the two cars
and his car just starts right up. Now in the
case where this battery is a little bit deader
than that, I might have to start my car, let
it run for a little while to charge this battery
up a little bit, and then have him try and
start his car. If the battery is worse than
that, we may have to pull the battery out
and take it some place and have it charged
and then put it back in. But the best protection
for your car, being the car that's jumping
the other car, is to leave your car turned
off so you don't run the risk of damaging
your alternator. In this situation, I'm just
going to hook the two batteries together which
I've already done and he's going to try to
start his car. My car is not running. And
his car started right up. So now we need to
disconnect it from the car once it starts,
you disconnect it just the opposite of the
way that you connected it. You disconnect
the negative first, the black in this case,
and then you disconnect the red and then you
do the same thing to the other car.