and pulled up to the car with a dead
battery so the jumper cables could reach
both batteries
wanna make sure both cars are separated
and don't touch each other when you do
this
yes or make sure that you take the keys
in the ignition for both vehicles
for each of our vehicles want to find
the battery and fine with the positive
and negative leads are this in my truck
battery this is better that works
day is the positive it's ready and then
here's the negative
its black now if we go over to our van
which is not starting
we can look at the battery it's eerie
here
black cable that's our negative and this
one is our positive it sir
red cable so once you identify that we
could begin
now you don't take a jumper cables and
spread them out to have one red one
black
any chance and just eating all the wires
here's the dead battery in our van
and will take out the jumper cables from
this point forward we don't want the
jumper cable ends to touch each other
first thing we can do is take the one
side the jumper cables we're going to
get our red
which is our positive or get attached to
the positive side the dead battery
but make sure you get a good connection
right on that battery post
you'd see that these copper pieces are
touching the metal on the post
and there's a good connection if you
want you can wiggle it around a little
bit just make sure you get it in there
good
the reason why attach the red cable to
the dead battery 1st
is because the dead battery doesn't have
as much energy as the good battery
starting here's the safest you could
take a ground and just put on a piece a
plastic
you don't want your ground touching any
bare metal was then you'll be grounding
it out images leave it there for now
we're gonna connected to the battery in
a second never gonna go over to the good
battery
we're gonna grab both early just like we
did before don't touch 'em together
we're going to take our red one and put
it on the positive terminal
which is also read at the good better
you're going to get a black leader
and we're going to attach it to our
negative side here to attach this here
now we have the black lead and the red
lead
on the good battery attached back at the
dead battery this is the last lead we
have to attach
be ongoing attached to the negative
battery terminal touching a lead to
negative battery terminal will cause a
spark
and the sparks can ignite any fumes from
the bad
re in cause an explosion batteries can
create hydrogen gas especially when the
rundown
and not working properly and hydrogen
gas is explosive
so to play it safe just find another
grounding point some cars have a ground
spot
away from the battery specifically for
jump in your car so check your owner's
manual
if not find a bear piece a metal
foreground that isn't the moving part
and is an attached to an electrical
component so when looking for a ground
you wanna try to find something that
bare metal if we look here
there's a nice ground here but
unfortunately this wires pretty thin
so if you don't have a good connection
to this ground this wires then
see could actually melted a good but the
look is on the engine when we look at
the engine here
here's a nice bear piece a metal my only
problem is their piece a metal is that
it's right next to the fuel pressure
regulator
and we're trying to avoid sparks next
anything flammable so this is a spot
that I would want to use
but it's nice because the nice thick
piece a metal its bare metal
it's directly connected to the engine
see get a good ground
in my case wanna do is I'm gonna go find
the strut tower
and as you can see a much stricter our
is a bunch a good ball to provide a good
ground
and they're also bare metal so we're
gonna tajik today the other good thing
is this stripped hours away from the
battery
so we don't have to worry about sparks
but there's tons a ground that you could
use
in this case this is just one of them
just getting here in class breakdown on
today
and make sure you have a good connection
so their cables all set up one last
thing you want to do you want to inspect
to make sure that these cables
are not near any cooling fans it's your
cooling fans over here
to not to worry about that in our
serpentine belt is on the other side
so we don't have to worry about that now
there are cables are clear this check
out the other side
moving to the good battery said the fan
is right here as well as the serpentine
belt in our cables after the way over
here
so we're ready to jump the vehicle
they're gonna start the engine in my
truck which is the good battery
and let it run for two minutes that
Matrox been running for about two
minutes so we can start the engine in my
van
hopefully it'll start up
Co
with
here we go
now right away you want to go and take
off the negative terminal first
and now if I take this off in its parks
it away from the battery which is being
charged
and potentially creating hydrogen gas
that we take off the red terminal first
we could create a spark great year which
isn't that the battery which would be
good
to remove the negative terminal first
don't let this touch anything
and no more move are positive turn on
the bad battery
Blake sure these don't touch then your
move the red cable
began in the black cable I'm
and now your car started see you not
stand it anymore pushes give a scenario
where you go to start the car and it
doesn't work
it slowly drags we don't get the car
started but the car sit for another five
minutes
but that other car that's running charge
up your battery essentially the
alternator in the other cars charging
your battery so sit for five more
minutes
take the key as ignition and in five
minutes try starting it again
if it seems like you're really close to
starting but you just need a little bit
more juice
have that person in the car with a good
battery rev up the engine to about 2,000
rpm
and hold it there as you try to start
the vehicle with the dead battery this
look at the alternator spinning faster
so you have more power to start the car
with the bad battery
I after all that if all you get is a
quick they can start your engine
your battery could be permanently bed
there could be a bad cell in there could
be sure it internally
but before you give up make sure that
you have a good connection on both the
positive
and negative terminals makes you check
the connections on the bad battery
as well as the good battery another
thing to do is if you attach it to this
ground
and it won't start the car try
connecting it to a better ground
allotted time switching to another grand
will start the car