positioned next to each other
turn the engines of and OpenFlow puts
next
carefully attach the red cables to the
positive terminals Beach battery
starting with the dead battery the
positive terminals are usually marked by
a plus sign
or colored red next attach the black
cable to the negative terminal of the
good battery the negative terminal
is usually black and marked with a minus
sign the remaining black cable should be
attached to the engine block in the car
with a dead battery
attach the cable is far from the battery
is possible
what's the cables are attached start the
engine of the car with a good battery
wait a minute or two then start the
engine at the car with the dead battery
leading both engines running
you can't disconnect the cables in the
reverse of the order which you connected
them
first the cable attached to the engine
block then the black negative cable from
the booster car
then the red positive cable from the
booster car
and finally the red positive cable from
the car you just jump start