not touching both turned off in park
and on a flat surface that the Safeway
to begin the process of getting your
battery
and get your car going here are jumper
cables there's
for connection point and I'm in a show
you the proper order in which to connect
the jumper cables notice
that the red cables are for the positive
connections
and the black handled cables are for the
negative connections look at your
batteries very closely
very easy to find the positive in
negative cables
it's either going to be marked on the
battery or with some batteries
the positive post is actually painted
read to make it easier
the for you to know that the positive
cable the black
or negative cable is
is easy really easy did to find as well
so let's begin let's connect first
to did didn't at dead car which is this
car
the dead car battery you start by
connecting the positive cable
to the positive chairman of on the dead
battery
then you connect the positive cable
to the positive post on your good
battery
next you're gonna connect the negative
cable to the
negative post on the good battery now
here's the most important thing and
where most people messed up
do not connect the negative cable
to the negative post you wanna fine
actually
a nice clean shiny Bowl are not inside
the engine compartment to connect it to
it's going to spark and that's normal
and we don't wanna
light a fire under battery so that's the
safest way to do it
so that's our connection now we're gonna
start the good car
and we're gonna let it run for a few
minutes
that's gonna charge up a little bit the
battery
on the dead car then we're gonna go
ahead and start
the dead car battery and it should
startup right away
congratulations you most likely were
able to start
the dead battery car however if you
weren't able to do it the first time
just let the two cars that connected for
a little while longer
and let that the dead battery charge a
little longer
and try again that should make you
successful
now we're going to remove our cables
we're gonna start
first bike breaking our connection by
removing
than negative cable from
our bowls then we're going to remove
than negative cable
from our good battery and then we're
going to remove our
positive cable from the dead battery