will come with to read clamps
and two black claims identify the
battery posts are both batteries
positive will have anything red
associate with the red
cover the red clamps the little positive
symbol right there
on the negative side you love black
cables
and a a little negative symbol right
there
sometimes it's very difficult to find
any coloring or any samples
one trick us look at the size the post
the positive is going to be much larger
in diameter
than the negative post it's best to know
which is which
because the hookup backwards you can
have serious electrical problems
were still as your battery discharges it
starts to emit a hydrogen gas
makes that was far and it what
you get what I'm sayin now you attach
the to read clamps
it doesn't really matter what order
because you're not getting a final
contact
notice i've wiggle the clamps
to get better contact that allowing the
black clamp touch any exposed metal
areas good plastic bumper like this is
good now you attach the black clamp
to the car that you're starting it with
on the negative post for your final
connection
and this is the one that counts wanna
find exposed metal location on your
engine
and clampett to it now
electricity will flow from the live
battery to the dead battery I recommend
you in the car with a live battery
to increase the flow of electricity in
fact
you can reading the end
faster like
hurt
I now try to start if it doesn't start
right away
it's no problem you'll just need to
spend more time waiting to charge that
dead
battery call
Paul
price target again
way yes
it okay I'll
cars running now pretty badly the cable
dangling from the front of the car that
struck down the road so I'd suggest you
disconnect the cable
starting with the last one the hookup
that your negative
plant spark is just as important this
time so make sure to let it go against
your plastic bumper
from there you can't disconnect the
cable