the first thing that you want to do is
bring a good car
up to your dead car and leave enough
space so that you can work around in it
there is a specific order that you wanna
connect these cables and to prevent
sparking and
shorting out of the cables so step one
is you going to connect wanna be read
Anza
one of the cables to the positive post
the dead battery
so here you can see it's already
connected
now you're going to move on to Step 2
which is you're going to connect the
other end of that red cable to the
positive post
be good battery
and while you're still there step three
is going to connect the
first black end of the cable onto the
negative post
above the good battery and back here on
the dead car you're going to connect the
other end of that black cable onto a
shiny metal part of the
engine block or on the middle chassis
don't connected to the battery post
because we want to prevent any possible
explosions or sparks
and here's another example here we found
a nice shiny ball sticking out to the
chassis
any of these will work
as a sanity check that you connected the
cables right you don't like should come
on on the dead car
so now let's start powering down
everything on both cars make sure that
all the lights are off on both cars
you want to unplug all of your power
port solve your cigarette lighter
adaptors
I'm
turn off your car radios on both
vehicles
if you have your air conditioner running
you wanna turn off your air conditioner
as well
I'm any radar detectors make sure those
are unplugged
and basically any device should be
unplugged including your iPods
start the engine on a good car and run
it for five minutes to charge the
battery on the dead car
C
I like to try method number one first
what we do is we try to charge the dead
car's battery 1st
and then return of the good car and see
if the decker will start on its own
specific this method to protect the
electrical system
starting vehicle
so if this fails i'd entrust starting
method number two
where you try to start the dead car with
the good cars engine running to give it
more power boost
now that you're dead car has been
resurrected you can't disconnect all the
cables