be
day when you open up and the first thing
you should do is identify the battery
positive and is Mike your ad and the
negative and is my flat that one
connector good plan to the
bad don't keep the keys
in the ignition and the dead car until
you're ready to start it that kid
connector
clamp again battery step to reconnect
the black lamp to the good battery
that port connector other black lab to
ground on the bad
higher a grounded any metal part in the
frame random
that 5 the good guy
that today
the bad
what have you been
thank you love me
ready with a black people of the bad
that he removed the block from the dead
battery
that be removed the red planet from the
dead battery