goods of vehicles open so
like I said we're gonna pretend that my
the coat is the gum that the dead
vehicle sorry
so now this just for demonstration
purposes but noticeable
batteries are on the driver side so this
actually technically won't work
but I don't feel like putting them into
and alright step 1: make sure your
vehicle is not running
either vehicle why pretty obvious
first step we use we're gonna start with
our jumper vehicle
we do not want the vehicle to be running
your life K
be positive and a jumper cable and
attach
choot ke good battery out right now
we're just gonna leave the negative and
alone
okay so now the next step is resuming
accumulate all green fuzz after I
cleaned it but anyway
the cake a positive lead on the other
end
and we attach the vehicles dead battery
now on to me get battery
we attach the negative cable make sure
these are securely fastened now in the
vehicle the dead battery
not want to hook this up to the negative
cable cuz if we do
for this crap on it may spark and
sparking hydrogen means boom
so we want is like her hair look and
there's plenty a metal on the engine
to rate here's a nice thick piece a
medal here
gonna move back and forth a little they
get a good connection
so we always run aground the
negative cable on the dead battery to a
good
solid engine ground force our body
ground some sort every down the exhaust
manifold way down there or up on top of
the engine but has to be something good
and solid metal
case in our guy come and start whose
jumper hit for and now we come over and
we start the vehicle
the dead battery the the
the