let's go over to the vehicle with a dead
battery 1st
and we woke up the Red Hills
to the positive post on the vehicle with
the
better step to go over to the vehicle
with a good battery
and though we want to make the
connection on the positive terminal
knows that there's a plastic cover here
some batteries have that make sure you
are un clip it folded all the way
so that you can make good connection
step 3:
own the vehicle with the good battery go
ahead and put the Black
cable and up to the negative post on the
battery
step number for Mike in the final
connection with your ground cable your
black table
you kn took it straight up to the
negative posts all the dead battery
although it is recommended to go
straight to a chess the Grail
so that the spark does not ignite
any acid that could be on top of the
Dead better
next we wanna cry Cup the vehicle with
the known good battered
its
and we will allow this vehicle rollover
23 medals
before you actually product price the
other being with
ok april's after few minutes a charging
let's try to crank this thing up a slip
in the start
night
vehicle fat restart now for those boys
will leave this vehicle on a it needs to
be present for at least 30 minutes or so
so the alternator
okay pros or so you have this direct
calif.-based Google do in the hospital
over
also how we looked it up who will take
the negative all
all the
dead battery be there first lay aside go
over to the vehicle with a good battery
we will disconnect the negative they
will disconnect
proselytize they will go back to the
vehicle