next position the vehicle's next to each
other then
open the hood and find where the
batteries are half you find the
batteries
look for a black or red
on the battery black is minus red
is a plus if they're is in a black or
red for a minus symbol
or a plus symbol to determine which
terminal with
the most important thing to remember
what jump starting your vehicle
is to not let the jumper cable and touch
each other first
hope the positive jumper cable and first
laying -1 to the side
then
but the negative jumper cable and to the
negative terminal
%uh
when she had jumper cables for to the
batteries
then want to start the working vehicle
and let him run
after that price starting vehicle with a
dead battery
it still wont start let the working
vehicle run for a few more minutes
right here once you get the vehicle with
the dead battery started
disconnect the jumper cables by removing
the negative and first