sonic RS convertible sir what husband
came first
I put 20
negative on a plastic parcel doesn't
fear
okay and the car needs to be posted
tonight
left positive
to someone was not touching anything
metal the
okay from a car
it's gonna be boosting the battery now
with connector
so good thorough
here
nice solid connection
okay the negative connection they say to
clamp the two
mom unpainted parlor car and
just the balanced pretty crazy haha
automatic star
and it's not hard to Madikeri
which was very weird on the side of
automatically again
so while that is strange to get into the
car
Free Edition
okay normally and a card is gonna be
boosting the other car once it starts
for a while
you raise RPM's to bar
2000 RPM's incur
and that will charge the battery
and then you go to the other car
and just simply start the car so use
possibilities for five minutes depending
on how the pleaded the battery is
song let's go to the Acura
of
and now you wanna travel accessories
radios going to be a problem
them through the cold
from Nova the car started you can unplug
the other battered
Co