all right so you want to take your
cables
keeping them separated from each other
at both ends of your cable.
red one's gonna go on positive.
lot of times your battery will have a little
plus mark on it
which indicates positive. or it may have a
red
cable terminal which indicates positive and
then you have your black
which goes on negative. as you can see there's
a negative
sign there and a black cable as well on
the battery's side.
make sure you're keeping all your cables
separate from each other so they don't
spark
which can be a problem. anyhow so
that's how we're hooking up our
batteries and we're keeping everything
separated. red and black. postitive and negative.
kee these separated.
so notice again this is a different
style of battery.
it's what we call a top post. our
other vehicle had a side post. but again
you see a plus mark.
you see red here. if you
come across a vehicle and you're
just not sure
the negative and positive post are two
different sizes.
the positive post is a bit larger. the
round post here.
the negative is a little bit smaller
than the postive. so that's another way
you can identify positive and negative
on a battery.
so again keeping our cables separate
we're making good contact.
see i just made a mistake. that's
black.
there's your negative black. postive
red. that could've caused a
little bit of a problem.
wouldn't have blown you up but it definitely
could cause a problem.
that's the reason why I don't have
my two cables connected just yet.
I've got everything right now and now
I'm gonna do my last connection between
the two cables.
so as you can see I got my
cables completely separate from each
other. I'm gonna bring my red to my red.
positive to positive. I'm gonna make good contact
here.
notice you get one side as your cable.
so I'm gonna make sure to get both cable
sides touching each other.
see the cable side. they're all
touching in the middle.
so that's a better contact.
cable side. cable side.
so now we have a good
contact and let it run for a little while
to charge it up. then we fire up the vehicle.
black-on-black.
well because the length that the electricity has to travel
we're gonna give it a minute to
charge the dead battery.
you can tell if your battery
alternator is charging on the running car
you can usually hear
a little bit of a high pitched noise and
that means that your alternator
is definitely charging and your connection
are good. you hear that high pitched whining
from your alternator
because it's actually charging a little extra than
normal.
we let it run for a minute and then
we'll
go ahead and fire up the Honda. the vehicle in the
back is a big V8.
so it has a higher charging rate. so the smaller
Honda
shouldn't take that much to start
up. so we'll give it a minute and then start up.
well it's running. I'm gonna carefully
disconnect the cables.
make sure to keep the red and the
black
the positive and negative terminals
separated from each other.