you will notice we have our cars parked head to heda not touching. both turned off in park
and on a flat surface. that is the Safe way
to begin the process of getting your
battery
and get your car going. here are jumper
cables. there's
four connection points and I'm gonna show
you the proper order in which to connect
the jumper cables. notice
that the red cables are for the positive
connections
and the black handled cables are for the
negative connections. look at your
batteries very closely.
very easy to find the positive and
negative cables.
it's either going to be marked on the
battery or with some batteries
the positive post is actually painted
red to make it easier
for you to know that that is the positive
cable. the black
or negative cable is
really easy did to find as well.
so let's begin. let's connect first
to the dead car which is this
car.
the dead car battery you start by
connecting the positive cable
to the positive terminal on the dead
battery.
then you connect the positive cable
to the positive post on your good
battery.
next you're gonna connect the negative
cable to the
negative post on the good battery. now
here's the most important thing and
where most people mess up.
do not connect the negative cable
to the negative post. you wanna find
actually
a nice clean shiny bolt or nut inside
the engine compartment to connect it to.
it's going to spark and that's normal
and we don't wanna
light a fire on our battery so that's the
safest way to do it.
so that's our connection. now we're gonna
start the good car
and we're gonna let it run for a few
minutes.
that's gonna charge up a little bit the
battery
on the dead car. then we're gonna go
ahead and start
the dead car battery and it should
startup right away.
congratulations. you most likely were
able to start
the dead battery car. however if you
weren't able to do it the first time
just let the two cars sit connected for
a little while longer
and let that the dead battery charge a
little longer
and try again. that should make you
successful.
now we're going to remove our cables.
we're gonna start
first by breaking our connection by
removing
the negative cable from
our bolt. then we're going to remove
the negative cable
from our good battery and then we're
going to remove our
positive cable from the dead battery and finally the positive cable from the good battery.