you want to put the positive jumper
cable
on the dead battery. go over to
your car
with the good battery and put on your
positive cable here. then go
with your negative cable
on your good battery and then
well take your negative cable for the bad
battery and apply it to a ground.
the body of the vehicle or the engine.
something that is gonna be grounded
other than the battery terminal. at that
point you are gonna wanna start the car with the
good battery.
rev it up a little bit and let it run for a few
minutes and then go ahead and give it a
crank on the bad battery side.
alright so we got the car with the good battery
running. Paul is gonna get in and rev it to about
2500 rpm. We are gonna let it sit like
that for
10-15 seconds. I am going to go to the
car with the faulty battery
and crank it over.
right now I am go ahead and crank over
this car.
so we got the car running. we are gonna reverse
the process
with the
jumper cables.
negative
positive and positive.