so we are gonna start by connecting the positive end of the
cable
to the positive post of the dead
battery. then we will connect
this positive end to the positive post
on the live battery.
now for the negative. you wanna connect negative
to negative.
so take the black end the negative end.
connect this
to the negative terminal on the live
battery
and then the negative cable here
to the post on the dead battery. now as an
option
you can connect this the negative end
to either the engine block or the frame
of the car. so is it really that important
to
connect the cables in that exact order.
you're full of questions today aren't
you.
actually you're asking great questions.
it is important to connect positive to
positive and
negative to negative. because the battery's
current is designed to only flow in one
direction.
if that current is interrupted we could
have a battery explosion.
I wouldn't want that. the reason we
can connect the negative end of the cable
to the cars engine block or the frame on
the car with the dead battery
is because this helps keep the positive and
negative cable separated
and maximize the chance of effective
grounding. now we've got the car separated
and i think we're ready to start the car with
the live battery.
why do you have to start this car first.
well that's a good question.
by starting the car with the live
battery first creates
a more efficient flow of current and the
alternator of this car
is already recharging the battery here
so that the flow to the car with the dead
battery
is going to be stronger that if we did
not have this car running.
now we've got the cables connected
properly and the live car running
we need to let this situation sit for just a
couple of minutes.
let the current flow from the good
battery into the bad.
couple of minutes should do it.
done.
okay I think you're ready to start the
car
with the dead battery.
okay we've got the car with the dead
battery started. now we can remove the cables.
you want to do that in the reverse order. so we start by
removing the negative.
then we move on to the positive cables.
make sure when you're removing the cables
that none of the ends touch.
that could result in a spark or maybe even a
fire.