We're going to connect one end of the red jumper cable to the
positive terminal on the stalled
battery. red on dead. Now we're going to move up to the good
battery and connect the other red
cable clamp to the positive terminal on
the good battery. now it's time to
move on to the black jumper cable clamps.
we are staying on the good battery. the jumper
car.
as you want to connect one end of the black
jumper cable to the negative terminal
on the good battery. now you might be tempted
to just connect
the black jumper cable to the negative
terminal on the dead battery
but most experts agree to not do this.
there's a chance you could cause a spark and an
explosion.
probably won't happen but better safe
than sorry. so what we want to do instead is
is connect the other black cable
to a clean unpainted metal surface under
the disabled car's hood.
the car's engine block is a good place or
somewhere along the frame
the car which is what I did. now what
you wanna do now is
start the car that's doing the jumping and
allow it to run for 2-3 minutes before
starting the dead car.
basically charging up the dead car's
battery. and now
turn the ignition on the dead car and
the car should start. well done.
you jump started a car. now what we need
to do is remove the cables in reverse
order
of how we connected them. so we start of with
the black cable
on the former dead battery's car. remove it
from that piece of metal
that you clamped it to. then we move back over to
the jumping car.
remove the black cable from the negative
terminal on the good battery.
we go to the Red cable on the good car.
remove that from that positive terminal.
go back to our formerly dead car and remove the red jumper cable from that positive terminal.