get the hoods of both vehicles open. so
like I said we're gonna pretend that my
decota is the dead
vehicle.
so now this is just for demonstration
purposes but notice that both
batteries are on the driver side. so this
actually technically won't work.
but I don't feel like putting them end to end. alright step 1: make sure your
vehicle is not running.
either vehicle. well that's pretty obvious.
first step. we're gonna start with
our jumper vehicle.
we do not want the vehicle to be running.
we're gonna take the
positive end of the jumper cable and
attach
it to the good battery. now right now
we're just gonna leave the negative end
alone.
okay so now the next step.
we take the positive lead on the other
end
and we attach it to the vehicles dead battery.
now on the good battery
we attach the negative cable. make sure
these are securely fastened. now on the
vehicle with the dead battery
we do not want to hook this up to the negative
cable. because if we do
we put this clamp on it may spark and
sparking hydrogen means boom.
so what we want is we want to come here and look and
there's plenty of metal on the engine.
right here's a nice thick piece of
metal here.
you're gonna move it back and forth a little bit.
get a good connection.
so we always want the ground the
negative cable on the dead battery to a
good
solid engine ground or body
ground of some sort. down the exhaust
manifold way down there or up on top of
the engine but it has to be something good
and solid metal.
so now we're gonna come and start the
jumper vehicle. now we come over and
we start the vehicle
with the dead battery.