jump-starting a car is not difficult but
can be dangerous if not done properly.
it's really important you follow the
right procedure. just stay safe. Park the cars
in a safe place
and make sure that the not touching. nose to nose works best
as jumper cables are not very long. check
that both cars are in park or neutral
and that the hand brakes are on. then
switch off the engine of the donor car.
open the bonnet of each car and locate
the batteries.
make sure that both batteries are 12 volts. if
you're not sure
don't attempt to jump-start the car
yourself. the batteries have a positive
terminal and a negative terminal.
the positive terminal is red with a
positive symbol
and the negative terminal is black with
a negative symbol.
if you can't see these you may need to wipe away some of the road grind and battery acid with a cloth.
now battery acid is pretty nasty
stuff so avoid getting it on you
and throw away the cloth right away. first
connect the red jumper lead to the
positive red terminal
at the flat battery and then attach the
clip on the other end of the lead
to the positive red terminal at the
donor battery. then connect the black
jumper lead to the negative black
terminal at the donor vehicle
before attaching the free end of the cable
to a solid metal part of the car with a
flat battery
such as the top suspension mount. don't
connect the cable to any moving part
and ensure that the cables are well clear of the
exhaust or drive belts.
an easy way to remember what color goes
where is to think of red
as a bright happy positive color and
black as a negative color.
start the engine of the donor vehicle and
let it run for a few minutes
at about
two thousand revs a minute. then start the
engine of the car with the flat
battery.
allow the engine to fast idle for a minimum of
two minutes before disconnecting
the jumper leads.
now carefully remove the jumper leads in
the reverse order to the connection starting with the one connected to the car body.