take your positive jumper cable. connect it to your positive terminal of the dead battery.
after connecting the positive cable to the
positive terminal
of the dead battery you're going to
connect the positive cable
to the positive terminal of the charged
battery. you will then connect the
negative cable which is black
to the negative terminal of the charged
battery.
then you'll connect the negative
cable
to either your engine block or in this
case we can connect
it there to the frame. perfect.
I would let it sit there for about 3 to
4 minutes
and then try and turn your car over. now
once the car turns over
you want to reverse the process. so you
would take the negative
cable from the frame. then you would take
the negative cable
from the charged battery. then take the
positive cable
off from the charge battery which is the red
one and then take the positive
cable off of the positive terminal from the dead battery.