you are gonna start with your good vehicle. the vehicle with the good battery.
we're gonna hook up our positive cable.
we're going to use the red color code
sor positive.
get a good clamp on our positive
cable here
and then on our negative cable here.
now at this point our cables are live. so we wanna
make sure
that we don't touch it. when you come to
the vehicle with the dead battery what's
gonna happen is
when you make this connection it'll
generate spark.
that's why we wanna keep the spark away from the
battery. so we wanna start here
the positive side hook up here.
then we want to find a good point
somewhere away from the battery
that's metal and will give us a good ground.
the other thing you need to be aware of
is where the belt is where the pulleys
are going to be turning. you don't want
to create
an interference with your cables and
the running vehicle.
so at this point okayour cables are hooked up. we got
the battery hooked up on the good
vehicle. we got positive cable on the dead
battery
and a good ground point away from the
battery. now we're gonna start our
donor car. make sure that all the accessories are turned off
so that the battery and the alternator can be dedicated
to charging up the new car.
if it's really dead you can let the vehicles run for a minute.
that'll help charge the vehicle battery from the alternator.
there you have it. now when you disconnect you want to do it in the exact reverse order.
we get our ground cable off. disconnect our
positive
from the dead battery. make sure we keep those
separated. then we disconnect our good vehicle.