okay step 1: this is our car with the dead
battery and this is the car with the dead
battery.
you need to park them as close together
as you can but without either of them touching
because that could cause a spark.
turn the ignition off in both cars. first off
remove the battery cover.
you're looking for the positive terminal first. it is usually marked
red like this one here or have a
little plus sign. you connect the
red jump lead to the positive battery
terminal on the dead car.
step 2 connect the other end of the red
jump lead to the positive
terminal on the good car. on this car the
positive terminal isn't
colored red but it does have a plus
sign here. so we
know that's the right one. step 3:
connect the black jump lead
to the negative terminal on the donor
car.
step four. connect the other end of the black
jump lead to an Earth point
on the dead car.
step five. leave the jumper cables connected
for about three minutes
so that the battery voltages can equalize. make sure
that the cables
are moved well away from anything moving in
the engine as well.
make sure you remove the battery cover
at the engine compartment.
step 6: started the donor car and allow it to run for a
minute.
then while it is still running start the
dead car and leave both running for about
10 minutes.
don't remove the jump leads once the cars
engines are running.
step 7. turn the ignition on both cars off
and remove the clamps in the reverse order
that you put them on.