your typical jumper cables will come with two red clamps
and two black clamps. identify the
battery posts on both batteries.
positive will have anything red
associated with it. the red
cover the red clamps the little positive
symbol right there.
on the negative side you'll have black
cables
and a little negative symbol right
there.
sometimes it's very difficult to find
any coloring or any symbol.
one trick is to look at the size of the post.
the positive is going to be much larger
in diameter
than the negative post. it's best to know
which is which
because if you hook them up backwards you can
have serious electrical problems.
worse still as your battery discharges it
starts to emit a hydrogen gas.
mix that with spark and boom.
you get what I'm sayin. now you attach
the two red clamps.
it doesn't really matter what order
because you're not getting a final
contact.
notice i wiggle the clamps
to get better contact. without allowing the
black clamp touch any exposed metal
areas. good plastic bumper like this is
good. now you attach the black clamp
to the car that you're starting it with
on the negative post. for your final
connection
and this is the one that counts you wanna
find an exposed metal location on your
engine
and clamp it to it. now
electricity will flow from the live
battery to the dead battery. I recommend
you run the car with the live battery
to increase the flow of electricity. in
fact
you can rev the engine
for a faster flow of electricity.
now try to start it. if it doesn't start
right away
it's no problem. you'll just need to
spend more time waiting to charge that
dead
battery.
try starting it again.
your car is running now. pretty bad to leave the cables
dangling from the front of the car as
you drive down the road so I'd suggest you
disconnect the cables.
starting with the last one that you hooked up.
that's your negative
clamp. spark is just as important at this
time so make sure to let it go against
your plastic bumper.
from there you then disconnect the
cable on the car that started it followed by the two red cables.