A very important note is that you
never does this to a damaged battery.
your first step is to get another vehicle with a
working battery
and park them next to each other so the batteries
are near each other so that you can reach them
with the jumper cables.
the next step is to get yourself a nice set of
jumper cables so you can properly jump
the vehicles.
first you hook up the red positive side to the
dead battery.
then you do the red positive side on the
good battery. then you do the black
negative on the good battery. then
you take the black from the dead
battery and hook it up on some kind of
ground on the engine.
it's best to hook up the ground as far away from the battery as possible so you don't overload
the circuit.
first try to start the dead vehicle like this
because sometimes
it's not dead dead and you will still be able
to start it like this.
if that doesn't work start the vehicle with the good battery and let it charge the dead
battery for a few minutes before you
start
that one.
once the good vehicle's started you want to let it run for a little while to charge up the dead
battery before attempting to start the other
car.
when you are unhooking the cables you do them
in the reverse order that you hooked them up in.
be sure to not to touch the cable
ends together.