line up the hood of the working car as
close as possible to the one with the dead
battery
but make sure they're not touching. next
turn off both cars and put them on park. also turn
off and unplug
anything in either car that runs on the
battery like headlamp
radio air conditioning and everything
plugged into the power outlet
like mp3 players or cellphones. okay
best really important.
if either battery is cracked or leaking do not
attach the jumper cables to it.
the battery could explode and spray acid all over you.
not pretty. now locate the positive and
negative terminals
to the batteries. conveniently enough every
battery is labeled.
so you shouldn't have too much trouble
determining which is which.
if you don't see the markings it's
probably because the battery terminals
are dirty.
just wipe off any corrosion or battery
acid near the terminals
with a rag. now
you're ready to connect the cables.
here is an easy way to remember how to
connect them. you're looking for a
positive outcome to the situation.
so you want the highest number
of positive connections possible.
as for the cable themselves the positive
cable
is usually red and the negative cable is
usually black. but
not all jumper cables are color-coded the
same way. so read the instructions that
came with them before you start. attach
the positive cable
to the positive battery terminal in the
car with a dead battery first.
then connect the other end of the
positive cable
to the positive battery terminal on the
working car.
next connect the negative cable to the
negative battery terminal
of the working car.
then find a solid metal part on the
engine
on the dead car to attach the other end
of the negative cable to. make sure it's
not a part of the battery
and that it isn't painted.
it should be a clean shiny metal like
a nut on the engine block.
if it is dirty or oily clean it up first.
when you connect the negative cable don't worry if there's a spark.
it is
normal. just think of it as a replacement
for your morning coffee.
now that the cables are set up
you're ready to start jumping. first turn
on the good cars engine
and let it run for a minute or two
before you try to start the dead battery.
if you wanna check that you have the
cable setup correctly
turn on the dome light in the dead car. if
it comes on
the cable are right. now you can try
turning on the dead car.
if the engine sounds like it is trying to
crank but won't turn over completely
give it a few more minutes and then rev
the engine a bit
on the good car. once the engine in the
dead car turns over
you can remove the cables. be sure to
leave the engine running though.
it takes a while for the battery to
fully recharge.
when you remove the cables be careful
not to let the clamps touch each other
or you could be in for quite a shock.
disconnect the cables in the opposite order than you connected them in.