so the first step is to get a car that runs and pull it up to the car with the dead battery so the jumper cables could reach
both batteries.
you wanna make sure both cars are separated
and don't touch each other when you do
this.
you also wanna make sure that you take the keys
out of the ignition for both vehicles.
for each of our vehicles you want to find
the battery and find where the positive
and negative leads are. this in my truck
battery. this is the battery that works.
so here is the positive. it's red and then
here's the negative
it's black. now if we go over to our van
which is not starting
we can look at the battery. you can see right
here
black cable. that's our negative and this
one is our positive it's the
red cable. so once you identify that we
could begin.
now you want to take your jumper cables and
spread them out to have one red one
black
in each hand and just detangle the wires.
here's the dead battery in our van
and we'll take out the jumper cables. from
this point forward we don't want the
jumper cable ends to touch each other.
first thing we are gonna do is take one
side of the jumper cables. we're going to
get our red
which is our positive and we are gonna attach it to
the positive side of the dead battery.
make sure you get a good connection
right on that battery post.
you can see that these copper pieces are
touching the metal on the post
and there's a good connection. if you
want you can wiggle it around a little
bit. just make sure you get it in there
good.
the reason why you attach the red cable to
the dead battery first
is because the dead battery doesn't have
as much energy as the good battery.
so starting here's the safest. you could
take your ground and just put it on a piece of
plastic.
you don't want your ground touching any
bare metal. then you'll be grounding
it out. we'll leave it there for now.
we're gonna connect it to the battery in
a second. now we are gonna go over to the good
battery.
we're gonna grab both of our leads just like we
did before. don't touch 'em together.
we're going to take our red one and put
it on the positive terminal
which is also red. at the good battery
you're going to get the black lead
and we're going to attach it to our
negative side here. so attach this here.
now we have the black lead and the red
lead
on the good battery attached. back at the
dead battery this is the last lead we
have to attach.
but you are not going to attach it to the negative
battery terminal. touching a lead to
negative battery terminal will cause a
spark.
these sparks can ignite any fumes from
the battery
and cause an explosion. batteries can
create hydrogen gas especially when they
rundown
and are not working properly and hydrogen
gas is explosive.
so to play it safe just find another
grounding point. some cars have a ground
spot
away from the battery specifically for
jumping your car. so check your owner's
manual.
if not find a bare piece of metal
for the ground that isn't a moving part
and is not attached to an electrical
component. so when looking for a ground
you wanna try to find something that
is bare metal. if we look here
there's a nice ground here but
unfortunately this wire is pretty thin.
so if you don't have a good connection
to this ground this wire is thin
so you could actually melt it. a good spot to
look is on the engine. we are looking at
the engine here.
here's a nice bare piece of metal. my only
problem with this piece of metal is that
it's right next to the fuel pressure
regulator.
we're trying to avoid sparks next to
anything flammable. so this isn't a spot
that I would want to use.
but it's nice because it's a nice thick
piece of metal. its bare metal.
it's directly connected to the engine
so you get a good ground.
in my case what i am gonna do is I'm gonna go find
the strut tower.
as you can see on my strut tower there
is a bunch of good bolts that provide a good
ground
and they're also bare metal. so we're
gonna attach it to that. the other good thing
is this strut tower is away from the
battery
so we don't have to worry about sparks.
but there's tons of grounds that you could
use.
in this case this is just one of them.
just get in here and clamp right down on
to that.
make sure you have a good connection.
so with our cables all set up one last
thing you want to do is you want to inspect
to make sure that these cables
are not near any cooling fans. you can see our
cooling fans are over here
so we don't have to worry about that. our
serpentine belt is on the other side
so we don't have to worry about that. now
that our cables are clear lets check
out the other side.
moving to the good battery side the fan
is right here as well as the serpentine
belt and our cables are out of the way over
here.
so we're ready to jump the vehicle.
now we're gonna start the engine in my
truck which is the good battery
and let it run for two minutes.
my truck has been running for about two
minutes so we can start the engine in my
van.
hopefully it'll start up.
there we go.
now right away you want to go and take
off the negative terminal first.
and now if I take this off and it sparks
it is away from the battery which is being
charged
and potentially creating hydrogen gas.
if we take off the red terminal first
we could create a spark right here which
is on top of the battery which wouldn't be
good.
so we remove the negative terminal first.
don't let this touch anything.
then we remove our positive terminal on
the bad battery.
make sure these don't touch. then you
remove the red cable
and then the black cable.
now your car started so you are not
stranded anymore. so let's just give a scenario
where you go to start your car and it
doesn't work.
it slowly drags but we don't get the car
started. let the car sit for another five
minutes.
let that other car that's running charge
up your battery. essentially the
alternator in the other car is charging
your battery so sit for five more
minutes.
take the key out of the ignition and in five
minutes try starting it again.
if it seems like you're really close to
starting but you just need a little bit
more juice
have that person in the car with the good
battery rev up the engine to about 2a000
rpms
and hold it there as you try to start
the vehicle with the dead battery. this
will get the alternator spinning faster
so you will have more power to start the car
with the bad battery.
after all that if all you get is a
click and you can't start your engine
your battery could be permanently bad.
there could be a bad cell in there, there could
be a shortage internally.
but before you give up make sure that
you have a good connection on both the
positive
and negative terminals. make sure you check
the connections on the bad battery
as well as the good battery. another
thing to do is if you attach it to this
ground
and it won't start the car try
connecting it to a better ground.
a lot of times switching to another ground
will start the car.