the first connection is the positive jump lead. it should first go
on the donor vehicle. that should connect to
the positive terminal.
you can now carefully take this over and connect this to the positive
terminal
of the casuality vehicle. next is
the negative and again
the first connection we make is to the
negative terminal of the
donor vehicle. be very careful
with the negative jump lead.
this needs to go on an earthing
point on the car. now this could be
a clean bit of metal on the engine or a clean bit of metal on the chassis
but it doesn't want to go directly onto
the battery itself.
when you connecting it also
consider and be careful that you don't
connect it to
near the battery or any fuel
componentson the car.
so there's a nice clean bit of metal here that
we could connect
and then straight onto the battery. now those leads are connected
we need to wait at least three minutes
for the voltage to stabilise between
the cars.
now that the leads have been connected and
left for a few minutes
we can now start the donor vehicle.
we should leave the donor vehicle running
for a few minutes and then start the
casualty vehicle.
we should leave them both running
for about 15 minutes to let the battery
voltages equalize.
if during those fifteen minutes the leads
start getting warm
or start getting hot you should turn off both vehicles and disconnect the leads.
whatever you do don't disconnect the leads while the
vehicles are running
as this can cause serious damage to
the car.
so we start with the negative terminal
which is placed on the engine
of the casualty vehicle and we
disconnect that being careful
and disconnect it from the donor vehicle.
once disconnected the negative we
can then move on to the positive
and again be careful when you disconnect
them not to touch any metal work and disconnect the donor vehicle as well.