Park both cars in neutral next to each
other so they are close but not touching.
and put the handbrakes on. you don't
want them to roll away.
next you should pop open both car bonnets
and secure them.
then check that the jump leads can reach
from one car battery to the other.
stand over by the car with a good
battery.
the red jump lead is the positive lead. so
find the positive terminal
on the working battery. now this should
have some kind of a plus Symbol
or will have a red cap or red markings.
connect to this terminal using the click
at the end of the read jump lead.
check that the teeth gripped the
terminal properly. then go back to the
car with the flat battery and connect the
other end
of this red jump lead to the positive terminal
on the flat battery. you then need to
switch back to the car with the good
battery.
pick up the black jump lead and connect
it to the negative terminal which should
have a minus symbol
or a black cap. now this is the tricky
bit to remember.
with the other end of the black jump lead
move back to the car with the dead battery.
this time instead of connecting it to
the negative terminal you will need to find a
solid piece of metal
on the engine like a bolt or a bracket.
double-checking that its
firmly attached. this earthing point has
to be away from the fuel system
and the battery. some cars even have a
specific earthing rod for this purpose.
check your hand book to find out if yours does.
that should be all four ends to the jump leads
properly connected.
now once all the jump leads are hooked up wait
a few minutes for the voltages to
equalize.
once you have waited for a bit you'll then need
to start the engine of the healthy car.
leave this engine running and then try and start
the engine of the car which had the flat battery.
if it doesn't work wait a bit longer with
the engine of the other car still
running before trying to start the
engine again.
if the engine does start then leave both
cars running for ten minutes.
now if you notice that the jump leads
are getting a bit hot then you need to
turn the engines off to let them cool
down a bit.
after the 10 minutes are up the next step is to
turn off both the car engines.
then in reverse order you need to
carefully remove
each of the jump leads. be really careful
not to touch the clips against each
other
or make contact with any of the metal
such as the car's bodywork.
otherwise you will cause a bit of a bang. start
by carefully unclipping the black
jump lead from the earthing point. then
unclick the other negative end of the same
lead.
do the same with the red jump lead
unclipping it from the positive terminals
of the donor car and then the newly charged car.