so on the car that's gonna be the booster you wanna connect the positive cable first.
I put the
negative on a plastic part so it doesn't
interfere.
okay and now on the car needs to be boosted
now you connect
the positive.
put this somewhere it is not touching anything
metal.
okay on the car
that's gonna be boosting the battery now
we connect the negative terminal.
nice solid connection.
okay the negative connection they say to
clamp it to
an unpainted part of the car.
that is pretty crazy. this car has
automatic start.
and it started automatically.
which was very weird. it started
automatically again.
wow. that is strange. i'm going to get into the
car.
okay normally on the car that is gonna be
boosting the other car once it starts
for a while
you raise the RPM's to about
2000 RPM's.
that will charge the battery.
then you go to the other car
and just simply start the car. so you
are supposed to do this for five minutes depending
on how the depleted the battery is.
so let's go to the Acura.
now you wanna turn off all accessories.
radio is going to be a problem.
you've to enter the code.
now that the car has started you can unplug
the other battery.
so now you do everything in reverse order.