position the vehicle's next to each
other. then
open the hood and find where the
batteries are. after you find the
batteries
look for a black or red
on the battery. black is minus. red
is plus. if there isn't a black or
red look for a minus symbol
or a plus symbol to determine which
terminal is which.
the most important thing to remember
while jump starting your vehicle
is to not let the jumper cable ends touch
each other. first
hook the positive jumper cable end first
laying the negative one to the side.
then
hook the negative jumper cable ends to the
negative terminal.
once you have the jumper cables hooked to the
batteries
you then want to start the working vehicle
and let it run for a few minutes.
after that try starting the vehicle with the
dead battery.
if it still wont start let the working
vehicle run for a few more minutes
and try again. once you get the vehicle with
the dead battery started
disconnect the jumper cables by removing
the negative end first and then the positive.