Ideally, that means hood to hood with a few
inches in between. Step 2. Turn off both engines.
Never light a match or smoke near a car battery.
The battery contains hydrogen, a highly explosive
gas. Step 3. Open the hoods of both cars.
Step 4. Identify the positive and negatives
terminals on both car batteries. They will
be labeled with a plus sign for positive and
minus sign for negative. Step 5. Connect one
of the red clamps on the jumper cables to
the positive terminal on the dead battery.
Step 6. Connect the other red clamp to the
positive terminal on the working car's battery.
Step 7. Connect the black clamp on the jumper
cables to the negative terminal on the working
car's battery. Step 8. Clip the remaining
black clamp to a clean metal part of the dead
car's engine to ground the circuit. Step
9. Attempt to start the dead car. If it doesn't
start, disconnect the jumper cables in the
reverse order: first the black clamps (starting
with the once-dead car), then the red clamps
(starting with the working car). Start the
engine of the working car and allow it to
run for about five minutes to boost its battery.
Step 10. Turn off the working car and again
attempt to jump the dead car by connecting
the cables in order and starting the