take your keys out of the ignition to prevent damage to
your car's computer. get your booster
cables ready
noting that there's black and red
terminals. the first connection
is to the red terminal of the dead car's
battery. that's the red caps terminal on
the dead car. move over to the good car. we put
the red
connection clamp on the red terminal.
positive of the battery.
then the black clamp on the negative
terminal of the battery.
make sure that they are good and
secure before we make our final
connection. move
over to the dead car and we put our final
connection on the engine
to a good metal surface. make sure
it's away from the battery
so you don't cause a spark which would cause
the batteries to explore.