you will need a set of jumper cables, another car, safety glasses, rubber gloves,
and a wire brush.
step 1: setup. lift up your hood and find
your battery.
it's usually in plain sight at the front
of the engine compartment.
but check your owner's manual for the
exact location in your vehicle.
step two.
safety first. put on your safety glasses
and gloves to protect you from any
corrosion on the battery.
step 3: positive ID.
your battery has two terminals. a
positive
and a negative. the positive terminal is
marked with a plus sign.
the negative is marked with a minus
sign.
step 4: a friend in need. now you will
need to find a good samaritan
or friend who will be willing to give you
the gift of life. it only takes a minute
and won't harm the other person's car one
bit. step 5: power-hungry.
have the other car pull up close to your
car so the batteries are near each other.
turn both cars off. open the jumper car's
hood
and locate the battery. step 6:
hook me up. attach one end of the jumper
cable to the positive terminal of the
dead car
and the other end to the positive
terminal of the car that will do the
jumping.
then attach the other clip to the
negative terminal of the car
donating the juice and attach the other
end to the engine block of the dead car.
step 7 the juice is loose.
start the car that is giving the jump.
never run a car in a closed space or sealed
garage.
wait a few minutes then start the car
with the dead battery.
if it doesn't work leave the jumper car going.
wait five minutes
then try again. if it doesn't work
you may have a more serious problem and
could need a tow. once your car's
running
don't turn it off as engine needs time
to recharge your battery.
step eight.
on your own. remove the cables in the
reverse order you attached them.
remove the cable on the engine block. then
the negative on the donor car.
remove the positive connection on the
jumper car.
then the positive connection on the used
to be dead car.
close the hood.