so this is our dead car and this is our
donor car. it's important to get them
parked beside each other but make sure
they're not touching and ensure that
ignition is off in both cars.
so depending on your car make and model
there might be color identifiers
to indicate whether it's the positive or the
negative terminal of the battery.
so you're going to connect the red cable to the
positive terminal of the dead car.
then you're going to connect the
opposite end of the red cable
to the positive terminal on the donor
car.
so next I'm gonna place the black cable
on the negative terminal of the donor
car. lastly I'm gonna place the
other end of the black cable
on an unpainted earthed point on the dead
car.
now once you have the cables connected
to both cars leave it for about three
minutes. that allows
the voltage of the batteries to equalize
between the cars.
in that time it's a good idea just to
make sure that the cables are
outside the engine bay and not near any
of the moving parts. after the three minutes
start the engine of the donor card and let
ir run for a few minutes before
starting the engine of the dead car.
so start the engine of the dead car.
once that's started let both cars run the engines for ten
minutes. make sure you turn off the
ignition in both cars before removing
the clips.
the clips will be removed in the reverse
order that they were placed initially.
so firstly remove the black cable from
the earthing point on the dead car. next
we're gonna remove the other end of the
black cable from
the donor car. so third I'm going to
remove the red cable
from the donor car and finally I'm
gonna remove the red cable from the dead
car.
once the cables are removed from the car
you can start the engine in your dead
car.