To properly jump start your car, the first
thing you want to do is park the
working vehicle close to the one that needs
to be jumped, but don't let
them touch. Next, shut off the ignition on
both cars. Be sure to turn off
your lights, radio, and anything else that
can drain power.
To connect the jumper cables, connect the
red positive clamp to the dead
battery's positive post. You'll see a plus
on the battery. Connect the
other red clamp to the good battery. Make
sure the cables don't dangle into
either engine compartment, where they can
get tangled onto moving parts.
Now, connect the black negative clamp to the
working vehicle's negative
battery terminal. Once set, connect the other
negative cable to any
unpainted metal surface on the engine of the
dead car. Do a final check to
make sure the cables are set and not near
any moving engine parts.
Now, start the working car. Let it idle a
few minutes to feed juice to the
dead battery. When you think it's got enough
charge, start the dead vehicle
and let them idle together. Once the dead
car is running smoothly,
disconnect the cables in reverse order. Be
careful not to let the dangling