when you open the hood the first thing
you should do is identify the battery.
positive end is marked red and the
negative end is marked black. step one.
connect the red clamp to the
bad battery. don't keep the keys
in the ignition of the dead car until
you're ready to start it. step two.
connect
the red clamp to the good battery. step three. connect
the black clamp to the good battery.
step four. connect the other black clamp to
ground on the bad
battery. a ground is any metal part of the
frame or the engine.
step five. start the good car.
step six.
start the bad car.
once you have
your vehicle up and running you disconnect your cables in the exact opposite order.
starting with the black cable of the bad car.
step two. remove the black clamp from the good
battery.
step three. remove the red clamp from the
good battery. lastly the red cable off of the bad car.