firstly check a flat battery for any
signs of damage
such as cracks or leaks.
never try to jumpstart a car
with a damaged battery as there can be a risk
of explosion
or fire. now we need a fully charge car
to take power from.
cars can be jump-started from
any other car with the same voltage
battery fitted.
most European cars operate a 12-volt
system. so check that both the flat and
the charged batteries
match. ideally the charge should come from
a similar or larger powered car. locate the
battery position
on both cars. then Park the fully charged
car opposite
to the dead car allowing a walking gap
between them
and turn off the engine. we now connect
the batteries together
using the jump leads which must be done
in this order.
connect one of the red
cable ends to the positive terminal on
the dead battery.
this will be identified with a plus sign
and is often red in color. connect the
opposite end
of the red cable to the positive
terminal on the charged battery.
attach the blacks cable to the negative
terminal
on the charged battery marked with a minus sign.
finally the opposite end
of the black cable to the negative
terminal
on the dead battery. in some instances
this can be
connected to any metal point in the
car's
engine bay. ensure that the cable
ends are kept apart during this process.
ensure that all electrical items
within each car are switched off such
as
lights heaters and radios. this makes it
easier to start the car by using less
power.
start the fully charged car
and let it run for three to five minutes
revving the engine as you do so.
now attempt to start the car with the flat battery.
it should start straight away. if not
leave the cars connected for a few
more minutes
allowing the charge to build up before trying
again.
once the car has been started remove
the leads in the reverse sequence. take off
the negative on the flat battery followed
by negative on the charged battery. then
the positive on charged battery
and finally positive on the flat battery.