let's go over to the vehicle with the dead
battery 1st
and we will hook up the red end
to the positive post on the vehicle with
the
dead battery. step two. go over to the vehicle
with the good battery
and we want to make the
connection on the positive terminal.
note that there's a plastic cover here.
some batteries have that. make sure you
unclip it and fold it out of the way
so that you can make a good connection.
step 3:
on the vehicle with the good battery go
ahead and hook the Black
cable end up to the negative post on the
battery.
step number four. making the final
connection with your ground cable. your
black cable.
you can hook it straight up to the
negative post of the dead battery
although it is recommended to go
straight to a chassis ground
so that a spark does not ignite
any acid that could be on top of the
Dead battery.
next we wanna crank up the vehicle with
the known good battery.
we will allow this vehicle to run for
2 or 3 minutes
before you actually try to crank the other vehicle.
after a few minutes of charging
let's try to crank this thing up and see
if it'll start.
now you wanna leave this vehicle running. it needs to
be driven for at least 30 minutes or so
so the alternator can charge the battery.
okay so now i want to show you how to disconnect the cables. basically we do it in the opposite order
of
how we hooked it up. so we'll take
the negative off
of the
dead battery vehicle first. lay it aside. go
over to the vehicle with the good battery.
we will disconnect the negative. then
we will disconnect
the positive. then we will go back to the
vehicle with the dead battery and disconnect the positive cable in it.