for the next trick we open the hoods on both cars. now that we have got the hoods open
on both cars battery on one side. battery
on the other side.
shouldn't be a problem because the cables
will be long enough.
this is the good car.
I'm going to start with the good car and
always start by putting on the
positive lead first.
here is something to be real mindful of. if these
are laying on the ground and they're
touching
my little incident earlier was because I
had it hooked up to a battery and I hooked the
two of these things together.
you don't want these touching. so you want
to hook these up
one at a time so that both are not
hooked up to one car
and then you have got these other two laying
on the ground that could potentially
spark in touch. so you start with the
positive battery cable.
just give it a little wiggle
when you put it on. that way that teeth
from the jumper cables will bite in
a little bit and can make a better
connection. okay which one positive and
which one is negative.
very good question. on top of the
battery
we'll see a lot of times
there is a plus sign for positive and a minus
sign for negative.
the positive cable will have like
something red on it.
like this one is red.
then the negative cable is usually
black.
but say in a case like this you don't know
you don't see a plus sign or a negative
sign. it is kinda hidden.
the negative cable usually runs
some place that touches the body
somewhere. you know. this is some place on
the body
or some place on the engine. the positive
cable always goes to
starter which is that guy. so what you
can do if you don't know which is which
is you can follow the cables and
the one that has anything that goes to
like the body of the car
or the outside of the engine that's the one
that's going to be negative
and of course the other is gonna be
positive. if you can't follow the negative
cable follow the positive cable.
okay now I'm gonna go to the dead car and
connect
the positive battery cable. once again make
sure that
these two do not touch. next we're going to
hook
the negative cable up on the good car.
there you go.
now here's the tricky part. you mightmy know
what's coming next.
you might not. don't hook the negative
jumper cable up to the battery on the
car that you are trying to jump.
a much better way to do this is to find
a good ground
on the engine itself. in other words find
a shiny metal spot on the engine
that you know is nice solid metal and
hook the ground cable up there
not to the battery itself. okay usually what I like
to look for is like a big hook sticking
up the top of the engine or something like
that.
this would be the engine. this is where
you would like
to have it mounted. the alternator
is an excellent place to put a cable
if you got enough. so how about right in here
on top of the alternator.
you wanna make sure to keep it away from
any of the spinning stuff.
cables are all hooked up from the good
car and the battery
and the bad car and the battery and a good
engine ground. now let's start the good car.
let the good car run for a little while
before you attempt to start the other
car.
give the battery time to
charge up a little bit before you actually
turn the key and try to start the other car.
if the other car is not starting
or it is really really dead what you might
want to do is you might want to raise
the idle up on the car that
is the good car and let it run into higher
idle. that will
allow the alternator to work a little
bit better and charge the battery up
even more than it would just by sitting
at idle. alright now I'm gonna go into the
dead car
which has been charging for a little while and try to
start it. please please please start.
alright now that both cars are running disconnect
the cables
on both cars. the sooner the better. you don't want to leave them on for
too long. you want to start with
taking the ground cable
off first.