if this was grandpa Joe, we would go like grandpa joe grandpa joe. he doesn't respond so we need to move on
to the next step. the next step is
calling 911.
when you call 911 you need to make sure
that you give them as much information
as possible
so they are able to help you. you also
should never
hang up on the operator first because if you do
they
might not have all information that
they need to come to the
rescue. also if there are other people
around you should have them call 911 and
tell them what to do
so you are able to move on to the next
step more efficiently
and quicker. the next three steps
have an acronym known as CAB or cab. the
first
letter for that is C and you do
compressions.
to do compressions you put your hand out
so you see your palm and then you
wrap it around your fingers.
you locate the lower breast bone on the person
and put your hands there. you need to
do
30 compressions at a rate of 100
compressions per minute.
the Depth of the compressions should be at
least two inches.
so if this were grandpa joe this is what
happen. you should also count aloud
when you do it so
you know what number you are at.
after you are completed with the compressions
you do the next part of cab which is
airway. to check the airway you should
put your cheek against his mouth.
when you do this you feel for moisture on your
cheek
listen for noises of breathing from
his nose and mouth
and look for chest rises. so
if this was grandpa Joe
we would go like this. look for Chest rises, feel for moisture
and listen for noise. next step
after that is to breathe into grandpa joe.
to do this you need to make sure that
the Airway is not obstructed and you need to put your
finger underneath his chin
so it's not clogged or anything. you
should give
the patient two breaths and these breaths
should be at a normal rate
at what you are breathing about right now.
make sure you plug his nose also so air does not
escape through his nasal passage.
so is this was grandpa joe it would go like.
after having completed
with the breath part you go back
to compressions. you repeat compressions breath
compressions breath
until the medical providers arrive.