personal protective equipment is
unavailable
are you alright hearing there's no
response to handle the forehead
Protection Act we tap on the collar bone
can you hear me
can you hear me there's no response you
in a purple shirt go call 911 come back
I might need your help
at this point we're going to assess the
patient for airway and breathing
I look closer feel looking down by
the patient per test ride and Paul
feeling to let me in prayer
I do not hear B or C any breeding
I think I may ask and I give to you
Press
I get my second brother
and I checked for a pulse this patient
is not remain
into not have a car on polls at this
time a vehicle right into CPR
Center just with one hand because this
is a trial
really begin are one-third to one-half
up the chest compression
the depth but just 30 times one and two
and three and four and five and six and
seven and eight and nine and 10 and all
up to 30
get two more trust followed by thirty
more compressions
and we're going to continue to do these
two breaths
and 30 compressions until either a the
patient revives
and begins to move or breathe or a
derives