surgeon you hear me can you hear me are
you awake
that point if we don't get any response
we're going to assess
are gonna look for chest rise and fall
we're gonna listen for air movement
through the mouth nose and we're going
to try and feel for
a brat on the side or cheek by doing
that we're gonna set their own
and wait for a couple seconds to assess
to make sure that the patients not
really have the patience not breathing
I'm gonna have my my partner here
reposition the airway
and reassess in the event no
also bear in mind when you're opening
their way we're going to use a head
tilts and left is a medical patient if
it was a trauma patient you typically
use the job for us maneuver
in order to to avoid manipulating the
cervical spine anywhere
or potentiating any type of problems I
might already be existing due to the
trial
at this point we're gonna say the
patients not breathing
on his own and I'm going to start my
partner here
to administer to press risk
and then reassess the patient we're also
going to check for a pulse after those
two breasts and if there's no pulse
we're going to establish CPR I'll
with hand placement one heal the hand
over the stardom
between the noble line the other hand on
top and we're gonna do
30 compressions so want you
then we're gonna ventilated patient
again twice we're going to make sure
that nine on was activated if we're
outside the hospital or away from the
ambulance
and if there's an AED in the area such
as the mauler
like malls are airport way to make sure
that the
they media's is brought to the side of
the patient with us as well
and until then we're going to continue
CPR
already
30 alright
that's pretty much it is continue CPR
and a 100 compressions per minute
preferably anywhere
from 10 to 12 a violations within that
same time frame
after every five cycles a CPR gonna
check appalls
and we're going to continue to do CPR
until the ad- rise on CAD arise if it
does
for prehospital or for in the ambulance
were also going to attach a patient to
monitor and assess
I with hard to relate or pads for for
any type %uh