laying on the ground appears to be
having problem the first thing that you
wanted to use to make sure that you are
safe
if you're safe you can approach the
person
and the first thing we want to do is
establish responsiveness
went to gently placed her hands on a
person's chast
and chic yell are you okay
are you okay if there's no response from
the individual
we can presume that they need help
sometimes
the second stop is to somehow hell
so many activate 911 once we know that
help is coming
then we can start to help the patient if
there's nobody around nobody
there too to go get help we need to go
get help
we want to call call 911 tell whether
the person is
and then come back so the first then ass
out
is to arm or not the airway we open the
airway by placing the palm of one hand
on patients forehand grasping the bony
prominences
Chan with the other hand gently told her
head back
once they had his back your mouth is
open
the airways open we can then look lesson
in creole
sleep what are your rates down less than
a mile
we're looking down the chest watching
for the chest to go up or down
listening for airflow in feeling the air
going in and out on here if they're is
the air coming out and they are bringing
which is simply hold your way open and
we for help to arrive
if there's no breeding and we need to
give them to
slow bowl grass by performing out there
now
you do that by pinching the nostril shot
with one hand
placing your mouth over the patients
about
and blowing twice cash
me once that's done
we now need to arm observed for signs of
life
so why would serve the patient on little
observe their skin color typically
around them now
the nose or the ear lobes if they're
if the heart isn't beating bill Turner
kinda blue tinge
if you see that then not that we want to
start compressions
sought to start CPR compressions
in a place the Hilo Hawaii and doesn't
matter right or left heel one hand in
the center the chest just pull in
Apple's
lower third of the sternum place the
other hand on top
you are an oppressed up and down thirty
times
and read about a hundred per minute that
most like this
one to them for fun
6 10 11
tall harem 40 buttons 17 PT
nineteen-point one point 3 for
compact text some and I'm turn
after 30 compressions we return to the
head
reopen the airway and give two breaths
back to the chest 30 more compressions
to and relations
in continue until help arrives