I tap and shout. hey hey. are you okay? he doesn't
respond to me.
meaning he doesn't talk to me he's not
moving.
I don't see any breathing or any signs of life.
at that point if I'm by myself
I yell for help. if someone comes
great.
I tell them to go and call 911 and get me an AED.
if no one comes then I'm gonna go leave to call 911 and
get an AED.
if no one comes and I saw him fall.
so he clutched his chest and fell on the ground
then
I'm gonna go call right away.
if i didn't see him fall, meaning I walked
up into the room and I found him down
after I did the hey are you okay I'm going
to
stay and I'm gonna do CPR for two minutes before I leave.
so you saw him clutch his chest and fall
you leave first. if you didn't see him
clutches his chest and fall
meaning you found him lying on the ground
stay and do 2 minutes of CPR first
then call but only if your by yourself.
Best case scenario
you yell help or there's other people around
you are
gonna send them to go call 911 and get the AED.
so we've established that I've sent someone to go and call 911
get me an AED. I'm gonna check make sure he's
not breathing.
he doesn't appear to be breathing. i'm
looking for chest rise and fall to see if he's breathing.
I don't see any chest fall and rise in this
mannequin here. I'm gonna say he's not
breathing.
from there I'm going to start with
my compressions. I'm gonna put the hell
of my palm
on the lower half of his breath bone. so
that big bone right in the middle of
their chest.
lower half of it. interlocking my
fingers
I'm going to press down. 30 compressions.
Press at least two inches in an adult. so
if this guy weighs 400 pounds it might
be four inches.
if they weigh only 120 about two inches.
you're going to do it at a rate of at
least a hundred beats
per minute. that's pretty fast. a 100
beats per minute.
so if you know the song stayin alive you can
do that.
if not you do about 30 compressions in
eighteen seconds.
that would be great. and you always
have to allow for proper recoil. meaning the chest has
to come back
all the way to it's natural position to let
the heart fill with blood.
so my 30 compressions are gonna
look like this.
30. then i need to give him 2 breaths.
get your pocket mask. remember it has a
teardrop shape.
sometimes they'll be so nice they'll
say nose at the top. that goes
around the mouth. make some gentle
downward pressure. you don't want to
squeeze. you don't want to mash.
just gentle downward pressure. and then you need to
tilt to open the airway. deliver two breaths.
I just need to see chest rise and fall.
you don't need to blow up too much.
if you blow up too much it causes air to go
in to their stomach and then that person is gonna
vomit.
we don't want that. that would be not so
good for him or you.
so two breaths. there's one breath.
notice you see chest rise and fall. We're looking to see the
chest rise and then fall.
then I'm gonna go directly back into
doing
30 more compressions.
go right back into giving two
breaths.