Always make sure the scene is safe for you and the victim.
Check for response by tapping the victim's shoulder and shout, "Are you okay?"
If there is no response, that is, if the victim is unresponsive and not breathing,
or only gasping,
activate emergency medical services
and get or call for an AED.
Immediately start the chest compressions.
Push hard and fast, at a rate of at least 100 compressions per minute.
Count out loud "1, 2, 3, 4, 5"
up to 30 compressions.
Push the chest at least 2 inches deep with each compression.
After 30 compressions,
open the airway using the head tilt/chin lift
method,
then give two
mouth to mouth breaths.
Deliver air over one second to make the victim's chest rise.
Give one breath
every five to six seconds
for a rate of 10-12 breaths per minute.
Continue 30 compressions
followed by 2 ventilations
for a ratio of 30:2.
The AED should be used as soon as it is available.
Resume chest
compressions immediately after the shock is given.
For adult CPR, the ratio of compression to ventilation is 30:2 for both
one and two rescuers.
For two rescuers,
change the compressor every two minutes
or every 5 cycles to avoid fatigue.
Rescuers should try to change the compressor role
in less than 5 seconds.