check for danger find out if they're
conscious by gently shaking their
shoulders
and speaking to them if I don't respond
open the airway by putting one hand on
their forehead
and gently tilting the head back lift
the chain
using two fingers look listen
and feel for normal breathing for up to
10 seconds
if they're not breathing normally give
them 5
initial rescue breaths pinch your nose
seal your mouth over there's and blood
for about a second age
then place your hand in the middle upper
chest
and gave 30 chest compressions people
tell which helped everything and then
come back use one or two hands
depending on the Souris at the child
continue cycles
30 chest compressions and to rescue
breaths
until the ambulance arrives