the first step in responding to this medical emergency is surveying the scene.
quickly survey the scene to see if there is anything harmful around or
blood on the victim and even poisonous fumes.
if your victim has blood on or around them it is very important
to put on gloves and keep the blood from contacting your skin.
after carefully surveying the scene
proceed to gently shaking the
victim and asking if he or she is okay.
from there we move on to the second step which is contacting
EMS. it is very important to stay with your victim at all costs.
so tell a designated person nearby
to contact EMS. hey can you contact EMS for me.
if there is nobody around
then you have to contact EMS on your own.
the third and final step is administrating CPR.
slowly move the victim's body
to a stable position
and then position yourself at the victim's
shoulders. slowly move the victim and check
their pulse.
proceed to doing your ABC's which stands for airway, breathing and
circulation. tilt the head
to open the airway and lean closely to the victim's mouth for any
signs of brething.
if the victim has any signs of breathing roll him or her over and
wait for medical professionals to get here.
but if there are no signs of breathing you have to quickly perform
CPR. with
rescue breathing first. the best way to give
rescue breathing is the mouth to mouth technique. Start by pinching the person's nose
and tilting the head back and keeping the chin lifted up.
then make an airtight seal with your mouth
on the victim and then give two quick breaths. then
check
for their pulse.
after the two breaths if there is still no breathing from the victim
then you will have to perform Chest
compressions.
with the heel of your hand on the sternum or the middle of the chest and your
fingers interlocked on the chest, keep your arms completely
straight
and do 15 reps of chest compressions.
then check for the pulse again.
if there's still no breathing, do the mouth to mouth
one more time
and 15 compressions
and check for the pulse again.
repeat this cycle until 4 times or until the victim is
now breathing or wait until the medical emergency people get here.