well
so the first thing to do is to look for
and if necessary remove any danger
now find out if the person is in fact
unconscious
and not just to sleep squeezing gently
and ask you to do something light
can hear me open your eyes
squeeze my hand. now is the time to send
the hell
call an ambulance also get someone to
bring different maleta
if there's one nearby you stop by
pushing on his chest to pump the
oxygen carrying blood to his brain then
you blow
you're a into the victims lines because
it still contains oxygen
once is a gets down here the lungs will
automatically
absorb the oxygen and put it into the
blood the diff
a third at the Chester after 30
compressions give
to Bretts to do this super hit back
lift the jewel the page to knows close
to make sure you get a good