position yourself next to the vitim's shoulders and then check the ABC's.
open the airway checked the breathing
and checked the circulation or the pulse.
first
open the airway. take the hand that's
closest to the victim's head
and put it on their forehead. next take
two fingers
of the other hand and put it on the bony
part of their chin. tilt back.
next check for breathing. look
listen and feel for the breath. look for
the chest rising and falling.
listen for the breath in your ear and
feel the breath on your cheek.
do that for about five seconds.
if there is no breathing you must give to
full breaths right away.
take two fingers of the hand that's on
the victim's forehead
and pinch the nose shut. then take your
mouth
and seal the victim's mouth giving two
full breaths so that no air escapes while
you are trying to breathe.
then check the circulation or check
the pulse.
take two fingers and put it on the
center of the victim's throat
and slide it into the groove that's next
to the throat.
do this for about five seconds and if
there is no pulse
chest compressions must be started right
away.
first position your hands
on the victim's chest.
take two fingers of the hand that's
closest to the victims feet
and slide it up the bottom of the rib
cage till you reach the notch
that is directly beneath the breastbone.
then take your other hand and place it
right next to your two fingers.
weave your fingers inside your other
hand. according to the American Red Cross
while keeping the correct hand position
straighten your arms and lock your elbows
so that your shoulders are directly over
your hands.
while in this position enough pressure
will be created to compress the chest
one-and-a-half to two inches for an
adult.
do this fifteen times counting out loud.
continue the cycles of
breathing and compressions four times.
after the fourth time
check the victims pulse again. if
there is still no pulse
continue these cycles until the victim
breathes again
or until trained medical professionals
arrive and can take over for you.