I love resuscitation and thats airway
breathing
circulation into fibrillation so first
thing I come up here you okay you okay
I make sure this person just again not
sleeping in the park
and make sure they're actually
unconscious there's no response I don't
see any movement I don't see any
breathing
when i activate the UMass system and
when I say help
somebody call 911 my point to somebody
you over there
go call 911 come back when you're done
this way we know that there's an
ambulance on the way
so we can get to help soon as possible
now I'm going to open the airway and
look listen and feel for breeding
as I talk to head back to put my hand on
the up on the forehead
put my fingers here on the bony
prominence to the chin
and I tilt the head back and bring the
time now the airway
and I'm gonna look listen and feel free
breathing looking at the chest thing if
the chest is rising
and listening for any air movement thing
if I feel any air movement
if no that's going to occur then I'm
gonna deliver two breaths
too nice for brats
another air to get the chest to rise if
you don't feel comfortable sticking your
mouth on the mouth were
another person you could use a
commercially available pocket mask
you can get most to these at pharmacy or
someplace like that
and you basically place the sort on the
the patient's face
any and you tilt your head back
mom but you're going to use your thumbs
to help hold this on the person's face
and then you gonna breathe inside still
delivering two breaths
alright so after the two breaths goin'
began looking for any signs a
circulation they're not moving
they're not talking arise then open up
for anything like that
I'm gonna go ahead and perform
compressions I'm gonna bring my
my hand basically in line with their
nipples right on their breast bone right
here on the sternum
and I'm gonna press down 30 times and
press hard in the press fast and press
down about an inch and a half to two
inches
up
and where do this over and over five
times
up
saw we do 30 are compressions with two
violations we do that five times