so check to make sure there's no danger
on the palce. it could be electrical wire
could be some glass some fuel. anything
that you consider dangerous.
that's the first thing to remove. next
we move on to
A for response. so talk and touch. can you hear me.
there's no response. okay
now we know there's no response. we move
on
to S for Send for help. so you have
someone here say
can you please go to call the ambulance
let them know we have an unconscious
patient.
if you're the only one here and have a
phone pick up the phone
call triple-0 and let them know what's
happening so someone's on their way
while you're working on the patient. okay
now we move on
to A. A is for airway. so we have to check
if the airway is clean. first we need a little bit of head
tilt like this.
that allows some air to get in. secondly
we open up
have a look to make sure his airway is clean.
in this case it is.
there's nothing obstructing the air
getting in or out. okay now we have checked his
airway so we move on to B for breathing.
so I have to check his breathing. so open
up.
firstly what i do to have a listen and a
feel and i watch the chest.
nothing's going up and down I can't feel
anything coming out of his mouth I can't
hear anything either.
so he's not breathing. now that we know
he's not breathing
we assume he's going to need CPR. so we
move straight into center of the chest.
heel of the hand at the Center of the chest and
compressing
from here. now with CPR
we need to do a ratio of 30 compressions to
two Breaths.
and the rate of those 30 compressions
that one hundred per minute.
so that's not quite two per second.
we immediately give two breaths. Jaw
support and head tilt again.
straight back to our 30 compressions again.
back for our two breaths. now with our CPR
and our 30 compressions and two breaths we
continue those until we get a response
until normal breathing resumes or till you are exhausted or until
professional help arrives.