1. Always make sure the scene is safe for
you and the victim.
2. Check for response by tapping the victim's
shoulder and shout, "Are you okay?"
3. If there is no response, that is, if the
victim is unresponsive and not breathing,
or only gasping, then activate emergency system
and get or call for AED.
4. Check for the carotid pulse for at least
5 seconds but no more than 10 seconds.
5. If you do not feel the pulse, then start
CPR immediately, starting with chest compressions.
Remember, start compressions within 10 seconds
of recognition of cardiac arrest. Push hard
and fast, at a rate of at least 100 compressions
per minute. Count out loud "1, 2, 3, 4, 5"
up to 30 compressions.
6. After 30 compressions, open the airway
using the head tilt/chin lift method. Give
two breaths. Deliver air over one second to
make the victim's chest rise.
7. Give one breath every 5 to 6 seconds for
a rate of 10-12 breaths per minute.
8. Continue 30 compressions followed by 2
ventilations, that is a ratio of 30:2, until
an advanced airway, endotracheal tube, combitube,
or laryngeal mask airway is placed.
9. Once the advanced airway is placed, then
start continuous chest compressions with ventilations,
at a rate of one breath every 6-8 seconds,
or a rate of 8-10 ventilations per minute.
10. AED should be used as soon as it is available.
Resume chest compressions immediately after
the shock is given.
Remember, for adult CPR the ratio of compression
to ventilation is 30:2 for both one and two
rescuers. For two rescuers, change the compressor
every two minutes or every 5 cycles to avoid
fatigue. Rescuers should try to change the
compressor role in less than 5 seconds.