victim and see if your victim is
conscious you walk up the victim in SA
hey hey are you okay the victim doesn't
respond the next thing we need to do
is to open the victim airway and check
to see if the victim is Brayden
we do that we'll by using what's called
a hit to channel if Matt
we take to hear in with tilted up and we
look within feel
what we're looking listening billboards
will look in
to see if the jesters rise in pollen
williston
to see if we hear exchange coming in at
the victims bout in with feeling with
the sad my cheek to see if we can feel
any
air movement I if the patient is not
breathing well I D here is we are
stopping wanna go call 911
I was now no one has been activated when
we come back to the patient we start
treating the patient the next thing I do
is win give the victims
breast were make sure that airways open
with the head torch and Leah with peeps
knows of
although I give the victim to breast
with each breath we want check to make
sure that the Chesters rise and fall on
why we're given the press
next thing we want is we wanna remove
the victim's clothes so we can get
victim's chest after that
we're gonna take their a hand in fantasy
nerve the victim's chest
and we'll take the heel with one hand
place in the sooner the chest
and then will that take your other hand
cross the fingers over
and we're gonna start known complex I
when do compressions you now
for a total of 30 compressions
with each compression we want to make
sure DJs
the victim's chest is going down about
one-half to one-third that the digest
from here we're going to continue this
these two steps we're going to give the
two breast in the 30 compressions