Tom safety valve
right there and you put the filter on
I and this point
but some really good
quality coffee low
a dumbass
but you know don't the don't press at
just make sure that there is no coffee
on the side
length and yeah to
time Park on outs go to the ass
both ok this is not my so
of from with I it's an hour let it boil
and all the water will
percolate up yet you and more
awesome awesome coffee or going away for
that too
to happen ISO we start getting some
percolation happening here
as you can see it's coming old to
spilling the top caster
I wanna closest stop cell it's fun
face
yes filling up
play fast not this is how you know
cell it's all done with the water quick
estimates the south side of this point
you just talk was also ok well it's got
a cock what's
supposedly issue use one of these small
cups and I like the Italian cups but I
like a big cup of coffee
and a lot of Mel