we're going to do then
and you don't wanna go more than that
because
then when you put your
proper grounding you wanna make sure
that the water didn't come up in this
area because you don't want to get your
coffee grounds
where before you actually make a call
game
so take this over here
you know here some coffee already agree
on a grounder here
finally going on
espresso of okay
okay have a but coffee
into the basket you notice I've got a
pretty well
full but they caution you
not to pack because if you packed the
coughing
grounds in there you could cause
it to the stain not come through the way
it should
and you could build up pressure on that
there wouldn't be a good okay so now I'm
gonna
screw top own and set it on the stoked
on
and we'll see what it okay
we have the top skirt on
something neglected to mention all goes
mmm around the time of %uh the
coffee basket yet to make sure that it
stays good inkling
fringe group back together so that you
make good CEO between the bottom Tom
as rubber gasket in New that you want to
make sure the
it is clean
you don't want get coffee grounds in
there annual
do look here in
once we start
hearings this team color from the bottom
will actually start seeing coffee come
out okay im startin hear something going
on
been about three minutes and
I'm a few years now but you can actually
hear
staying making a racket in the bottle
pop down there
what we ought to be seen here just in a
min
is some good espresso coffee coming up
through that
will bring in the center there and when
it does we'll have closed the top down
because
after the coffee comes out it starts
long will this thing now middle spew out
here own
in kitchen will with week
there we go
air comes the espresso map
okay and
in just about another minute or two it's
gonna start
making a little bit churchill jervis I
know
and you know it's just about done
the good
it
I think it's about the United
in where you can tell it's finished
is when it stops making that noise
okay so it's GE first about that point
when all the water in the bottom has
been covered in just a minute stamens
come up through the
coffee grounds it would require
so loosely in RR the lady espresso maker
actually did Leslie working expressing
good me
you know it's kinda hard