square and yeah
slow hands as I said now few
Caskey release also we're going to take
this
I your favorite espresso latest
on our very fine your local grocery
stores teaspoon
and your glasses view gaslight
music US actually hahaa said you know
its usual
hacer for all it
so it's chaos this it makes a
for her said okay for schools are so
happy say have makes you feel like crap
hahaa now and ozarks
Paso of
now 4x
you could have a small Bernard when you
to know I'm
why have to handle towards you so that
it doesn't get high as well
accident
if so why in a tonight
then ration it do it rent a
said share %uh
now here's what you really want a class
once you see it first
copy year what basically makes it now
she was like Capri a sweet to your cell
10 p.m. course he sells
10 waiting for us see how it is
%uh 0 then you and watch the hockey and
make sure that once the first no matter
coffee with Steph for right now make
said that sexy in the FR
so class once it starts making that I
still see it
what I N except for just first little
bit
office I
where I
hi ha
high to low green light brown on you can
see
halfway
her here so
see that sounds where section II
for safety first then we're gonna take
coffee for a dejar little for me sugar
mixture