you wanna make sure you fill a right
below or right on the bubble decided to
pop
them replace the final looking thing
that I probably should know what it's
called in English
and placed inside a Pok after that we
put our coffee inside the pot
you can either make a little mountain
bike am doing compressing the copy and
it will use to the top part on
are you compress it as you put it in
then was cool on the top as tight as we
can to make sure to copy or come out
from the side
and we simply put on sto over low heat
to prevent the copied from burning
because that woodstock you have to make
the copy all over again while the I
still burning hot
and that is no fun up
model
then you just have to wait five or six
minutes until you see the coffee
starting to come out from the holes
inside the park
the to
local vo
are
little