to set that aside and we're gonna fill
up the water
so weird me using three hundred forty
milliliters of water
on this particular mock apart a man that
just comes
right under the released I'll
you can use any outside and may have
just been a little too much
Gio right now that we have that sets
can do is worth just gonna set that
water
it sits at the base side i right
and now will prepare culture so
to prepare the filter we're going to be
using 26 grams of coffee
I'm just way that out all rights
love shopping around but the next things
up
is we are going to set our grinder and
for the most part I suggest a crime that
is
the slightly finer than drip
so on this key
and Cap'n for them using here that's
about one number
ring loader lower than trip
as you'll notice here
a grand directly into the basket much
like you do first press 0
I'm granite directly into the
portafilter I'm just be careful how much
you settle
because it can be easily fit a lot more
than 26 grams in the basket to depends
on how hard to settle
so may look a little bit deceptively
low: and
a.m. you notice important reminder
although it looks kind of like the
basket
espresso machine do not tampered
a mocha audit not designed to deal with
a pocket that's that is that dance it'll
actually
you tap it has a good chance to have a
popping the relief well
so now that we have
are coffee all set and we have the mocha
part reassembled
we will get ready to set it up
so just the turn the heat up too high
for using a stovetop burner than
it's probably going to be medium
medium-high and waiting at the clock
okay so now we have a top view so this
total process should take about five
minutes
start to finish depending on how fast
takes your water to heat up
so we're actually gonna go ahead and
skip
towards the end so this is about four
minutes 45 seconds now into it
and we're gonna see that the CAF is
beginning to come out so
right as the coffee beans to come out I
like to lower the heat to about fifty
percent of what it was
so for me it's Lauren it from hyde
medium would run the stovetop the maybe
from medium-high to medium-low
something like that and more to do is
worth the wait
as it approaches the as it approaches
the
very base the spout and right as it hits
the base the spout were gonna turn off
the heat all together
so it's right about now right at the
beginning at the spout and so
turning off the heat and the residual
heat is actually gonna carry this a
extraction all the way to the end the
reason to Lauren heat is that we really
don't want
it to be burst the water to be bursting
out at the bottom from start to finish
really wanna kinda temper that he didn't
temperature pressure because remember
trauma he is also I'm patrolling p
pressure in the rate at which the
water's coming from bomb if the heat is
on full blast
whole way through that I'll definitely
be splattering out so
now that we're finished we're gonna go
ahead and
poor the mocha part so if you're using a
stovetop burner
assertion electric one you might wanna
take it act of the actual bernard has it
will continue to
keep them occupied even after somebody's
gonna go ahead and poor
for sport carefully especially if I
pouring from a