dole just underneath the CFL input
filter
on top I'll next
fill the filter with expresso grounds
the car usually loosely packed to the
top of the filter
being careful not to overfill per pack
too hard
if you do back at your heart your pot
may be in danger of exploding
or we might just wait for her and no
coffee look here
authors step is just screw the top of
the coffee pot
I firmly once you've done that
place this on the heat
make sure the plastic and all is not too
close to the heat source
I'm going to label it out for a little
bit you can see where the party starts
to brew
that is probably better just leave it
down
in real life in order to avoid bills
fail to express
all through anything so hot months ago I
suggest not using the old record
for your free trader my expresso to call
sprouts 3 5 dry
thanks for joining