to about the center are the pressure
valve now put the basket in place
to make sure you didn't put too much
water in the bottom kept the basket
if water comes up you have a little too
much the mocha pot is made to make an
exact amount coffee
you really need to put the right amount
of water in the pot
next we'll fill the filter basket with
fine ground
is six or seven grams the coffee per
ounce today for our coffee
worry is not pre sick of the original
Special Blend
us press 0 pre see this is a fantastic
espresso
that's surely small batch roasted what a
flavor profile
constructed specifically furthest I love
coffee making
so how do you know just how to find the
coffee needs to be ground
one simple way is to go to your nearest
grocery store
by a small amount a coffee beans maybe a
quarter pound and grind it in the stores
coffee grinder
just like this one grinding on the
espresso citing
and use this as your control sample so
you know what the coffee should look
like
when you grind it at home you want to
make sure there's no coffee
in the stores trying to be four you
prepare your sample loosely fill this
basket and don't pack it down
it's okay at the basket is just over
filled now issued a top piece on tightly
settle on the slow watch and listen
when you see this team in here the pot
lovely