anybody
a who use these in Italy who created the
water
I'm so the water just gets added Roger
Lee cold water just get added to the
bottom reservoir I'm the the manual that
comes with this will say something about
filling water into you get to the
registration marks or to the water level
marks
I'm just as someone who spent what i'm
looking for them there are no such marks
I was trying to do is you after all the
water just up to below where the valve
is so just under the valve by
like a centimeter so I'm if you don't
have a valve in america pock
I endured during soar want to use anyway
I'm the way to see how often forget the
water is to make sure that no water
intrudes into
this funnel-shaped grounds comb
when it's inserted all the way singer
following the side and see about where
the bottom of this
this %uh followers are pop it inside to
make sure that
no water comes up through
this song this filter colour filter
funnel
and that's how much water should have as
much as you can get in without intruding
into this
I to fill this once again probably the
ideal would be
freshly ground locally roasted are
firstly roasted coffee
I'm grounded something less than an
espresso grind
to the grind for this the proper grind
is finer than a filter coffee ground
crying and and not as fine as an
espresso grind
if you get to find that's really get
problems with an overpressure situation
in the the bottom part although like I
said I've I've never actually seen that
and I've
stop these things for coffee many times
absurd to fill this
are you take your your copy which is
percent not quite as per se ground you
don't want to be caking
as a surly and you feel this more coffee
for thermal coffee filter
all the way to the top I actually
even fill it slightly over the top
I misusing Lovatt sup fine ground
a espresso coffee in a cam from the
store
are that is pretty much what everyone in
me pose used
are they would use Kimbo which is a big
local brand everyone liked
I'm every now and then you to use when
using tule aren't you he was probably
you know the the premier are that the
premium coffee
was also from up north and so cabin or
sell thing going on Italy where
no here southerners didn't are cater to
the northern parts quite as much in so
the local brands over camber were from a
comment
and then I just loosely packed this now
I'm not to camping at
I'm not packing it like you would
espresso I just don't want to get all
over the map
rubber gasket here so
this loosely Camperdown you screw the
top reservoir on up
really tight and it goes right honey
burner on the stove I'm this is our
my caster has a very high flame so
actually set slightly off-center
so that the plastic handle doesn't get
enough for forces the flame and then you
want
whatever medium a flame on this
are you don't wanna just torture I
because that will just
serve worsen the problem about this top
was working really hard and cooking the
coffee
now we're going to %uh put this on the
burner and what will happen is the water
in the bottom or boy all
generate steam this team will generate
pressure but a lot
a little bit of pressure and that
pressure will force the water
down and then up through that siphon
and that that makes up the coffee the
Coffee Co
and then I'll come up into the upper
reservoir
you see there's a lot how we're here
where that the water will come out of
and that will make the coffee one thing
that
was commonly used to see people doing in
Naples was
they were taken to a small mental power
most like a steaming pot for milk
and put all the sugar for the public
coffee in there and when the first few
drops a coffee came out
from the the top %uh the the mocha part
the pore tightening cream it
with sugar almost sure what you're
making a very
concentrate frosting or something I
would they would use a spoon cream that
sugar
and that the first few drops a coffee
together
and then when you pour the coffee into
that metal container after was brewed
I'm he would be almost like a Crammer
kinda of a crime on top
I'm I'm not sure what's different I've
tried doing that the last couple times
and couldn't go to work anymore
I'm I used to do this all the time
fifteen years ago but I'm so either the
sugars different or other copies differ
I'm different but
any case if you see people doing that
that's that the attempt is to come to a
pseudo crema
I and I will just let this go they will
check back in a couple minutes
okay receiving an action shot here the
coffee actually starting to brew
the water's been on the boil here for
about a minute should be getting pretty
close
and you'll see that the copy start to
first %uh kinda whose herbicide also
despite a little bit and then it should
come in a steady stream
and here we go the first drops are
coming out
and this for your cough a little bit is
what they call it works but some coffee
and the juice will pick up a steady
stream this is actually just
group keeping the cost up but you see
coming out into a trick or this will
speed up
as the the water begins to our come down
or get harder faster and pressure
increased rapidly in
nose strips or sputtering out and that
means is probably a good time consider
closing the lid
because I guess the very tail and when
there's more steam and water
this will turn to our sort of spotter or
below coffee out
and I'm wearing a white shirt so let's
close the lid
in this should be done hopefully in
about 45 seconds
okay I can hear that this is just about
done it's so I just sore sputtering
towards the end
so soon is it's finished you want to get
this off the heat
we don't want to to cook at upper
chamber any more than we need to
and died in all good warmer will have no
cup is already warming
and will allow take a look at server to
a standard
are stegner witness which was a lot of
apart milk
not just in italy has a calf LA but on
this would be another
with making a very for standard
a capital H A you do the the hot milk
separately
added to the very strong coffee with
usually plenty of sugar
into an even in preparation of Cuban
coffee or cup a coupon or
would-be as we have the same process
using something like a
como que express because you run or most
people don't have
three four thousand dollar expresso
machines in their home that's what book
that's how they get their coffee
so much time earned midday as a coffee
break
quick espresso at the cafe but at home
people are using things like a
the smoke express to me to make a are
relatively strong
a cup of coffee which is a through the
the practical way of making
espresso price for the milk swarm I know
I'm pouring this into a are
to a small class as opposed to a cop I'm
before when was a semi hate mail about
that are being a traditional corporate
yeah I know
I just wanted to show with the
consistency the coffee I don't have any
clear coffee mug coffee cup so I'll use
this little
them in our class and