to create the perfect espresso to use
the stove top espresso maker
start by answering the lower chamber and
fill it with water
right below the safety valve place to
filter on top
and fill it with finely ground espresso
coffee a small amount of ground coffee
should be used if you desire
light brew however to make real espresso
you must fully feel the filter with
coffee and level it off
at the top without pressing it screw
back to top part
making sure that the filter and gasket
are on place under medium heat
gently through your Sprint cell if your
stove is a gas flame stove
be cautious not to expose the handled
directly to the flame
remember to bring your espresso with a
lid on it all times
inside though your coffee will be bring
to perfection once the coffee is
three-quarters full