right about there
you don't want to go over King
then the coffee holder
holds the coffee right above that
you notice it has lots of little holes a
so what happens on the water starts
boiling steam pressure Mexico up
through the coffee um
and and even though
this is the coffee around years I've got
some Fargo
in a container is once you open this
these are backing pack
bricks by the way and you can get these
almost anywhere these days I know
karema charges a and
person yeah here angler and it goes on
sale
tele that got some
this is not Maxwell House crash rose but
Inc to have I'll spoons for some sort of
here
coffee scoop works fine and
to fill this up
and it is also important to tamp it down
as it is with some other fancier
machines
some other the really a
fancy machines like to get a restaurant
often they're made in Italy and a
they rely on steam pressure but they are
pump driven and pump a
the education system steam pressure but
they also talked a lot
I am gonna tap it down
don't work my hands are clean
just wash now looks
then put the top lock is what happens
when the
steam pressure goes to the coffee
grounds it comes out here at the top
and I'll it comes down
and also after a little while you want
this
to be shot but for sure lasyone
certain to come out and that's I'll an
important part
parties who the top of here why leave it
open sea concealer for starts to come up
and I need to point out that this is the
the but the call three cup size you can
get these
a for anywhere from
six to ten dollars finally
pick while they come in different sizes
this is the nine cup size
a I found this while
at bloom for eight dollars
were deal a this one
alt mall and they may come out well I
think 15 cup size
make the smaller the three cups ice up
fast at the point out there
I have to face this because the handle
about to break off so I use a little
clamp
a gotta do what you gotta do it
out the best way it works now
important parts sugar such as the
three cup size per 3-14
ship obviously if you have a sweet tooth
you could put in more
or if you got like sure you could do it
with outer
old ok you
espresso Catholic lot
okay she got her
them ready put it of the
flame or stovetop this is a gas
a startup which is really much better
because it's easier control Richard L
you can use electric but missile
typical attack
it houses trial right
K somehow got the flank
this except really important and ass
do at the time all waiting for the year
hockey come up come up steam pressure
Zambrano
top a you wanna have some
cuts ready these urgent task ups
a and
this does about 3 size small
a you also have like this anything
smaller than
rate kafka just seconds we're gonna see
the first batch in this is
really really import
now at this point when little coffee
first article of its just a little bit
thicker
write about their you close the and then
you put just a little bit in the sugar
maybe about a quarter sized that's about
right
per pack of Lancel continue growing
on them mister this yr and this is the
secret
this is a but makes it look
fans help to
shared peace
be face a
she gets to calif.-based where
if you live and you have friends waiting
for she can make
gurgling noises have expensive pushing
the time necessary
home now this will start hurling here
second we'll see hot steam
from ha in here
here its just about ready
and I want to open this now /url
be like about the serious K
it's ready
pouring here keep stirring