so missed
possible sprawling
up and I set my coffee grinder to
espresso total very fun
said
there
planned
nice
did not get it
all
K keep
all home
builders
people don't smoothed over
up
no
edge
so we can hope this can school in Taipei
cake
no
turn the printer on high but that
they're
it'll take a couple months more state
perking up the world
what happens in HR percolator its the
water
turns to steam down here and it's four
stop
through the filter and then part
through this little so under their
and off the top and fills up the top of
the the pot and it makes a very strong
up a copy so it is a lot like a spoiled
its
and going to stop it was come back
was not boiling yet but
yessi even it's a cream like Willis
presso
similar process is just the pressures
and quite as much as a
those with a real espresso machine
to close the schools when it starts to
boil steam comes over the top
mister
oil
up
tape