you don't use any less because
it needs that quantity to perform for
probably
and if you do more than home
you know if you look hot over that and
now in it so can function properly if
you put too much pressure
thanks for the call littlefield this is
a little fun
I'm so custody and this is what you used
to produce for so you so your coffee
so I was going to take a program coffee
of course I'm just phase but for best
results you can grow into quantum
just if we wanna re sub-issues a
medium senator on his as phone
as you would use for an espresso machine
but you don't wanna
task force's much through for entry side
somewhere in between usually wakes best
its bid for giving it doesn't have to be
precise
known to go ahead end zone just
evenly put in the coffee India is no
need to compress into
botanical you can have a compressed
needs to be released so that we can fly
three
in force from we feel a I can say
so they can say I've filled up the om
top funnel Bay WI the program coffee
it's all just Lucy just don't wanna
pack it in so same otherwise it's not
gonna let them wander through
speed next step
is I'm to you put this together
basically so you've got some with you
start to feel BAE
like a silicon ring that's done for many
seal heat for you
and a little fills the screen that's
gonna stop a motive
the grinds getting through into actual
drink so it's pretty
feels really
and then put the Iranian cynically to
get
in
easy screwing the two together
so you wanna do that
until it's just I not to talk to the was
you
Reckitt but just enough to formally meet
tight seal
my no one sits on
not something the next step step 3 I
guess
is just a puppet strings the medium I'm
heat on your plate and
stop the brewing process C-one techie he
not
to you get there the hangover the direct
source
heats up easy gas so on some ban on
you don't want obviously the hot he up
on this he looks
you can integrate into it you don't know
on if it's something like an electric
one here
just keep it off to the side so it's
nothing indirect a the same to the
design to stay relatively cool to touch
so the nipple was this is going to take
probably
you know about five minutes to happen
and
will come back when it starts to starts
to break so take a few minutes just to
explain what's happening in the process
of growing this coffee
so the naturist 02 warehouse design is
that you feel that the bottom reservoir
we cold filtered water arm
by pipeline heat sources what it's going
to do is is hate the template that water
of course creating steam which is going
to build up
fresh respond compartment the pressure
that builds up in there once it gets to
the right point
is going to stop forcing that he said
what up through the bottom of that fun
on and and go through the coffee grinds
which is going to be the extraction fue
coffee
grimes Victor brewed espresso is then
going to Kenya
the the top of this spare your
any into the sort holding with reservoir
the top
that's where the coffee ultimately spam
finishes its Bri
now one as a sign it's important not to
have that he too high
because what that will do he's in the
coffees for one thing
heat the water too quickly into hot on
you want to avoid that so that's why I
suggest a medium heat to stop if you
want to experiment for what's best for
you
you know some it might find in the day
you to Jorge Doral 08
any on this starts arms this is still
just heating up gently
and now I'm like a high in this press 0
or or proper spur sorry brewed under
extreme pressure is not going to be that
monthly fee golden crime at the Eagle
most shots
extractions what you'll find is this
is a small amount of grimacing on top I
suppose you can call it that
you'll see when when the bridge happens
what's going on name
found the basically don't get that
reached peak
honey like creme other you would offer
hi extra
high-pressure extraction because this is
the press release is not quite as much
some other things that I I want to use
the espresso for of course it's a lovely
smooth
way to bring you coffee and I'm teens to
get rid of a lot of
the on business or sickness
we can start here opening up in the
bottom
you it seems to balance at the flight is
really well not funded usually quite
dismayed
coffee on to drink
think this I really quite full point I
so they do sin up quite well to me know
on if you like to heat milk found and
use the espresso
in that city you make use of what some
things that's
inside good said butts
here we go as you can see coffee just
stuff to do before the top
is this is happening too quickly war I'm
its it's flowing really fast then you
know you've got the heat you find
smoking reduced sleuth what's this
brewing
online too soon as you see fit gauge
when when the
was about three-quarters two-thirds
three-quarters full I like to remove it
from the heat source
down because you don't want to run the
bottom
some you take it off the moved on
so basically it's running and it would
enhance put up through the funnel
& Young's extractions for you ok way so
you well it was unjustly that CK for
to finish Dublin 1 and we'll be back in
a few moments to use is the bridge
complete all set up just like I would
hear
I'm only if you have to work a long
black style that drink