okay so as you see here have a bottom
portion filled with water already
you just swiftest this middle course
inside
I'll come and get my first round think
which today is the
ethiopia saddam a natural from social
this
are brewing method really brings out the
very cleaver out this
coffee and it just rearm a
highlights the great flavors about it
of course without a slightly Anza
according leveling off so her
here even extraction throughout basket
so I just left wing
and it's really important to make sure
you don't have any
any grounds runs outside edge so that it
doesn't get screwed down and
and block yes
the sea or now here's a little tip that
I wanna show you
just put an extra amount there
and the center that will help without
creating more pressure
and I'm yeppers a nice which part of
this way
so their habits clean around the edges
and he just simply screw down to stop
ok make sure it's nice and secure
so that the pressure builds up and
doesn't in the water doesn't shoot up
sides are ok that's not what you want so
you just sit there and what this Brewer
and I'm user a medium heat
so what time is six meses copy will be
rare ho
case which you can see the coffee is
turning to Bruno
I'm you can see how just how rich that
is
so we recommend is that while you were
burning your coffee that
you actually I boil a kettle as well
because this is
like double strength and then you can
you can drink it that way if that's
safer for
five-time most people like to mix it
happen half with
some hot water
dubbed
after the bridge complete
with that beautiful rich cafe to your
mother about halfway up
think your cattle