free
way good partisan filter and
where around rapid you all want to you
ground right a try you ground coffee
here yet very
you don't get really want you rather
stronger
I'm coffee right no Henry
my going lot more and
an idiot yeah
heart call it the upper chamber anywhere
I yeah who are all lower
through the round rather
and we'll come right up to two hours are
after for crime know it
anyone actually through it here
we don't want the water me I
and that over
few hi yeah last two
I hid I but %uh
eighty yeah to hi you I had more
yeah problem other eurozone I
burkett laser feel rather let
bean no I don't get it unity yeah
your lemme and family go
and now I'm rather dont
not done enough blood a lot of heard it
of
my reply diplomat or
I have it here my him away
rocket I love you you
on it hard
that I'll write it
here word for Whitney
here thing I word
right you are rather and after
video you all I you did of crap here