emergency dial sir
staying outta is too much pressure
inside
despite a lot of a little yeah when you
put your paper copy
I is up this is a espresso coffees that
Walmart I bought and then I whole being
branded myself
not happy and is moving around a little
the and those little late bit you see
is actually Coco I
dad and son cocoa bean
or ground-up my head
that is a little bit to the left rough
later on the bottom that
local pocket filter Anna rubber gasket
any insight is a POS they like about
this local pot
is the post insider that with the cop
comes out
is pointed downward so it won't spotter
out the top
couple of other mogul pots slaughter
actually kinda bad
unfairly modern leave the room a
comeback
fine coffee lol place this is a
stainless steel seat heater induction
cooktop
and it doesn't take very long as
actually had a surprise
my other local Haas
T 45 minutes to cook to come up the
temperature
this one doesn't take long at all and
I'll go ahead and show your Ad here just
how long
does
presidency are here pot he had passed
out
I've been using it for a while mom
and really try same
really nice copies good value some other
ones isn't cheap ones
as an easy years is that the Walmart
pear tree bernie & the
law but works really well stainless
steel
I'm maybe we'll see get some stuff in
here
where AM was doing this great on this
induction cooktop and
actually on proper plastic bag against
it month in the bag until
registry job
before I to just a better to do it
granite
three minutes all the copies for plenary
and
will be done here in his pretty quick
is there really any local park as India
pretty fast too
I was actually as president how fast it
was but that's the
by a lady be a smoking hot I really
enjoyed
interview when were done
some fresh know that yes
presso but some really good