you grand the copy I pick members though
a
brother copy that we have because
everything copies are sweet and they
tend to be more forgiving in another hot
I'm a Canon copier they're going to be a
little bit are there and a little bit
more about little
they don't know who pick products on the
market while I companies that are
sweeter
at home when I try and the copy I just
look and my
little tiny but I'm Koppikar and I have
and bring it to her
somewhere finer than what would be an a
paper welfare
the sky government right here and they
actually want that kind of all
everybody doesn't have the that their
house probably even though we do for the
transfer espresso Dirks
you down it this is a spoon and your
profit on a fast because
but physically even you can Cup if I do
that together if you want to put the top
back on here
but you want to but I'll see them bail
paying guest they just grab it
in it what's happened burbank here and
it turned the volume back up again
wait untill the pot set to make funny
little neither from the call the press
me is there something that's like when I
might start making out with you know
that fuckin the
copy out might take a while on the track
while you're waiting you can play with
the entire care what kind of a broom
handle
waiting for to play starting to get a
kind
happy at if you're using a staff that
a gas stove it does not take this long
here
I
thank you
publishing it can gather them coming out
over play early on attorney up
and actually taken off the heat %uh like
we're just gonna come up into the top
I i'm ok if I and you're gonna happen at
it's going to be
I really strong I'm tech top it's not
great and I
French math copy and going to be very
good if he did it the right way
kallins and makes to