and if you fill it abounds
the it is is that they're not just a few
they just recommend not to just for
safety reasons therefor
you over if you get into the develop
submerged admiral improperly leave
anything
concert that's that
in
you've got your coffee
was used to be provides a criminalist o
strategical
european stove top
the sort of social and ok and and what's
the crimes like anger i guess i set my
heart
quite as fun as this person
apartment you want it
little finally views for
trip coffee
somewhere in the meadowlands somewhere
in the butler solidifying threat like
that even if i were over at that point i
thought that would work
just for candy than
stuff up then
one downside with the
still talkin it's only down side is that
you have to understand is
you'd have to make it to cassidy
but i can't make really short
assure
so i couldn't sleep as i say it's just
me as i was going to put enough coffee
and water in for one shocked the packers
one stove top maker we offer that does
useful of stocker
uh... that's the ilsa
that fiscal year abreast gadgets
unique in that food basket
because of the little insert for you can
unifil it for
we could put the inserting
traveling upon use half as much water
call so it's a little more facts about
right okay
because this needs to
because his uniform sort of
approximately an espresso machine
just filling the staff with water
is it really gonna work because anyway
happy or have coffee in his death
because the coffees can be pushed up
against the screens with half full
it's not gonna get
pushed against the screen
and uh... basically do you need that as
sort of like a pressure element with the
building at that scene getting a lot of
the democrat
products
nice thing about
he's still talking it's a simple
basically left for it
hills where item is the gasket
f_m_ my wife and i have been using the
same gasket for over a year now aka
methods of f and ideas short of
you know breaking the plastic handle
virtually nothing go wrong jasmine
recently
seven forty sevens diet and
uh... just as we said a few miles this
is a specifically then they set which is
the brushed
and then there's the this is that the
message is this something that little
separate miles that you're talking about
them
overhear at the bottom
cameron which is double walled
connections in some that what they did
have a double wall for about half
uh... travelers retention her of the
year
okay purpose in this of course is the
delivery
turf club they thought the original and
made of aluminum yet but it's chrome
plated aluminum so you're not going to
get uh...
nasty health effects
account but uh... this one is actually
this is the with a lot of april are
right mesoscopic no staff emily here
with i think that what is that he may be
the original design that they did with
ruby ridge and science
it's understood museum of modern art
sorrow
and ending this is the
the leading moka express
which is any combination start up a
special maker and the milk froth there
occurring
yet uh... if you had your looking here
at all actually to use some of the
steamed pushed through the milk
and uh...
certainty that combine a copyrighted and
ok seattle ones so what about your one
it's it's the one faction nasty ethnic
old or maybe a uh...
thirty intent as opposed to a thick
things that i think anti-semitism this
guy and it does take awhile to get it
going
in her and that i think we'll probably
decided going in and out of an accepted
ten that you know
the thing is that
one nice thing about this is it tells
you when it starts working it's gonna
make noise seattle
wait for to start gurgling ok we'll be
right back
spam
it's starting its little medicaid for
things that you know is reviewing its
teeming with uh... do nothing
now with the bigger ones you'll leave
martin luther king longer internally
once it starts curving when copy starts
coming out there who can actually for
heat up
alliances leading just let it depends on
its own strike
home
if you kept going in the back burner
copy it and it was you know she has
collectors even
the upper craft to the coffees and
danoff leap from improvement temperature
can you look at it intersects with the
pressure momentum
the feed them
general
was the finished
victory mobile but without the uh...
sort of greed and nature of french
pressed more and you can throw needs
across the room which unity with the
french press but it breaking
well there are some novel once these
days right facility
it and nobody municipal i think
what is your favorite do you drink it
straight or do you add what water to add
or are just reduced rate ok uh... the
six cup size it to the site here in will
fill one regular american coffee mugs so
size accordingly if you want to people
to have too good strong cups of coffee
her
would redeem themselves out of a
stripper in the morning handgun
technology
choice if you want to make it
one american size company francisco
you'd better at night
and that you can make you like something
up that's fine you can mix it with hot
water where with hotmail brutal picnic
and capping ole cafe au lait competitor
america missiles boop boop boop boop
queen along with his offices we're cfl
during its business magic castle grande
acquittal very interesting news
houses here is the finance finally put
fewer to did you think
creepy fifty quietly because out when
they were using just like trains click
happy howard price denounces
ridiculousness i mean i was not a
deterioration
quocuy quit
and
okay i will say it's the one that i have
a leading thing yourself quest
eighty-fifth equally just hang out and
sell quite fast spreading a mars and
co-conspirator press fifteen cloth slow
regularly quickly
quote so we are using of rocket what
actually happens to that area i would
have too expensive to think that i yet
whether i can get on the seventeen
hundred dollars for that day
internal report and bring unionized
bruin here content annexation mention in
the hospital it's common uses sparkling
water
in the filled and uh... you get a bit of
equipment
i'm not that they just something that we
say we definitely need to talk about
point
details when inside
that's very nice brute stone
obviously not through stress so we can
just kill political attitudes