you gently just put it in and fill it up like that.
this is a full cup
machine or what they call it in English
a stovetop expresso maker. I just like to
call the cafeteria.
you put the coffee in. some people to
really
squash it down but I don't like to
squash it down. I just like to level it out
so it makes the boiling water go through the
coffee. the more you squash it, the
stronger it comes. there you have it. so you just put
it on the fire.
this will be on fire.
what will happen is after
four five minutes the heated up water will kind of
rise through to go through the coffee
and come out of those two holes
on either side.
you can just
hang here for a few minutes. I like to
keep an eye on it so
you don't want the coffee to come up. you
might be doing something else and the coffee
is sitting in here
hot on the fire so it'll burn the taste of the coffee.
so you kind of
wanna
hang around. it will only take three or four minutes.
these cafeteria can
pretty much boil anyway. Good continental delis
will have them. the ones you really want to be looking for
are the Italian made ones. I mean there are ones made in China
and so forth
but the quality of them is not that good. There a lot of
places where they tend to leak on the Chinese ones.
So you
really want the Italian ones. the best
brand to buy from is Bialetti. They've been making them for
a hundred years. so
that is pretty much the top of the brand.
but there are other Italian brands.
as long as it's pretty much made in Europe
at least are the ones you
really wanna go for. they come in different sizes. This
one here prints it as
two cups size. there's a 3 cup, there's a 4 cup.
and they go up about to 12 cups. so you can
get some pretty big ones
if you're a big family.
the coffees you use are
the fresh ground coffee. or you can buy them in these packets
that are already prepacked. This is an Italian brand.
It's lavazza. It's one of the best brands you
can buy. that's pretty much
exported all around the world
so you'll be pretty hard pressed not to find this brand anywhere in the world wherever you are.
This is an
australin brand. They just brew really well, I mean I
can't fault these really as well. but depending on where you are
if you got a good local brand get that. you can get the
beans and ground them down
so you get them nice and fresh or you can just buy one of these.
now we just wait a while for the coffee to come up.
the coffee cups we normally use
are these ones here. These are the typical Italian size
coffee cups. They are quite small.
the italian coffee is quite strong.
It's not like you are drinking the americans type of coffee.
all you need is half a cup of coffee
and that's enough.
what you can do, what I normally always do
is in my coffee I always put
some sort of alcohol.
you just put a
dash in to it and it changes the flavour altogether.
it gives it that really nice refined
elegant touch of alcohol and really tasty.
But you can put in any type of alcohol into it
like you can put whisky, brandy.
Any type of alcohol.
Just try and add a little dozes and see how you go.
The way people move on now these days are these
new coffee machines. They're good if you're really in a rush.
I use these in the morning when I've to get to work. Put these on,
and
within 20 seconds you got a coffee.
however i still am a traditionalist and i still like my coffees to be done
the old fashioned way. They do have a different taste to
those kind of coffees. these type of typical coffees
retain their flavour more.
so we'll just wait for a second for the coffee to come up.
okay.
as you can see the coffee is starting
to come out. that took us about four to
five minutes.
just keep an eye on it and it'll take about 20
seconds to come up.
it's just the most beautiful fresh coffee.
really tasty.
Can't go wrong. you really gotta taste these
kinda coffees.
and it's clean coffee. There's no residue, there's
none of the coffee beans or anything coming through. It's just nice
clean crisp.
so when it's just about
still coming out, you'll see it will
start to bubble.
as soon as the water runs out that's when you know.
there you go. that shouldn't happen but it did.
now you take it off the fire.
you should put thelid down.
that is a safety precaution.
that was for demonstration purposes anyway. It's good that
you saw that so
now you know and you're not gonna burn yourself.
So once the coffee's out there you go. That's beautiful nice hot coffee.
you just pour it into your nice glasses.