you fill the water all the way to the safety valve
right there. you put the filter on.
at this point
you put some really good
quality coffee.
made a mess.
don't press it. just make sure that there is no coffee
on the side of the rim.
put the top part on. now lets go to the stove.
ok this is not my stove
so i'm not familiar with it. alright so now we are going to let it boil.
all the water will
percolate up the tube and we're
gonna have awesome coffee. we are going to wait for
that to
happen. alright so we have started getting some
percolation happening here.
as you can see it's coming out the tube
and it's filling the top canister.
I'm gonna close this top.
it's filling up
pretty fast. now this is how you know
that it's all done with the water. because it makes this sound. so at this point
you just turn it off. it's all set. now let's get a cup.
supposedly you should use one of these small
cups you know like the Italian cups but I
like a big cup of coffee
and a lot of milk.