simply fill the bottom chamber of the
espresso maker with water
up to the line. then put the
funnel-shaped filter in place
on top of the bottom chamber and fill it
with ground coffee.
the next step is to screw the top part
of the bialetti
onto the bottom part and once your
heat source is ready
in this case a burner for camping place
the espresso maker
over it. once the water is sufficiently
hot
it creates enough pressure in the bottom
chamber
to force itself up the funnel and through the
coffee grounds
splurting brewed coffee into the top
chamber
as you can see. when all that is done pour the coffee into your cups and enjoy your brew.