now what i do is I put this object here.
I'm going to take one of my tablespoons that I use for my
espresso macine.
I can use a different one but this one is a bit easier to
use.
Then I'm going to take that, pour it here.
I have a couple of skills that
I use but I don't use them for
coffee.
I don't really use them at all.
I like to think that human imperfection in things
actually
makes things taste better.
I'm gonna add anothe spoon here I think.
That's not too much.
you know when I got this moka pot it said
you're not supposed to tamp it down and I have a tamper for
my espresso machine
that i use.
This is the tamper.
now I'm putting this on the range.
for me because you're not
supposed to let it sit on the heat for
too long
what I do is when i hear burbling, I
open up the lid to see if it's pouring out then
I turn the heat off the moment
it stops going out and starts to
get
fizzy sort of.
so welcome back.
you can see the coffee is pouring in.
now as it reaches that mark
I go ahead and turn the heat off.
there we go.
It does smell kind of like chocolate.
I'm going to go get a cup.
so the problem with this
moka pot is that it starts to leak
when I pour coffee
from it. I'm gonna get two cups.
That's about a half cup. we'll just add more later.