you have water in here which you fill up to the valve till right about there.
you don't want to go over.
then the coffee holder
holds the coffee right above that.
you will notice it has lots of little holes.
so what happens when the water starts
boiling the steam pressure makes it go up
through the coffee.
even though
this is the coffee we're gonna use I've got
some already opened
in a container. the thing is once you open this
these are vaccum packed
bricks by the way. and you can get these
almost anywhere these days.
it goes on sale a lot.
But i have got some.
this is not Maxwell House crash rose but
you need to have some spoons or some sort of
way of getting it in here.
a coffee scoop works fine and
you need to fill this up.
it is not so important to tamp it down
as it is with some other fancier
machines.
some of the really
fancy machines like you get a restaurant
often they're made in Italy and
they rely on steam pressure but they are
pump driven. pump
gives you consistent steam pressure but
they also cost a lot.
so I am gonna tamp it down a little bit.
don't work my hands are clean.
I just washed them. that looks good.
then put the top on coz what happens is
when the
steam pressure goes through the coffee
grounds it comes out here at the top.
it comes down
and so after a little while you want
this
to be shut. but for some time you want to
see it come out and that's an
important part of doing this.
once you screw the top on here you want to leave it open so you can see when it first starts to come up.
I need to point out that this is the
three cup size. you can
get these
for anywhere from
six to ten dollars. depending on where you pick them up.
they come in different sizes.
this is the nine cup size.
I found this one
at bloom for eight dollars.
what a deal. this one
holds more. they may come up to 12 and I
think 15 cup size as well.
they make these small. the three cup size is about the best.
I have to point out that
I had to fix this because the handle
was about to break off. so I use a little
clamp.
gotta do what you gotta do. it
is not the best way but it works. now
an important part of this is the sugar. since this is the
three cup size we put in 3 spoonfuuls of sugar.
obviously if you have a sweet tooth
you could put in more
or if you don't like sugar you could do without it.
but i don't think it will be real cuban coffee.
it will be espresso but not cafe cubano.
okay. so you got the sugar.
then when you are ready put it on the
flame or stovetop. this is a gas
stovetop which is really much better
because it's easier to control what you are doing.
you can use electric but it gets a little difficult.
there we go.
it helps if you turn on the right one.
okay. so now we got the flame going.
so this next step is really important as it has to
do with the timiing. while we are waiting for the
coffee to come up because the steam pressure
is gonna bring it to the
top, you wanna have some
cups ready. these are demi task cups.
this does about 3 this size. maybe little small.
you also have them like this. anything
smaller than
a regular coffee cup. in just a few seconds we're gonna see
the first batch and this is
really important.
now at this point when coffee
first starts to come up its just a little bit
thicker.
right about there you close this and then
you put just a little bit in the sugar.
maybe about a quarter size. that's about
right.
put it back on the flame so it will continue brewing.
then you stir this up. this is the
secret.
this is what makes it look and taste like that.
fancy cup that you would
get from your favorite barista.
it gets to a kind of a paste.
if you want or if you have friends waiting
for this you can make
gurgling noises so they think you have an expensive machine
for the time necessary.
now this will start gurgling here
in a second. we'll see the steam
coming out. you can hear it.
it is just about ready.
I don't want to open this now. it will
be like mount vasuvius. okay.
it's ready.
pour it in here. keep stirring.