so once after having added the water, just put the coffee in.
I do oen scoop for one person.
now you can just tamp it down but it is really
important just to get an even spread
in packing down the coffee. you can use a spoon or a scoop as in this case.
justgoing to put the lid back on.
it's important here to make sure that you
screw it on nice and tightly
without any leaks. that way any pressure
build-up will go right through your freshly brewed coffee.
we don't want too much heat on the stove. just enough to
start it boiling up. one trick you can do is add
boiling water
when you are filling it up. it will speed up the
process.
this will take about five minutes.
so nw you will hear the freshly brewed coffee.
it is coming out of the top os the stovetop espresso.
now it's all finished.
now it's just time to pour freshly brewed coffee.