okay so as you see here I have the bottom
portion filled with water already.
you just slip this this middle portion
inside.
I'm going to get my first ground coffee.
which today is the
ethiopia saddama natural from social.
this
brewing method really brings out the
very flavour out of this
coffee. and it just really
highlights the great flavors about it.
I push it down slightly as
I'm putting it in here. level it off so that
you can have even extraction throughout the basket.
so I am just levelling.
and it's really important to make sure
you don't have any
grounds around this outside edge. so that it
doesn't get screwed down and
and block
the seal. now here's a little tip that
I wanna show you.
just put an extra amount there
in the center. that will help with
creating more pressure
and it brews a nice rich pot
this way.
so there we have it. It's clean around the edges.
you just simply screw down this top.
ok make sure it's nice and secure
so that the pressure builds up and
the water doesn't shoot up
out of the sides there like that. that's not what you want. so
you just sit there and let this brew.
use a medium heat.
so in about five to six minutes, the coffee will be ready.
okay so as you can see the coffee is
starting to brew now.
you can see how just how rich that
is.
so what I recommend is that while you are
brewing your coffee that
you actually boil a kettle as well
because this is
like double strength. then you can
you can drink it that way if that's
how you prefer.
but most people like to mix it
half and half with
some hot water.
after the brewing is complete
fill your mug to about halfway up.
Take your kettle and fill with water to the desired strength.