I just fill up
the filter basket to the top. Like this.
And you'll probably actually want a little bit more coffee than what I put in here.
But you'll just want to make sure that it's
nice and level.
while filling up the entire filter basket
you don't want to go over the edges. you
don't want any coffee around the edges.
so I'm gonna just remove the filter
basket real quick because I haven't
added my water yet
and I would recommend actually doing
that
before you do what I just did.
so before I mess anything up here and
spill coffee all over the ground
I will resume once I have the water
in there.
okay so once again you do not want
your water being too high up there.
I've used
this little notch (pressure release valve) once again
to kind of gauge how high the water
should be. If the water is too high it's
going to come up into the filter basket
before
the thing is even heated.
so here's my filter basket with the coffee.
You don't want to tamp this.
just keep it loose and
as evenly distributed as possible.
Ok? Like that.
We'll screw the lid on.
So, one of the things I really like about this coffee maker it's really easy to use.
one of the claims that people have is that
it's all
aluminum and whether there is
accurate research or not. people think
that leeched aluminum is terrible for your
health.
I am of the camp that doesn't believe
that.
I don't think there has been enough
research that has shown that
but even if it is bad for you
I'd much rather have aluminum in my final
cup of coffee then
unknown plastic chemicals.
so I'm gonna show you
how this works.
I'm just gonna put it on the stove
and have it running on low heat. The brew time itself is very
very long in my opinion. Takes at least
10 minutes.
as far as
portability goes this is probably the
best option. I'm going to take this
camping
over my Aeropress probably so I'll get more
coffee out of it.
it's very good I think it's better than
French press. so
I'll see you on the other end at the stove.
okay.
so let me first show you about how hot
or how high
your burner should be.
so this is too much it's too hot.
I have it down to about here.
so very low-heat. I'm not sure how these
are supposed to work on an electric stove.
I think it's fine but you'll wanna check
on that yourself with the manufacturer.
I think it says in the instruction booklet.
other reviewers also have information on
that
but basically a very low flame is what
you want.
once you start hearing that hissing
noise
you'll notice that coffee starts to brew and
come out of the spouts here and it
should come out in
an espresso-esque color.
so you'll see
some creaminess but this isn't espresso. It doesn't have enough
bars of pressure to make it
espresso, officially.
Hence, the moka name. so it's a different type of coffee
but a very good one, very rich, lots of
oils.
so I'd say it's most similar French
press but
much more low maintenance. you don't have to do any plunging
stirring or any of that nonsense
and
it's also much easier to clean, and I'll show you
that whole process after this is done
brewing.
So once it starts to brew, I'll turn the camera back on
so you can see what it looks like.
Ok. So we're about 5-7 minutes in
and you can already see
the coffee coming out of the spout at the top
and you can hear
that
sizzle if you will.
here's what I was talking about.
I don't know if you see what's going on but
the flames are starting to go crazy because
water is seeping out of the sides here.
so thats one of the downsides of this coffee maker.
I don't
know if maybe I'm doing something wrong
and that's definitely possible
but it doesn't seem really have an
impact on on
the overall output. it doesn't really
create a mess. Just something to note.
Some of that water is lost on the side
so you can see
or maybe you can't... the very rich
looking coffee. got something
that's close...I mean it isn't crema. But it looks delicious.
maybe that's where it
gets its moka name...the dark color of it.
the question...this is another downside.
you do have to
keep an eye on this thing because once
the coffee stops
coming out of the top there or it starts to look
clear that's when you want to take this
thing off the heat.
So you're not going to get any beep of course to tell you when it's done, you'll just have to keep an eye on it.
so already it's starting to look a
little bit thin and watery.
so I'll want to be taking it off
the burner any second now.
In fact, I think I'll do that right now.
so there's a look at it.
I'm gonna pour it out to show you what I was talking about...
this is enough coffee for
one of these mugs.