Fill the bottom of the pot with water to about the center of the pressure
valve. now put the basket in place.
to make sure you didn't put too much
water in the bottom tap the basket.
if water comes up you have a little too
much. the moka pot is made to make an
exact amount of coffee.
you really need to put the right amount
of water in the pot.
next we'll fill the filter basket with
fine ground.
use six or seven grams of coffee per
ounce. today for our coffee
we're using a Parisi coffee original
espresso Blend.
this is a fantastic espresso
that's truly small batch roasted with the
flavor profile
constructed specifically for this kind of
coffee making.
so how do you know just how fine the
coffee needs to be ground.
one simple way is to go to your nearest
grocery store.
buy a small amount of coffee beans, maybe a
quarter pound and grind it in the stores
coffee grinder.
just like this one. grind it on the
espresso setting
and use this as your control sample. so
you know what the coffee should look
like
when you grind it at home. you want to
make sure there's no coffee
in the stores grinder before you
prepare your sample. loosely fill this
basket and don't pack it down.
it's okay if the basket is just over
filled. now we screw the top piece on tightly.
settle it on the stove. watch and listen.
when you see the steam and hear the pot
rumbling, yur coffee is ready.