this is a very traditional grinder.
The best place to store beans
is not outside, is not in
the fridge
but in the freezer. the best place to store beans.
so we're going to grind the beans now.
you can play a little game when you grind the beans. Pretend you're
at the cup final.
Milan versus Barcelona.
or you could think you're in Spain.
Beans are done.
Fill water.
Fill it there like I said. Up to that level.
There. Perfect. Pop it in.
if you have you too much water it'll become quite evident here
it'll come to the hose. In this case it hasn't happened therefore
we filled it properly. Get your coffee.
watch this now. this is very important.
don't press it. don't tamp it. It doesn't like
being tampered with.
so you just fill it up.
make a little mound. if it's higher, it doesn't matter
because it'll just be a bit stronger.
That's okay. there's no problem with that.
put it on. Make sure there's no water in here after washing.
now we'd like to cook it.
because this ting is so high up from the element,
it takes a long time. so i do this.
put it right on top of the element.
this may not always work in your house. your
kitchen your oven might be different
from this one. here is how we light it.
this is very old fashioned.
we turn it down, not too high because it will burn the handle.
put it on here like that
and you wait
for the horses to come. which is what we call
the steam stampede. now with this coffee
would like espresso.
George Clooney and John Mackey
each with their artificial coffee
in those plastic containers. try opening one
before you make coffee. open one of those espresso
coffee and see what's in there and  Smell it.
it is full
of preservatives, artificial stimulants
everything. and furthermore, it is wrapped in
plastic. I have a theory about plastic.
my theory is that the only thing that
should be stored in plastic is a penis.
we go back here again. Condoms of
course I was referring to.
Nothing else should be put in plastic. Plastic is a
petrochemical
and it leaks into the product. we don't worry about
the semen business. we are not talking about that now. We are cokking here now at the
moment. this is not a program about sex not
to be confused.
by the way ladies and gentlemen watching if there
are any
children watching this program it might
be best
to send them off to some other room now because this cook
is liable to say anything. thank you.
now I have another theory about coffee
because I'm a purist about coffee.
number one is I don't use sugar and I don't use milk.
I have a theory about milk.
cow's milk is for baby cows. Sheep milk
is for baby sheep. Goat's milk is for baby goats.
for us humans if you are going to use milk then
it should be
breast milk. because we can't do this.
but we use soya milk.
but then again as I say I don't really
totally approve of milk in coffee.
Soya milk. Organic
soya milk.
The best way to cool coffee
believe it or not is cold coffee
from a previous brew.
what you should always do when you make
coffee is make more of it than you want.
The coffee that you leave over,
you put it in a jug and you put it in
the fridge. cold coffee
to cool hot coffee. what can be more logical
than that?
why would you be tainting you coffee
with something other
than coffee. if you want pure coffee you
cool it with coffee.
but we don't always think like that.
therefore, the next best thing to cool
coffee is water. because that's what
coffee is made with.
now because we're having just a little
amount of coffee, I'm going to go and get some very small cups.
so we are going to go ahead now with the
preparation of the coffee.
Pretty nice
Regina's cups that she imported from
Italy.
some of you might have
nice organic chocolate whipped coffee
this time of the day. we have some nice organic choclate.
the coffee should be nearly ready now. I'd like
you to watch what is happening here. because this is a
very important part
of the process. watching the coffee
coming through the mountaintop. it is
basically like a beautiful orgasm is how
I've always described it in my cokkery books.
but today because if the children are still
watching perhaps I shouldn't say that.
in effect
this is a mokaorgasm. watch it now here.
the coffee is just coming through.
you are going to hear it. the steam stampede.
Listen.
Listen to the horses coming.
can you hear them? when the hosrses are just
close you know exactly.
now you make the horses go away again. they have
just passed the House.
brewing coffee like this
touches the 5 senses. Sight
sound taste
smell and we touched the beans.
An espresso? What is an espresso? why would
anybody want to
drink an espresso? can you tell me that? we
are now going to taste the coffee.
so you watch this,
this is liquid gold.
this is the ultimate taste.
this is opium.
the opium of masses.