the maximum amount of water regardless of the size of your stovetop maker that you want to use
is right up to this boiler valve. you want to have
this boiler
valve above the water level. so can see that also inside.
so once we fill out the water then we
take our funnel and our grounds.
we loosely fill the espresso grounds
into the funnel. we don't wanna pack it or
tamp it
for these makers because the maximum
pressure they produce
is basically whatever they can produce
by water boiling and that is not
very strong. so in order for the water to
percolate through the grounds
you only wanna fill it up loosely into the funnel.
then you kind of use your finger to level
it a little bit. put the funnel back into the boiler and then
just screw the
top compartment back on the boiler.
so that's that. that's all we have to do
for our espresso. so we put that aside.
prepare the milk frother.
so now we are gonna prepare our milk frother
which is even easier compared to preparing
the espresso. all you
do is you take the milk frother.
take our milk and fill that into the frother.
this is a 6-cup.  translate into about
fluid ounces completely filled. but the way
you want to do it is
you only wanna fill these about one-third of
the frother up to a half.
that's the max you should do. because you need some
air on top
for the froth to expand of course and
also to have some sort
of air circulation.
you can pretty much use any type
of milk you want. cold milk froth as well. warm milk
froth is
fantastic. the perfect
temperature
for warm milk to forth is about a
hundred
and forty five to a hundred and fifty degrees farenheit. if it is too hot
it kind of changes the consistency
of the milk and you can
have this sort of a white liquid that you don't want.
so if you want to have a
nice creamy cup of cappucino with a nice
firm and airy froth then you wanna
not exceed 150
degrees. one note to the lid. the lid is not
sealing the frother. it's not supposed to seal it. so
when you ultimately froth, you will see some
milk
and spilling or froth explanding on the edge of the
lid which is totally normal. it's not going to splatter all
over the place. but it's just not sealing
the frother because it has to leave
some air in the frother. to not create a vacuum inside
otherwise you couldn't froth and also to provide some sort
air circulation
for the froth to expand. so spilling or milk coming out
of the side
on the lids, on the top is completely normal. so basically that's
all we have to do. now we just have to put it on
the stove
and it takes about 4 to 5 minutes.
so the next thing we have to do is simply
take our espresso maker, put it on the
heat source. you wanna use a
medium high setting. you don't wanna exceed medium high.
you want to have a gentle process of brewing. it really
doesn't save
you much time. so uses a medium high setting
that doesn't burn your espresso and has a good impact on the
taste of the espresso.
then we use the body of our milk frother without the plunger
of course. also put this on the stove. also in this case use a medium high setting.
as I mentioned before the perfect temparature for frothing
milk is about a 145 to 150 degrees farenheit.
i think it's very useful to use a
thermometer. i mean while doing it you kind of
get the feeling
when the perfect temparature is reached. the thermometer really takes the guesswork out of it. makes
it much easier. so i'm using a thermometer. put it in the milk on the side of the milk frother.
if it reaches about a 140 145
just switch it off. now this is the perfect temparature.
once the milk reaches the proper temperature
which again is about a 145 to 150 degrees farenheit
and once your espresso is done brewing
all you have to do is take it off the stove and pour yourself a nice creamy
cup of cappucino. we do recommend using oven mitts
to do so
because especially if they are made of stainless
steel
the handles can get quite warm. you want to make sure you
don't burn yourself.
so frothing a moka is very easy.
all you have to do is you take your milk
and you take the plunger and the lid.
put the plunger on the top
of your frother.
you see I am doing it very lightly.
you can achieve different results if you froth it a little longer.
it kind of creates a firmer froth if you
like I do froth just a few times you have
a very nice
airy froth.
so all that's left to do now is so
simply take your espresso and pour into your cups.