you don't want to use any less because
it needs that quantity to perform
properly.
you know if you fill up over that little valve
then it's not gonna function properly if
you build up too much pressure.
this is a little funnel.
so we will put that in and this is what you use
to put your coffee in.
so I am just going to take a preground coffee
of course just for ease. but for best
results you wanna grind it on demand
just before you brew.
so best to use a medium setting.
you don't want to grind it as fine
as you would use for an espresso machine.
but you don't wanna
grind it as coarse as you might for a drip.
somewhere in between usually works best.
its a bit forgiving. you don't have to be
precise.
so now i am going to go ahead and just
evenly put in the coffee in here. there is no
need to compress it
or tamp it down too. you can't have it compressed.
it needs to be loose so that water can flow
through.
so as you can see I've filled up the
top funnel with the preground coffee.
it's all just loose. you don't wanna
pack it in as I was saying. otherwise it's not
gonna let them water through
at the speed you need. next step
is to put this together.
so you've got with your stove top there will be a
a silicon ring that's going to form a
neat seal here for you.
a little filter screen that's
gonna stop a lot of
the grinds getting through into your actual
drink. so we put this together.
filter in.
and then put the ring in.
then easy as screwing the two together.
so you wanna do that
until it's just tight. not too tight otherwise
you will
wreck it. just enough to form a neat
tight seal.
now once that's on
nice and firm, the next step. step 3 I
guess.
just pop it on to medium
heat on your hot plate and
start the brewing process. so you wanna take care
not
to get your handle over the direct
source
of your heat. so if you're using gas or a burner
you don't want obviously the hot heat up
on this handle.
You're going to need to grab on to it. You don't
want to melt it. if it's something like an electric
one here
just keep it off to the side so it's
not in direct heat. these handles are
designed to stay relatively cool to touch.
so then of course this is going to take
probably
you know about five minutes to happen.
we'll come back when it starts to starts
to brew. so I'll take a few minutes just to
explain what's happening in the process
of brewing this coffee.
so the nature of a stovetop or a house design is
that you filled up the bottom reservoir
with cold filtered water.
by applying the heat source what it's going
to do is heat that water
of course creating steam which is going
to build up
pressure in this bottom compratment. the pressure
that builds up in there once it gets to
the right point
is going to start forcing that heated
water up through the bottom of that funnel
and go through the coffee grinds
which is going to be the extraction of
the coffee.
The brewed espresso is then
going to come out
of the top of this spout here
any into this sort of holding reservoir
at the top.
that's where the coffee ultimately
finishes its Brew.
as i was saying it's important not to
have the heat too high
because what that will is burn the
coffee is one thing
heat the water too quickly and too hot.
you want to avoid that. so that's why I
suggest a medium heat to start with.
you want to experiment what's best for
you.
you know some people might find they need a hotter
heat or a lower heat
depending on their stoves. this is still
just heating up gently.
now unlike a high espresso
or a proper espresso brewed under
extreme pressure there is not going to be that
lovely thick golden crema that you get at the top
of those
extractions. what you'll find is
a small amount of crema sitting on top. I
suppose you can call it that.
you'll see when the brew happens
what's going on there.
basically you don't get that
rich thick
honey like crema that you would of a
high-pressure extraction because this is
the pressure and this is not quite as much.
some of the things that I like to use
the espresso for of course it's a lovely
smooth
way to brew your coffee and tends to
get rid off a lot of
the bitterness.
we can start to hear that bubbling up in the
bottom now.
it seems to balance out the flavors
really well. I find that they are usually quite
a smooth
coffee to drink.
I really quite full boil it though
so they do stand up quite well to milk.
if you like to heat milk and
use the espresso
in that to make your sort of froth whites and
things that's
also a good way to serve it.
here we go. as you can see the coffee just
starts to gently pour out the top.
if this is happening too quickly or
it's flowing out really fast then you
know you've got the heat too high.
so what we are gonna do is sort of watch this
brewing.
I like to use a bit of a gauge
when
it's about three-quarters two-thirds
three-quarters full I like to remove it
from the heat source.
because you don't want to run the
bottom hot dry.
So I'm going to take it off the heat now. It's nearly done.
so basically it's running out of water
now to push up through the funnel.
this extractions is pretty well complete.
So what i do is i sort of just let that sit
to finish bubbling away and we'll be back in
a few moments. so now that the brew is
complete all serve it up just like I would
here
at home. if you are after a more long
black style of drink, simply pour out your desired amount of coffee.