You can use tap water or filter water, whatever you prefer. you wanna make sure you fill it right below or right on the valve on the side of the
pot.
then we place that funnel looking thing
that I probably should know what it's
called in English
and place it inside the Pot. after that we
put our coffee inside the pot.
you can either make a little mountain
like I am doing, depressing the coffee in
while we screw the top part on
or you can compress it as you put it in.
then we screw on the top as tight as we
can to make sure to coffee won't come out
from the side.
we simply put it on the stove over low heat
to prevent the coffee from burning
because that would suck. you will have to make
the coffee all over again while the
pot is still burning hot
and that is no fun.
then you just have to wait five or six
minutes until you see the coffee
starting to come out from the holes
inside the pot.