These are the beans. Close the top.
Put the leveer in the container and grind it well.
No more beans.
so what
we do next. take the moka pot.
So
ideally you wouldn't put water more
than
above this vavle.
There is a little rim inside. you can use that as a measure.
I don't know if you can see it.
just put little bit above it.
just a tiny bit.
Ideally
Bialetti uses this as a measure
for the water and you put it back.
I personally never use it.
Get your filter.
make sure that it is dry.
then you drop in your coffee.
so one thing you don't want to do is
compress it. if you
tamp it
for example you are going to have a problem
with the taste.
it's going to be bitter. the water
with take longer to go up
and you will over do the coffee.
you don't want to go over the rim as well.
I have a bit less.
it is OK.
but never go over. okay.
so
just screw it together.
Make it tight. Just don't screw it too tight
there will be problem later. That's great.
put it back on the stove.
Just put it on fire.
you can leave the top opened or closed. doesn't matter.
there is this valve on the brikka. so the coffee actually doesn't
spill out
like a normal moka pot.
instead this here just increases the
pressure.
usually the moka pot
it will have one and a half power
of pressure due to the steam that is
generated
at the bottom. this one because
of this valve should do around
two, two and half. I'm not even sure about it.
when there is enough pressure
the coffee will push the
valve up and it would make
a crema park.
I can tell you that the crema is kind of fake. it looks nice
but once you put it in the glass there is not much
left to be honest. you will also see that when you put it in the glass
it kind of gets pale.
the coffee will take about
three minutes.
Don't use an extra fine
grind
for the coffee. I use it a bit
coarse. I have it not too coarse but just a bit
coarse. It just goes better in my opinion.
I also read that it helps with the flowing.
when you see this you want to turn off
the heat.
okay it looks nice.
I'm going to pour it.