They say to fill it up to that line. so we're going to do that.
you don't wanna go more than that
because
then when you put your
coffee grounds in you wanna make sure
that the water doesn't come up in this
area because you don't want to get your
coffee grounds
wet before you actually make your coffee.
so take this over here.
I have some coffee already ground
in my grounder here.
Finely ground
espresso coffee.
okay I have put the coffee
into the basket. you'll notice I've got it
pretty well
full but they caution you
not to pack it. if you pack the
coffee
grounds in there you could cause
the steam not to come through the way
it should.
you could build up pressure in that.
That wouldn't be a good thing. okay so now I'm
gonna
screw the top on and set it on the stove
top
and we'll see what it does.
we have the top screwed on.
something I neglected to mentiona while ago is
around the top of the
coffee basket you have to make sure that it
stays good and clean.
When you screw it back together so that you
make good seal between the bottom and the top.
there is a rubber gasket in there that you want to
make sure that
it is clean.
you don't want to get coffee grounds in
there.
we will look here and
once we start
seeing some steam coming from the bottom
we'll actually start seeing coffee come
out. okay im starting to hear something going
on.
It's been about three minutes and
I don't know if you can hear it or not but you can actually
hear
the steam making a little racket in the bottom
of the pot down there.
what we ought to be seeing here just in a
minute
is some good espresso coffee coming up
through that
little thing in the center there. when
it does we'll have to close the top down
because
after the coffee comes out it starts
blowing a little bit of steam out and it'll spew
out here
in the kitchen. we don't want that.
there we go.
there comes the espresso.
okay.
in just about another minute or two it's
gonna start
making a little bit of chuga chuga chuga sound
and you know it's just about done.
I think it's about done.
and the way you can tell it's finished
is when it stops making that noise.
okay so it's just about that point.
when all the water in the bottom has
been converted into steam and that steam has
come up through the
coffee grounds it will be quiet.
so let's see how our bialetti espresso maker
actually did. Let's see what kind of espresso we got.
Looks pretty good to me.