All the italians I've ever seen
use water right out of the tap.
Now that the base is filled with water, you want to put the filter
into the bottom. And it fits really easily.
Then you're going to fill the filter with
coffee grounds. The only important thing is to not pack the
grounds tight. Because if they're packed too tight, the water can't escape.
You'll just be basically baking the moka on the stove.
Now that that's finished, you wanna take the top part
and screw it really really tight to the base.
Because if it's
not tight, water will leak out all over your stove and trust me, it has happened to me a lot of times.
Now we're ready to brew
our espresso. And you want to use a flame that's
in between low and medium. Because if the flame is too high the water
goes through the coffee really fast and doesn't pick up any of those
great aromas or flavours. So our italian espresso should be ready
in about 5 minutes. So our moka has been on the stove
for a few minutes. so I'm gonna open the lid
and check
if we are brewing espresso.
see how it's coming out of the little metal part in
the middle.
do you hear that? that rumbling
sound is your moka telling you your
delicious espresso is
ready. so when you hear this sound,
take it off the
flame immediately. Because it's
done.
Look. You have a whole pot of coffee inside. If you like sugar
or the people that you're making coffee for
like sugar you can add it
right into the moka. So now your coffee is pronto.
it's ready to drink. we just have to drink it.