you can see where you're filling the water by looking
inside the coffee maker.
okay.
next we're going to fill the
coffee basket
with coffee.
of course a great cup of coffee
depends on using great coffee.
I only use coffee from la colombe.
so you fill the coffee basket with coffee. it's important
that you don't pack down the coffee.
you just leave it kind of loose
inside the basket
so that it can brew properly.
and you set the basket inside
the bottom.
next you put
the coffee pot on top by fitting it on one side
and locking it on the other side.
you put the stovetop coffee maker on the stove.
you set it over heat that
is high enough to cook the coffee
but not so high that the flames come
over the side of the coffee maker.
and you wait for the coffee to brew.
the coffee is starting to brew.
you can see the coffee filling the coffee pot. you wanna leave the lid closed while this is happening
to let the coffee brew.
so open up the lid.
make sure the coffee has stopped
coming out into the receptacle.
look like it has.
so your coffee is done.
now ususally what i do is
i make a latte so i put some milk into my mug.
then i heat it in the microwave
for about fifty seconds. it gets nice and
warm.
kind of sweet when the milk heats up.
pour the coffee into the mug and enjoy.