first fill the bottom chamber with cold
water up to the line.
second put the funnel filter in place
over the bottom chamber like this.
fill it
with coffee ground.
third screw the top chamber onto the
lower part and heat the espressomaker.
All of the bialetti moka express is equipped
with a pressure release valve. for maximum safety
stay close to your coffeemaker
while it's brewing. As the water is
heating, pressure is building up in the
lower chamber forcing the water up the
filter funnel and into the upper chamber.
you know your coffee is ready when you
don't hear the coffee
splashing inside the upper chamber anymore.
now it's ready.