You fill it up and after you do that, you grind the coffee.
I pick the Brazil Esperanca
coffee that we have because
brazilian coffees are sweeter and they
tend to be more forgiving in the moka pot.
Canion coffees are going to be a
little bit more earthier and a little bit
more vegital.
they don't normally work. for just boiling in the moka pot
I like coffees that are
sweeter.
at home when I grind my coffee I just
look in my
little tiny coffee grinder that I have
and grind it to
somewhere finer than what would be a
paper filter.
this guy goes inside here. you
actually want that kind of full.
everybody doesn't have these at their
house probably even though we do because we
are espresso Dorks.
if you don't then you just use a spoon and you press
it down as fast as you can.
so that it's basically even and you can tap the side of it
to make it even. you want to put the top
back on here
but you want to use a towel so you don't burn your little
fingers. so you just grab it and you twist the top on.
then it goes on here and you
turn the volume back up again
and wait untill the pot starts to make funny
little noises called the first sneeze
or something. when it starts making noises you
know that it is
sucking the coffee up.
it might take a while on this contraption.
while you're waiting you can play with
your knives. try not to burn the
handle
while waiting for it to boil. it's starting to get there
kind of.
if you're using a gas stove
it does not take this long.
It's starting
to do a bubbling thing. you can see the steam coming out
of it and so you really wanna turn it off.
actually take it off of the heat. all the liquid is
gonna come up into the top
part of the moka pot. you're gonna have coffee in it.
it's going to be
really strong thick coffee that's not
grainy like
French press coffee and it's going to be very
good if you did it the right way.
it makes two normal size cups of coffee or one giant size cup of coffee.