fill the water in. they have this emergency valve that will
start spitting out if it gets too much pressure
inside.
you just fill the water up to a little bit below that and then you put your favorite coffee.
this is an espresso coffees that
at Walmart I bought. I buy whole beany
and grind it myself.
I am not packing, I am just moving it around a little
but and those little light bits you see
is actually a Coco.
I got this coco bean
that's ground up and i added that.
just a little bit to give it a little extra
flavour. on the bottom of the
moka pot you can see a filter and a rubber gasket.
on the inside there is a post. the thing i like about
this moka pot
is the post in the center where the coffee
comes out
is pointed downward so it won't sputter
out of the top.
I've got a couple of other moka pots that sputter
actually kinda bad.
if i leave them on and i leave the room, i will
come back
and find coffee all over the place. this is a
stainless steel. so you can use it on a induction
cooktop.
this doesn't take very long. I was
actually kinda surprised.
my other moka pots
take 4 5 minutes to cook to come up to
temperature.
this one doesn't take long at all and
I'll go ahead and show you here just
how long
it does take.
as you can see i've already made a pot. just to kind of test it out.
I've been using it for a while now.
I've really tried some nice coffees.
the moka pot works really well. it's stainless
steel.
you may be able to see. we've got some scruffing
here
where I was doing this right on this
induction cooktop and
I accidentaly dropped this plastic bag against
it. it melted the bag on to it.
so i just scraped it off.
before I took just a minute or two
and here i am at
three minutes and the coffee is percolating already.
it'll be done here pretty quick.
it's a really handy moka pot and as you can see it's
pretty fast too.
I was actually kinda surprised at how fast it
was. but that's the
bialetti venus moka pot. I really
enjoyed
doing the review.
we're done. some fresh. not exactly espresso
but some really good fancy coffee.