so we are going to add the water in now. probably about three fourths of
the way. that's good. the second part is the filter and
this is where the ground espresso goes. you only want to use
ground espresso. if you try to use ground coffee
the taste will be very different and very weak.
you don't want that. you really want to use the espresso. It's a
stronger
coffee roast. so we go ahead and pack that lightly.
I like my brew strong so I am going to put
a little bit more in and we go ahead and add that.
now the top part is called the upper chamber which has a stem.
now what happens is the water will boil from the bottom and
go through the ground espresso
and will come right up into this upper chamber. that's where we pour it from.
so we go ahead and put the top on.
you want to make sure that you screw it very tightly.
we don't want any water to leak out from the
sides. then we put it on the edge of the burner and
turn it to high. now this is a glass stovetop and you can use this on any stovetop
but if you are using a
gas stovetop, you want to have it more towards the center.
if that's a problem because of your opening
you can purchase like plates that sit right on top
and allow you to put something without having to worry about it tipping in. so we are going to give this just a few minutes to heat up.
we'll hear it boiling and our espresso will be ready.
I can tell our espresso is done.
it stopped making the boiling noise. so i want to turn this off.
now keep in mind why i said to put this on the edge of the burner.
I can touch this handle, it's not hot. so it keeps it away from the heat.
if that's not possible with your type of stove
use an oven mitt or a pot holder to protect your hand
and simply move it to another burner.
let it sit and cool just for a minute or so or just pour it right away.
make sure you are protecting your hand. we wanna go ahead and pour this
right into our espresso cups. hope you found this
video useful. now you know how to use a stovetop espresso maker.