if you fill it above the valve. does that cause an issue?
they just recommend not to just for
safety reasons. if
you over heat it with the valve submerged
it may not open properly and release the pressure.
okay.
then you insert your basket
and
add your coffee.
we are using lavazza crema gusto
traditional
european stove top
espresso blend. what's
the grind like compared to an espresso. the grind is
not
quite as fine as the espresso
grind but you want it
a little finer than what we use for
drip coffee.
so somewhere in the middle like a fine drip.
that would work
just fine. dandy.
one downside with the
stovetop units is
you have to make it to capacity.
you can't make a short
pot.
so i couldn't say it's just
me so i was going to put enough coffee
and water in for one shot. the
one stove top maker we offer that does
give you some options
that's the ilsa.
that this guy here. it is
unique in that the basket
comes with a little insert. so you can
either fill it full
or you can put the insert in and half fill it
and use half as much water.
so it's a little more flexible.
right. okay.
because this is going to form sort of a puck
like an espresso machine
just filling one of these half with water
is not really gonna work because
because the coffee is going to be pushed up
against this screen. so it's half full
it's not gonna get
pushed against the screen.
and uh... basically do you need that as
sort of like a pressure element with the
building up that steam and getting that water through.
got it.
nice thing about
these stovetop units is they
basically last forever.
the only wear item is the gasket.
my wife and i have been using the
same gasket for over a year now.
a fair amount of use. short of
you know breaking the plastic handle
there is nothing to go wrong with these.
so before we start this guy
we just have a few models. this
is specifically the musa which is
the brushed.
then there's the venus which is the shiny.
then the elsa models that you were talking about.
overhear we have the bottom
chamber which is double walled.
they do have a double wall for more heat retention.
okay then this of course is the
bialetti
moka pot. the original one.
made of aluminum but it's chrome
plated aluminum so you're not going to
get
nasty health effects.
this is the one that a lot of people are
familiar with.
I think this might be the original design.
it's on display at the museum of modern art.
it's iconic.
and then this is the
the bialetti moka express
which is the combination of a moka stovetop espresso maker and a milk frother.
if you add your milk here
it will actually use some of the
steam to push through the milk.
so does it combine the coffee and the mil together then. yes. okay.
it's the one touch of a stovetop espresso maker.
okay so we are going to start this guy and it does take a while to get it going.
so i think we'll probably
just get it going and then come back when it's up to
temp.
one nice thing about this is it tells
you when it starts working. it's gonna
make noise. so we will
wait for it to start gurgling. ok we'll be
right back.
it's starting its little magic. you can see the steam coming out. it's gurgling, it's
steaming, it's doing its thing.
now with the bigger ones you wanna leave
them on the heat a little bit longer. but generally
once it starts gurgling and the coffee starts
coming out you can actually cut
the heat off.
just let it do it's own thing.
if you kept going would that burn
the coffee then because it was too much heat.
yeah.
because at that point you are heating the upper craft too that the coffee is in and
you can get an off flavour from too much temperature.
can we look at it or do we need to keep the
pressure.
you can see the coffee spouting out.
you see it's a nice
thick brew but without the
sort of greedy nature of french
press. you can throw one of these
across the room which you can't with the
french press without it breaking.
well there are metal ones now these
days.
what is your favorite. do you drink it
straight or do you add what water to it.
i genereally drink it straight. the
six cup size which is this size here will
fill one regular american coffee mug. so
size accordingly if you want two people
to have two good strong cups of coffee
for
dragging themselves out of a
stooper in the morning.
if you want to make
one american size cup at a time the six cup would be better.
you can mix it with hot
water or with hot milk. you can make a cafe au lait or cafe
americano so to speak.
now it's really going. even though the heat is off you can see it's really doing its business. the magic of steam pressure
discovered by archimedes thousands of years ago
now finally put to good use.
totally because when
they were using just like trains
powered by steam that was just
ridiculous. i mean that was just not a
good application.
okay i will trust you on that one. i will let you edit yourself.
so you just hang out until
it stops spuritng anymore.
the heat is off.
we are done brewing. Got a nice brew here. And actually I should mention in
Italy it is common to use sparkling water
in the fill and you get a bit of
crema to it.
we definitely need to try it out.
that's very nice brew.
It's obviously not true espresso but you can
just tell by the color that it's more than just coffee.