That's probably enough.
now I set my coffee grinder to
espresso. which is a very fine
setting.
top off. coffee in.
the grinder
makes a nice even grind.
It's good enough to make espresso.
Tamp it down just to smooth it over.
so this can screw on tightly.
there we go.
turn the burner on high. put that
there.
it'll take a couple of minutes to start boiling.
what happens is, it's not a percolator. the
water
turns to steam down here and is forced up
through the filter and then up
through this little hole under there
and off the top and it fills up the top of
the pot. it makes a very strong
cup of coffee. it tastes a lot like espresso.
I'm going to stop it right here and come back.
the water is not boiling yet.
it even let's it cream up like
real espresso.
similar process it is just that the pressure
isn't quite as much as a
real espresso machine.
I'm gonna close this coz when it starts to
boil, steam comes out the top
and it makes a mess.
You can hear it boiling now.
Better take it off the burner.