fill the lower chamber with water almost up to the safety release valve. never overfill and never let
anything inside or outside the moka pot
cover the safety release valve. the only
proper way to use a moka pot is to
fill it up
to the point just under the safety
release valve.
insert the funnel-shaped coffee basket
into the lower chamber stem first.
then add espresso ground coffee to the
basket.
do not grind the coffee any finer than
an espresso level grind.
true espresso is tamp down so that it
forms a park.
but for the moka pot gently pack the
coffee into the basket
but don't tamp it down.
finally replace the collecting chamber
over the unit and screw it tightly into
place.
when everything is ready set the moka
pot onto the stove.
ideally you should have a burner that
fits the pot.
but this is the smallest burner on my
stove. turn the heat to medium-high.
in about 4 to 5 minutes you may hear a
slight hissing
or rumbling as the brewed coffee makes
its way up the stem.
you can open the pot to check the
progress. when about a third of the
coffee has collected in the chamber
lower the heat. when about half to
two-thirds of the coffee has collected
in the chamber
turn off the heat and remove the moka pot from the burner.
the water in the lower chamber is so hot that it will finish the process.