take our water, pour it right in.
just below the hinge as I said. now cubans
like their coffee really really strong. so we're going to take
this.
your favorite espresso. you cna use pilon or
whatever you find in your local grocery
stores. take a spoon
and you are gonna want to fill it very very genereously.
usually cubans actually pat their coffee down. so use your spoon and pat it down.
you pretty much want to fill it all the way to the top.
this makes about 4 cups
so it's gonna be about four tablespoons or so of coffee.
but as i said you want to make sure you fill it right up
and pat the coffee down.
then we're gonna close our espresso.
now it's really important
you put it on the smallest burner and when you
turn it on you want to
have the handle towards you so that
it doesn't get really hot as well.
alright
so you're gonna turn your stove on not too high to about 8 or 9.
then what we are actually gonna do is we are gonna take
some sugar in order to make some foam.
now here's what you really want to watch.
once you see the first
little bit of coffee you are gonna want to basically mix it. now
cubans like their coffee pretty sweet too. so it's gonna be about 4 teaspoons since we are making about 4 cups of coffee.
so you fill it in this little
bowl. then you watch the coffee and
make sure that once you see the first little bit of
coffee we arejust gonna pour it in there and mix it.
that is actually gonna be our foam.
so let's watch. once it starts making that noise
you pour a little bit in. so gonna pour that out. just that first little bit to make our foam.
put it back.
meanwhile we are gonna
mix our sugar with that first little bit of coffee.
so you see it kind of makes a little creamy like brown milky consistency.
then we are just gonna add the coffee right in there.
so it's gonna be really good.
so once that's done we are just gonna turn the oven off.
safety first. then we're gonna take the
coffee pour into our little foamy sugar
mixture. careful you don't want to burn yourself.