I never knew anybody
a who use these in Italy who preheated the
water.
so the water just gets added. Rather
the cold water just get added to the
bottom reservoir. the manual that
comes with this will say something about
filling water until you get to the
registration marks or to the water level
marks.
just as someone who spent a lot of time
looking for them there are no such marks.
what you wanna do is you want to fill the
water just up to below where the valve
is. so just under the valve by
like a centimeter. if you don't
have a valve in your moka pot
and you are a daring soul who wants to use it anyway
the way to see how to fill the
water is to make sure that no water
intrudes into
this funnel-shaped grounds cone
when it's inserted all the way. so you can
hold it on the side and see about where
the bottom of this
funnel is. pop it inside to
make sure that
no water comes up through
this filter cone or filter
funnel
and that's how much water you should have. as
much as you can get in without intruding
into this.
to fill this once again probably the
ideal would be
freshly ground locally roasted
firstly roasted coffee
grounded at something less than an
espresso grind.
now the grind for this the proper grind
is finer than a filter coffee grind
and not as fine as an
espresso grind.
if you get it too fine that's when you get
problems with an overpressure situation
in the the bottom part. although like I
said I've never actually seen that
and I've
stuffed these things full of coffee many times.
so to fill this
you take your copy which is
like I said not like an espresso ground.
you don't want it to be caking
unnecessarily and you fill this little coffee
filter
all the way to the top. I actually
even fill it slightly over the top.
I am just using lavazza fine ground
espresso coffee in a can from the
store.
that is pretty much what everyone in
Naples used.
Or they would use Kimbo which is a big
local brand everyone liked.
every now and then you see someone
using eely. Eely was probably
you know the premier or the
premium coffee.
It was also from up north and so kind of north
south thing going on Italy where
the southerners didn't cater to
the northern products quite as much and so
the local brands of Kimbo were more
common.
then I just loosely pack it down. now
I'm not to tamping it
I'm not packing it like you would an
espresso. I just don't want it to get all
over the
rubber gasket here. so
just loosely tamp it down. you screw the
top reservoir on.
really tight and it goes right on the
burner on the stove.
my gas stove has a very high flame so
I actually set slightly off-center
so that the plastic handle doesn't get
full force of the flame. then you
want
kind of medium flame on this.
you don't wanna just torch it
because that will just
worsen the problem about this top
reservoir getting really hot and cooking the
coffee.
now we're going to put this on the
burner and what will happen is the water
in the bottom will boil
generate steam. this steam will generate
pressure, not a lot,
a little bit of pressure and that
pressure will force the water
down and then up through that siphon
that makes up the coffee cone.
then It'll come up into the upper
reservoir.
you see there's a little tower here
where that the water will come out of
and that will make the coffee. one thing
that
was common, I used to see people do in
Naples was
they would take a small metal pot
almost like a steaming pot of milk
and put all the sugar for the pot of
coffee in. when the first few
drops of coffee came out
from the the top of the moka pot
they would pour that in and cream it
with sugar almost like you're
making a very
concentrated frosting or something.
they would use a spoon and cream that
sugar
and the first few drops of coffee
together.
then when you poured the coffee into
that metal container after it was brewed
it would be almost like a Crema
kind of like a fake crema on top.
I'm not sure what's different. I've
tried doing that the last couple of times
and couldn't get it to work anymore.
I used to do this all the time
fifteen years ago. so either the
sugars different or the coffee is different
or I'm different but
in any case if you see people doing that,
the attempt is to come to a
pseudo crema.
we'll just let this go and we'll
check back in a couple of minutes.
okay we are seeing an action shot here when the
coffee is actually starting to brew.
the water's been on the boil here for
about a minute and should be getting pretty
close.
you'll see that the coffee starts to
first kinda ooze over the side and then it'll start to
sputter a little bit and then it should
come in a steady stream.
here we go the first drops are
coming out.
It's gonna cough a little bit. That is
what they call it where it spits some coffee
and then it will just  pick up a steady
stream. this is actually just
sort of skipping the cough step. you'll see it
coming out in a trickle. this will
speed up
as the the water begins to come down.
It'll get hotter faster and pressure
will increased rapidly and
it'll sort of be sputtering out. that
means it is probably a good time to consider
closing the lid.
because when it gets to the very tail end, when
there's more steam than water
this will tend to sort of sputter our
coffee out.
so let's close the lid.
this should be done hopefully in
about 45 seconds.
okay I can hear that this is just about
done. it's just about sputtering
towards the end.
so as soon as it's finished you want to get
this off the heat.
we don't want to to cook that upper
chamber any more than we need to.
I'm pouring this into a
small glass as opposed to a cup.
before there was a semi hate mail about
that being a traditional corporate.
yeah I know.
I just wanted to show the
consistency of the coffee. I don't have any
clear coffee mug or coffee cup so I'll use
this little
luminar glass.