Fill the bottom chamber with water until just underneath the
steam valve. Put the filter
on top. next
fill the filter with expresso grounds.
the coffee should be loosely packed to the
top of the filter.
be careful not to overfill or pack
it too hard.
if you do pack it too hard your pot
may be in danger of exploding
or you might just wait forever and no
coffee will appear.
the third step is just screw the top of
the coffee pot
on firmly. once you've done that
place this on the heat.
make sure the plastic handle is not too
close to the heat source.
I'm going to leave the lid up for a little
bit so you can see when the coffee starts
to brew.
but it is probably better just to leave it
down
in real life in order to avoid spills.
if you want to add mily to your espresso
while it's brewing, you can heat some on the stove.
I suggest not using milk directly
from your refrigerator as it might make your espresso
too cold.
When the espresso is done brewing, pour the desired amount into
your mug adding milk adding water and enjoy!