First thing we're gonna do is take out the filter. set that aside. we're gonna fill up the water.
so we are gonna be using three hundred forty
milliliters of water
on this particular moka pot. that
just comes
right under the released valve
that you kind of see on the outside.
now that we have that set,
we are just gonna set that
water
that sits at the base aside.
now we will prepare the filter. so
to prepare the filter we're going to be
using 26 grams of coffee.
I'm just gonna lay that out.
we are going to set our grinder and
for the moka pot, I suggest a grind that
is
slightly finer than drip.
as you'll notice here
I grind directly into the basket. much
like you would do for espresso.
I'm gridning directly into the
portafilter. just be careful how much
you settle
because it can easily fit a lot more
than 26 grams in the basket. depends
on how hard you settle.
so it may look a little bit deceptively
low.
an important reminder.
although it looks kind of like the
basket
of an espresso machine, do not tamp it.
a moka pot is not designed to deal with
a pocket that's that dense.
if you tamp it has a good chance of
popping the release valve.
so now that we have
our coffee all set and we have the moka pot reassembled
we will get ready to set it up.
so just turn the heat up to high.
if you are using a stovetop burner then
it's probably going to be medium
medium-high. we're just gonna hit the clock.
okay so now we have a top view. so this
total process should take about five
minutes
start to finish depending on how fast
takes your water to heat up.
so we're actually gonna go ahead and
skip
towards the end. so this is about four
minutes 45 seconds now into it.
we're gonna see that the coffee is
beginning to come out. so
right as the coffee begins to come out I
like to lower the heat to about fifty
percent of what it was.
so for me it's lowering it from high to
medium. if you are on the stovetop then maybe
from medium-high to medium-low
or something like that. what we are going to do is
we are going to wait
as it approaches the
very base of the spout. right as it hits
the base of the spout we're gonna turn off
the heat altogether.
so it's right about now. right at the
beginning of the spout. so
turning off the heat and the residual
heat is actually gonna carry this
extraction all the way to the end. the
reason to lowering the heat is that we really
don't want
the water to be bursting
out at the bottom from start to finish.
we really wanna kinda temper that heat and
tempe that pressure because remember
controlling that heat is also controlling the
pressure and the rate at which the
water's coming out from the bottom. if the heat is
on full blast
the whole way through then it'll definitely
be splattering out. so
now that we're finished we're gonna go
ahead and
pour the moka pot. so if you're using a
stovetop burner
or an electric one you might wanna
take it off the actual burner as it
will continue to
heat the moka pot even after. So we're just
gonna go ahead and pour.
first pour carefully especially if you are
pouring from such a high distance.